<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>The Philips Videopac+ G7400 is a third-generation home video game console released in limited quantities in 1983, and only in Europe; an American release as the Odyssey³ Command Center was planned but never occurred. The G7400 was the successor to the Philips Videopac G7000, the European counterpart to the American Magnavox Odyssey². The system featured excellently tailored background and foreground graphics. The G7400 could play three types of games: all normal G7000 games, special G7000 games with additional high-res background graphics that would appear only when played on the G7400, and G7400-only games with high-res sprites and backgrounds.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">La Philips Videopac+ G7400 es una videoconsola dome'stica de tercera generación lanzada en cantidades limitadas en 1983, y sólo en Europa; se planeó un lanzamiento americano como Odyssey³ Command Center, pero nunca se produjo. La G7400 fue la sucesora de la Philips Videopac G7000, homóloga europea de la Magnavox Odyssey² estadounidense. El sistema ofrecía gráficos de fondo y primer plano excelentemente adaptados. El G7400 podía reproducir tres tipos de juegos: todos los juegos normales del G7000, juegos especiales del G7000 con gráficos de fondo de alta resolución adicionales que sólo aparecían cuando se jugaba en el G7400, y juegos exclusivos del G7400 con sprites y fondos de alta resolución.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Der Philips Videopac+ G7400 ist eine Heimvideospielkonsole der dritten Generation, die 1983 in begrenzter Stückzahl und nur in Europa auf den Markt kam; eine amerikanische Veröffentlichung als Odyssey³ Command Center war geplant, kam aber nie zustande. Das G7400 war der Nachfolger des Philips Videopac G7000, des europäischen Gegenstücks zum amerikanischen Magnavox Odyssey². Das System zeichnete sich durch exzellent abgestimmte Hintergrund- und Vordergrundgrafiken aus. Auf dem G7400 konnten drei Arten von Spielen gespielt werden: alle normalen G7000-Spiele, spezielle G7000-Spiele mit zusätzlicher hochauflösender Hintergrundgrafik, die nur auf dem G7400 erschien, und reine G7400-Spiele mit hochauflösenden Sprites und Hintergründen.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">La Philips Videopac+ G7400 est une console de jeux vide'o de salon de troisie'me ge'ne'ration commercialise'e en quantite's limite'es en 1983, et uniquement en Europe ; une sortie ame'ricaine sous le nom d'Odyssey³ Command Center e'tait pre'vue mais n'a jamais eu lieu. La G7400 e'tait le successeur de la Philips Videopac G7000, le pendant europe'en de la Magnavox Odyssey² ame'ricaine. Le syste'me pre'sentait des graphiques d'arrie're-plan et d'avant-plan parfaitement adapte's. Le G7400 pouvait jouer a' trois types de jeux : tous les jeux normaux du G7000, les jeux spe'ciaux du G7000 avec des graphiques d'arrie're-plan haute re'solution supple'mentaires qui n'apparaissaient que sur le G7400, et les jeux re'serve's au G7400 avec des sprites et des arrie're-plans haute re'solution.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Il Philips Videopac+ G7400 e' una console per videogiochi domestica di terza generazione rilasciata in quantita' limitate nel 1983, e solo in Europa; un'uscita americana con il nome di Odyssey³ Command Center era prevista ma non e' mai avvenuta. Il G7400 era il successore del Philips Videopac G7000, la controparte europea dell'americana Magnavox Odyssey². Il sistema era dotato di una grafica di sfondo e di primo piano ottimamente adattata. Il G7400 poteva riprodurre tre tipi di giochi: tutti i normali giochi del G7000, i giochi speciali del G7000 con grafica di sfondo aggiuntiva ad alta risoluzione che appariva solo quando si giocava sul G7400 e i giochi solo per il G7400 con sprite e sfondi ad alta risoluzione.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




