<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>Here is a collection of all the games created by Eighting Co., Ltd. and featured on this machine.                                                  Eighting Co., Ltd. (also known as 8ing or Raizing) is a Japanese software company. Founded in 1993, it produces shooter and fighting game video games. Among the titles developed by the company are 1944: The Loop Master, Fate/Unlimited Codes, and Castlevania Judgment.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Ecco una raccolta di tutti i giochi creati dalla Eighting Co., Ltd. e presenti su questa macchina.                                                  La Eighting Co., Ltd. (anche nota come 8ing o Raizing) e' una software house giapponese.Fondata nel 1993, produce videogiochi di genere sparatutto e picchiaduro. Alcuni dei titoli sviluppati dall'azienda sono 1944: The Loop Master, Fate/unlimited codes e Castlevania Judgment.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Voici une collection de tous les jeux cre'e's par Eighting Co., Ltd. et disponibles sur cette machine.                                                  Eighting Co., Ltd. (e'galement connue sous le nom de 8ing ou Raizing) est une socie'te' japonaise de de'veloppement de logiciels. Fonde'e en 1993, elle produit des jeux vide'o de tir et de combat. Parmi ses titres figurent 1944: The Loop Master, Fate/Unlimited Codes et Castlevania Judgment.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Hier ist eine Sammlung aller von Eighting Co., Ltd. entwickelten und auf dieser Maschine enthaltenen Spiele.                                                   Eighting Co., Ltd. (auch bekannt als 8ing oder Raizing) ist ein japanisches Softwareunternehmen. Es wurde 1993 gegründet und produziert Shooter- und Kampfspiele. Zu den von dem Unternehmen entwickelten Titeln gehören 1944: The Loop Master, Fate/Unlimited Codes und Castlevania Judgment.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">Aquí tene'is una recopilación de todos los juegos creados por Eighting Co., Ltd. e incluidos en esta máquina.                                                  Eighting Co., Ltd. (tambie'n conocida como 8ing o Raizing) es una empresa de software japonesa. Fundada en 1993, produce videojuegos de disparos y lucha. Entre los títulos desarrollados por la compañía se encuentran 1944: The Loop Master, Fate/Unlimited Codes y Castlevania Judgment.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>





