<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>Hypseus SINGE, Somewhat Interactive Nostalgic Game Engine, (named after the dragon from Dragon's Lair) is the logical evolution of the Daphne emulator, which uses a Lua-based scripting system to quickly simulate LaserDisc games or create completely new games based on video files! The language is easy to learn, very powerful and fast. All the functions needed to develop your own game are available through a simple application programming interface (API).<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Hypseus SINGE, Somewhat Interactive Nostalgic Game Engine, (benannt nach dem Drachen aus Dragon's Lair) ist die logische Weiterentwicklung des Daphne-Emulators, der ein Lua-basiertes Skripting-System verwendet, um LaserDisc-Spiele schnell zu simulieren oder völlig neue Spiele auf der Grundlage von Videodateien zu erstellen! Die Sprache ist leicht zu erlernen, sehr leistungsfähig und schnell. Alle Funktionen, die Sie zur Entwicklung Ihres eigenen Spiels benötigen, sind über eine einfache Programmierschnittstelle (API) verfügbar.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Hypseus SINGE, Somewhat Interactive Nostalgic Game Engine, (nomme' d'apre's le dragon de Dragon's Lair) est l'e'volution logique de l'e'mulateur Daphne, qui utilise un syste'me de script base' sur Lua pour simuler rapidement des jeux LaserDisc ou cre'er des jeux comple'tement nouveaux base's sur des fichiers vide'o ! Le langage est facile a' apprendre, tre's puissant et rapide. Toutes les fonctions ne'cessaires au de'veloppement de votre propre jeu sont disponibles via une simple interface de programmation d'applications (API).<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Hypseus SINGE, Somewhat Interactive Nostalgic Game Engine, (dal nome del drago di Dragon's Lair) e' la logica evoluzione dell'emulatore Daphne, che utilizza un sistema di scripting basato su Lua per simulare rapidamente giochi LaserDisc o creare giochi completamente nuovi basati su file video! Il linguaggio e' facile da imparare, molto potente e veloce. Tutte le funzioni necessarie per sviluppare il proprio gioco sono disponibili attraverso una semplice interfaccia di programmazione delle applicazioni (API).<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




