<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>Here is a collection of all the games created by Atari and featured on this machine. - Atari is an American video game and gaming hardware manufacturer founded in 1972 by Nolan Bushnell and Ted Dabney. The company played a significant role in the development of arcade video games[3] and personal computers, assuming a dominant position in the world market until the early 1980s. The brand has been acquired several times by competing companies: Infogrames acquired it following its purchase of Hasbro Interactive, which in turn had bought it from JTS Corporation, which had merged with the original Atari in 1996; it then became the property of Atari SA, formerly known as Infogrames SA. Infogrames Inc. sporadically used the "Atari" trademark as a trademark for select titles before Infogrames S.A. officially changed the name of its subsidiary company to Atari, Inc. in 2003. The trademark was also used several times by Atari Games, a different company that spun off in 1984. It should not be confused with Atari S.A., which was founded in 1993 under the name Atari, Inc. -<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Ecco una raccolta di tutti i giochi creati dall' Atari e presenti su questa macchina. -Atari è una società statunitense produttrice di videogiochi e di hardware per uso videoludico fondata nel 1972 da Nolan Bushnell e Ted Dabney. La società ha avuto un ruolo rilevante nello sviluppo dei videogiochi arcade[3] e dei personal computer, assumendo una posizione di predominio nel mercato mondiale sino all'inizio degli anni ottanta. Il marchio è stato più volte rilevato da società concorrenti: Infogrames lo acquisì in seguito all'acquisto di Hasbro Interactive, che a sua volta lo aveva comprato da JTS Corporation, che si era fusa con l'originale Atari nel 1996; è divenuta quindi proprietà di Atari SA, precedentemente nota come Infogrames SA. Infogrames Inc. ha sporadicamente utilizzato il marchio "Atari" come marca commerciale per titoli selezionati prima che Infogrames SA cambiasse ufficialmente il nome dell'azienda subordinata in Atari, Inc. nel 2003. Il marchio è stato anche usato varie volte dalla Atari Games, una differente società che si è staccata nel 1984. Non va confusa con Atari SA, fondata nel 1993 sotto il nome di Atari, Inc. -<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Voici une collection de tous les jeux créés par Atari et disponibles sur cette machine. - Atari est un fabricant américain de jeux vidéo et de matériel de jeu, fondé en 1972 par Nolan Bushnell et Ted Dabney. L'entreprise a joué un rôle majeur dans le développement des jeux d'arcade[3] et des ordinateurs personnels, occupant une position dominante sur le marché mondial jusqu'au début des années 1980. La marque a été rachetée à plusieurs reprises par des entreprises concurrentes : Infogrames l'a acquise après avoir racheté Hasbro Interactive, qui l'avait elle-même acquise auprès de JTS Corporation, laquelle avait fusionné avec Atari en 1996; elle est alors devenue la propriété d'Atari SA, anciennement connue sous le nom d'Infogrames SA. Infogrames Inc. a utilisé sporadiquement la marque « Atari » pour certains titres avant qu'Infogrames S.A. ne change officiellement le nom de sa filiale en Atari, Inc. en 2003. La marque a également été utilisée à plusieurs reprises par Atari Games, une société distincte créée en 1984. Il ne faut pas la confondre avec Atari S.A., fondée en 1993 sous le nom d'Atari, Inc. -<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Hier ist eine Sammlung aller von Atari entwickelten und auf dieser Maschine enthaltenen Spiele. - Atari ist ein US-amerikanischer Hersteller von Videospielen und Spielkonsolen, der 1972 von Nolan Bushnell und Ted Dabney gegründet wurde. Das Unternehmen spielte eine bedeutende Rolle in der Entwicklung von Arcade-Videospielen[3] und Personalcomputern und nahm bis Anfang der 1980er-Jahre eine dominante Stellung auf dem Weltmarkt ein. Die Marke wurde mehrmals von Konkurrenten übernommen: Infogrames erwarb sie nach der Übernahme von Hasbro Interactive, das sie wiederum von der JTS Corporation gekauft hatte, welche 1996 mit dem ursprünglichen Atari fusioniert hatte; anschließend ging sie in den Besitz der Atari SA über, die zuvor als Infogrames SA bekannt war. Infogrames Inc. nutzte die Marke „Atari“ sporadisch für ausgewählte Titel, bevor Infogrames S.A. den Namen ihrer Tochtergesellschaft 2003 offiziell in Atari, Inc. änderte. Die Marke wurde auch mehrmals von Atari Games verwendet, einem anderen Unternehmen, das 1984 ausgegliedert wurde. Sie sollte nicht mit Atari S.A. verwechselt werden, die 1993 unter dem Namen Atari, Inc. gegründet wurde. -<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">Aquí tenéis una recopilación de todos los juegos creados por Atari e incluidos en esta máquina. - Atari es un fabricante estadounidense de videojuegos y hardware para videojuegos fundado en 1972 por Nolan Bushnell y Ted Dabney. La compañía desempeñó un papel importante en el desarrollo de videojuegos arcade[3] y computadoras personales, alcanzando una posición dominante en el mercado mundial hasta principios de la década de 1980. La marca ha sido adquirida varias veces por empresas competidoras: Infogrames la adquirió tras la compra de Hasbro Interactive, que a su vez la había comprado a JTS Corporation, la cual se fusionó con la Atari original en 1996; posteriormente, pasó a ser propiedad de Atari SA, anteriormente conocida como Infogrames SA. Infogrames Inc. utilizó esporádicamente la marca registrada "Atari" para algunos títulos antes de que Infogrames S.A. cambiara oficialmente el nombre de su filial a Atari, Inc. en 2003. La marca también fue utilizada en varias ocasiones por Atari Games, una empresa distinta que se independizó en 1984. No debe confundirse con Atari S.A., fundada en 1993 con el nombre de Atari, Inc. -<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




