<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>eXoDOS is an attempt to catalog, obtain, and make playable every game developed for the DOS and PC Booter platform. We strive to find original media rather than using scene rips or hacks. This collection uses DOSBox to allow these older games to play on modern systems. Games supported by ScummVM give the user a choice between emulators. All required emulators are included and have been setup to run all included titles with no prior knowledge or experience required on the user's part. This pack includes 7,666 DOS games. The focus is on games that were either released in English or are fairly easy to play without a knowledge of the native language. This is not every DOS game ever made, however it is a very high percentage of all commercial releases. There are thousands of freeware, homebrew, and shareware games that will continue to be added in future packs. Non English games will be released in Language Packs. Currently several are in development. All language packs require the base English pack to function properly. There is also an optional Media Pack Add-On, which can be downloaded below. This adds books, catalogs, magazines, and game soundtracks to eXoDOS. The games have already been configured to run in DOSBox. <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">eXoDOS è un progetto che si propone di catalogare, reperire e rendere giocabili tutti i giochi sviluppati per le piattaforme DOS e PC Booter. Ci impegniamo a trovare supporti originali piuttosto che utilizzare versioni pirata o hack. Questa collezione utilizza DOSBox per permettere a questi vecchi giochi di essere eseguiti sui sistemi moderni. I giochi supportati da ScummVM offrono all'utente la possibilità di scegliere tra diversi emulatori. Tutti gli emulatori necessari sono inclusi e configurati per eseguire tutti i titoli inclusi senza richiedere alcuna conoscenza o esperienza pregressa da parte dell'utente. Questo pacchetto include 7.666 giochi DOS. L'attenzione è rivolta ai giochi che sono stati pubblicati in inglese o che sono abbastanza facili da giocare anche senza conoscere la lingua originale. Non si tratta di tutti i giochi DOS mai realizzati, tuttavia rappresenta un'altissima percentuale di tutte le uscite commerciali. Migliaia di giochi freeware, homebrew e shareware continueranno ad essere aggiunti nei pacchetti futuri. I giochi non in inglese saranno rilasciati in pacchetti lingua. Attualmente diversi sono in fase di sviluppo. Tutti i pacchetti lingua richiedono il pacchetto base in inglese per funzionare correttamente. È disponibile anche un pacchetto multimediale aggiuntivo opzionale, scaricabile qui sotto. Questo pacchetto aggiunge libri, cataloghi, riviste e colonne sonore di videogiochi a eXoDOS. I giochi sono già configurati per funzionare in DOSBox.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">eXoDOS est un projet visant à cataloguer, obtenir et rendre jouables tous les jeux développés pour DOS et la plateforme PC Booter. Nous privilégions les supports originaux plutôt que les copies ou les modifications. Cette collection utilise DOSBox pour permettre à ces jeux anciens de fonctionner sur les systèmes modernes. Les jeux compatibles avec ScummVM offrent à l'utilisateur le choix entre plusieurs émulateurs. Tous les émulateurs requis sont inclus et configurés pour exécuter tous les titres inclus, sans aucune connaissance préalable requise. Ce pack contient 7 666 jeux DOS. L'accent est mis sur les jeux sortis en anglais ou relativement faciles à jouer sans connaître la langue. Il ne s'agit pas de tous les jeux DOS jamais créés, mais d'un pourcentage très élevé des jeux commerciaux. Des milliers de jeux gratuits, amateurs et shareware seront ajoutés dans de futurs packs. Les jeux non anglophones seront disponibles dans des packs de langue. Plusieurs sont actuellement en développement. Tous les packs de langue nécessitent le pack anglais de base pour fonctionner correctement. Un pack média optionnel est également disponible en téléchargement ci-dessous. Ce module ajoute des livres, des catalogues, des magazines et des bandes originales de jeux à eXoDOS. Les jeux sont déjà configurés pour fonctionner sous DOSBox.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">eXoDOS ist ein Projekt, das alle für DOS und PC Booter entwickelten Spiele katalogisiert, beschafft und spielbar macht. Wir bemühen uns, Originaldateien zu finden, anstatt Szenen-Rips oder Hacks zu verwenden. Diese Sammlung nutzt DOSBox, um ältere Spiele auf modernen Systemen spielbar zu machen. Spiele, die von ScummVM unterstützt werden, bieten dem Benutzer die Wahl zwischen verschiedenen Emulatoren. Alle benötigten Emulatoren sind enthalten und so eingerichtet, dass alle enthaltenen Titel ohne Vorkenntnisse oder Erfahrung des Benutzers ausgeführt werden können. Dieses Paket umfasst 7.666 DOS-Spiele. Der Schwerpunkt liegt auf Spielen, die entweder auf Englisch veröffentlicht wurden oder relativ einfach ohne Englischkenntnisse zu spielen sind. Es handelt sich nicht um alle jemals erschienenen DOS-Spiele, aber um einen sehr hohen Prozentsatz aller kommerziellen Veröffentlichungen. Tausende von Freeware-, Homebrew- und Shareware-Spielen werden in zukünftigen Paketen hinzugefügt. Nicht-englische Spiele werden in Sprachpaketen veröffentlicht. Derzeit befinden sich mehrere in Entwicklung. Alle Sprachpakete benötigen das englische Basispaket, um ordnungsgemäß zu funktionieren. Es gibt außerdem ein optionales Medienpaket, das Sie unten herunterladen können. Dieses fügt eXoDOS Bücher, Kataloge, Zeitschriften und Spielsoundtracks hinzu. Die Spiele sind bereits für die Ausführung in DOSBox konfiguriert.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">eXoDOS es un intento de catalogar, obtener y hacer jugables todos los juegos desarrollados para la plataforma DOS y PC Booter. Nos esforzamos por encontrar material original en lugar de usar copias piratas o modificaciones. Esta colección utiliza DOSBox para permitir que estos juegos antiguos se jueguen en sistemas modernos. Los juegos compatibles con ScummVM ofrecen al usuario la posibilidad de elegir entre emuladores. Todos los emuladores necesarios están incluidos y configurados para ejecutar todos los títulos incluidos sin necesidad de conocimientos ni experiencia previos por parte del usuario. Este paquete incluye 7666 juegos de DOS. Nos centramos en juegos que se lanzaron en inglés o que son relativamente fáciles de jugar sin conocer el idioma original. No se trata de todos los juegos de DOS jamás creados, pero sí de un porcentaje muy alto de todos los lanzamientos comerciales. Hay miles de juegos gratuitos, caseros y de prueba que se seguirán añadiendo en futuros paquetes. Los juegos que no estén en inglés se publicarán en paquetes de idiomas. Actualmente, varios están en desarrollo. Todos los paquetes de idiomas requieren el paquete base en inglés para funcionar correctamente. También hay un complemento opcional de paquete multimedia, que se puede descargar a continuación. Esto añade libros, catálogos, revistas y bandas sonoras de juegos a eXoDOS. Los juegos ya están configurados para ejecutarse en DOSBox.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




