<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>

	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <pos>0.95 0.8</pos>
         <origin>1 0</origin>
         <size>0.90 0.1</size>
         <backgroundColor>00000000</backgroundColor>
         <color>F5F5F5</color>
         <fontPath>${themePath}/_inc/fonts/SF Slapstick Comic Bold.ttf</fontPath>
         <fontSize>0.055</fontSize>
         <text>Tiger is most well known for their low-end handheld electronic game systems with LCD screens. Each unit contains a fixed image printed onto the handheld that can be seen through the screen. Static images then light up individually in front of the background that represent characters and objects, similar to numbers on a calculator or digital clock. In addition to putting out some of its own games, Tiger was able to secure licenses from many of the time's top selling companies to sell their own versions of games such as Capcom's Street Fighter II, Sega's Sonic 3D Blast, and Konami's Castlevania II: Simon's Quest. Later, Tiger introduced what they called "wrist games". These combined a digital watch with a scaled-down version of a Tiger handheld game.</text>
			<text lang="es">Tiger es más conocida por sus sistemas de juegos electrónicos portátiles de gama baja con pantallas LCD. Cada unidad contiene una imagen fija impresa en el dispositivo portátil que puede verse a través de la pantalla. Las imágenes estáticas se iluminan individualmente delante del fondo y representan personajes y objetos, como los números de una calculadora o un reloj digital. Además de sacar algunos de sus propios juegos, Tiger consiguió licencias de muchas de las empresas más vendidas de la época para vender sus propias versiones de juegos como Street Fighter II de Capcom, Sonic 3D Blast de Sega y Castlevania II: Simon's Quest de Konami. Más tarde, Tiger introdujo lo que llamaron "juegos de muñeca". Combinaban un reloj digital con una versión reducida de un juego de mano de Tiger.</text>
			<text lang="de">Tiger ist vor allem für seine elektronischen Handheld-Spielsysteme mit LCD-Bildschirmen im unteren Preissegment bekannt. Jedes Gerät enthält ein festes, auf das Handheld gedrucktes Bild, das durch den Bildschirm hindurch gesehen werden kann. Statische Bilder leuchten dann einzeln vor dem Hintergrund auf, die Zeichen und Objekte darstellen, ähnlich wie die Zahlen auf einem Taschenrechner oder einer Digitaluhr. Tiger brachte nicht nur eigene Spiele auf den Markt, sondern sicherte sich auch Lizenzen von vielen der damals meistverkauften Unternehmen, um ihre eigenen Versionen von Spielen wie Street Fighter II von Capcom, Sonic 3D Blast von Sega und Castlevania II: Simon's Quest von Konami zu verkaufen. Später führte Tiger die so genannten "Handgelenkspiele" ein. Diese kombinierten eine Digitaluhr mit einer verkleinerten Version eines Tiger-Handheld-Spiels.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Tiger est surtout connu pour ses systèmes de jeux électroniques portables bas de gamme dotés d'écrans LCD. Chaque unité contient une image fixe imprimée sur l'ordinateur de poche qui peut être vue à travers l'écran. Des images statiques s'allument ensuite individuellement devant l'arrière-plan pour représenter des personnages et des objets, comme les chiffres d'une calculatrice ou d'une horloge numérique. En plus de produire ses propres jeux, Tiger a pu obtenir des licences de la part de nombreuses sociétés les plus vendues à l'époque pour vendre leurs propres versions de jeux tels que Street Fighter II de Capcom, Sonic 3D Blast de Sega et Castlevania II : Simon's Quest de Konami. Plus tard, Tiger a introduit ce qu'il a appelé les "jeux de poignet". Ceux-ci combinaient une montre numérique avec une version réduite d'un jeu portable de Tiger.</text>
			<text lang="it">Tiger è nota soprattutto per i suoi dispositivi portatili di fascia bassa con schermo LCD. Ogni unità contiene un'immagine fissa stampata sul dispositivo portatile che può essere vista attraverso lo schermo. Le immagini statiche si illuminano singolarmente davanti allo sfondo e rappresentano personaggi e oggetti, simili ai numeri di una calcolatrice o di un orologio digitale. Oltre a produrre alcuni dei propri giochi, Tiger fu in grado di ottenere licenze da molte delle aziende più vendute dell'epoca per vendere le proprie versioni di giochi come Street Fighter II di Capcom, Sonic 3D Blast di Sega e Castlevania II: Simon's Quest di Konami. In seguito, Tiger introdusse i cosiddetti "giochi da polso". Questi combinavano un orologio digitale con una versione ridotta di un dispositivo portatile Tiger.</text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>
				<multiLine>false</multiLine>
				<autoScrollDelay>3000</autoScrollDelay>
				<singleLineScroll>true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>

</theme>