<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>The PocketStation is a Memory Card peripheral by Sony Computer Entertainment for the PlayStation home video game console. Categorized by Sony as a combination of a Memory Card and a miniature personal digital assistant, the device features a monochrome liquid crystal display (LCD), infrared communication capability, a real-time clock, built-in flash memory, and sound capability. To use the device's memory card functionality, it must be connected to a PlayStation through a memory card slot. It was released exclusively in Japan on January 23, 1999. Software for the PocketStation was typically distributed as extras for PlayStation games, included in the CD-ROM, enhancing the games with added features. Stand-alone software could also be downloaded through the PlayStation console. The software is then transferred to the PocketStation for use. A built-in infrared data interface allows direct transfer of data such as game saves between PocketStation units, as well as multiplayer gaming.</text>
			<text lang="es">La PocketStation es un perife'rico de tarjeta de memoria de Sony Computer Entertainment para la videoconsola dome'stica PlayStation. Clasificado por Sony como una combinación de tarjeta de memoria y asistente digital personal en miniatura, el dispositivo cuenta con una pantalla monocroma de cristal líquido (LCD), capacidad de comunicación por infrarrojos, reloj en tiempo real, memoria flash integrada y capacidad de sonido. Para utilizar la funcionalidad de tarjeta de memoria del dispositivo, debe conectarse a una PlayStation a trave's de una ranura de tarjeta de memoria. Salió a la venta exclusivamente en Japón el 23 de enero de 1999. El software para la PocketStation se distribuía normalmente como extras para los juegos de PlayStation, incluidos en el CD-ROM, mejorando los juegos con funciones añadidas. El software independiente tambie'n podía descargarse a trave's de la consola PlayStation. A continuación, el software se transfería a la PocketStation para su uso. Una interfaz de datos por infrarrojos integrada permite la transferencia directa de datos, como las partidas guardadas, entre unidades PocketStation, así como el juego multijugador.</text>
			<text lang="de">Die PocketStation ist ein Speicherkarten-Peripheriegerät von Sony Computer Entertainment für die Heimvideospielkonsole PlayStation. Das Gerät, das von Sony als eine Kombination aus einer Memory Card und einem Miniatur-Personal-Digital-Assistenten bezeichnet wird, verfügt über ein monochromes Flüssigkristall-Display (LCD), eine Infrarot-Kommunikationsfunktion, eine Echtzeituhr, einen integrierten Flash-Speicher und eine Soundfunktion. Um die Speicherkartenfunktion des Geräts nutzen zu können, muss es über einen Speicherkartensteckplatz mit einer PlayStation verbunden werden. Es wurde am 23. Januar 1999 exklusiv in Japan veröffentlicht. Software für die PocketStation wurde in der Regel als Extras für PlayStation-Spiele vertrieben, die auf der CD-ROM enthalten waren und die Spiele mit zusätzlichen Funktionen ausstatteten. Eigenständige Software konnte auch über die PlayStation-Konsole heruntergeladen werden. Die Software wird dann zur Verwendung auf die PocketStation übertragen. Eine eingebaute Infrarot-Datenschnittstelle ermöglicht die direkte Übertragung von Daten wie Spielständen zwischen PocketStation-Einheiten sowie Multiplayer-Spiele.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La PocketStation est un pe'riphe'rique a' carte me'moire de Sony Computer Entertainment pour la console de jeux vide'o PlayStation. Classe' par Sony comme la combinaison d'une carte me'moire et d'un assistant nume'rique personnel miniature, l'appareil est dote' d'un e'cran a' cristaux liquides (LCD) monochrome, d'une capacite' de communication infrarouge, d'une horloge en temps re'el, d'une me'moire flash inte'gre'e et d'une capacite' sonore. Pour utiliser la fonctionnalite' de carte me'moire de l'appareil, celui-ci doit être connecte' a' une PlayStation par le biais d'un emplacement de carte me'moire. Il est sorti exclusivement au Japon le 23 janvier 1999. Les logiciels pour la PocketStation e'taient ge'ne'ralement distribue's en tant qu'extras pour les jeux PlayStation, inclus dans le CD-ROM, ame'liorant les jeux avec des fonctionnalite's supple'mentaires. Les logiciels autonomes peuvent e'galement être te'le'charge's via la console PlayStation. Le logiciel est ensuite transfe're' sur la PocketStation pour être utilise'. Une interface de donne'es infrarouge inte'gre'e permet le transfert direct de donne'es telles que les sauvegardes de jeux entre les unite's PocketStation, ainsi que les jeux multijoueurs.</text>
			<text lang="it">PocketStation e' una periferica per schede di memoria di Sony Computer Entertainment per la console di videogiochi domestica PlayStation. Classificato da Sony come una combinazione tra una Memory Card e un assistente digitale personale in miniatura, il dispositivo e' dotato di un display monocromatico a cristalli liquidi (LCD), capacita' di comunicazione a infrarossi, orologio in tempo reale, memoria flash integrata e capacita' audio. Per utilizzare le funzionalita' della scheda di memoria, il dispositivo deve essere collegato a una PlayStation attraverso uno slot per schede di memoria. e' stato rilasciato esclusivamente in Giappone il 23 gennaio 1999. Il software per la PocketStation veniva solitamente distribuito come extra per i giochi per PlayStation, incluso nel CD-ROM, migliorando i giochi con funzioni aggiuntive. Il software stand-alone poteva anche essere scaricato attraverso la console PlayStation. Il software viene poi trasferito alla PocketStation per essere utilizzato. Un'interfaccia dati a infrarossi integrata consente il trasferimento diretto di dati, come i salvataggi di gioco, tra le unita' PocketStation e il gioco multiplayer.</text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>
				<multiLine>false</multiLine>
				<autoScrollDelay>3000</autoScrollDelay>
				<singleLineScroll>true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>

