<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>The Neo Geo Pocket is a monochrome handheld game console released by SNK. It was the company's first handheld system and is part of the Neo Geo family. It debuted in Japan in late 1998 but never saw an American release, being exclusive to Japan, Asia and Europe. The Neo Geo Pocket is considered to be an unsuccessful console. Lower than expected sales resulted in its discontinuation in 1999, and was immediately succeeded by the Neo Geo Pocket Color, a full color device allowing the system to compete more easily with the dominant Game Boy Color handheld, and which also saw an American release. Though the system enjoyed only a short life, there were some significant games released on the system such as Samurai Shodown, and King of Fighters R-1.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">La Neo Geo Pocket es una consola portátil monocroma lanzada por SNK. Fue el primer sistema portátil de la compañía y forma parte de la familia Neo Geo. Debutó en Japón a finales de 1998, pero nunca salió a la venta en Ame'rica, siendo exclusiva de Japón, Asia y Europa. La Neo Geo Pocket se considera una consola poco exitosa. Sus ventas, inferiores a las esperadas, provocaron su interrupción en 1999, e inmediatamente fue sustituida por la Neo Geo Pocket Color, un dispositivo a todo color que permitía al sistema competir más fácilmente con la Game Boy Color, la consola portátil dominante, y que tambie'n vio la luz en Estados Unidos. Aunque el sistema tuvo una vida corta, se lanzaron algunos juegos importantes, como Samurai Shodown y King of Fighters R-1.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Das Neo Geo Pocket ist eine monochrome Handheld-Spielkonsole, die von SNK herausgegeben wurde. Es war das erste Handheld-System des Unternehmens und ist Teil der Neo Geo-Familie. Es kam Ende 1998 in Japan auf den Markt, wurde aber nie in den USA veröffentlicht, da es exklusiv in Japan, Asien und Europa erhältlich war. Das Neo Geo Pocket gilt als eine erfolglose Konsole. Geringere Verkaufszahlen als erwartet führten dazu, dass das System 1999 eingestellt wurde. Es wurde sofort vom Neo Geo Pocket Color abgelöst, einem Vollfarbgerät, das es dem System ermöglichte, leichter mit dem dominierenden Game Boy Color Handheld zu konkurrieren, und das auch in Amerika veröffentlicht wurde. Obwohl das System nur eine kurze Lebensdauer hatte, wurden einige bedeutende Spiele wie Samurai Shodown und King of Fighters R-1 auf dem System veröffentlicht.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">La Neo Geo Pocket est une console de jeu portable monochrome e'dite'e par SNK. C'est la premie're console portable de la socie'te' et elle fait partie de la famille Neo Geo. Elle a fait ses de'buts au Japon a' la fin de l'anne'e 1998, mais n'a jamais e'te' commercialise'e aux e'tats-Unis, e'tant exclusive au Japon, a' l'Asie et a' l'Europe. La Neo Geo Pocket est conside're'e comme un e'chec. Des ventes infe'rieures aux pre'visions ont entraîne' son abandon en 1999, et elle a e'te' imme'diatement remplace'e par la Neo Geo Pocket Color, une console couleur permettant au syste'me de concurrencer plus facilement la console portable dominante Game Boy Color, et qui a e'galement e'te' commercialise'e aux e'tats-Unis. Bien que le syste'me n'ait eu qu'une courte dure'e de vie, quelques jeux importants sont sortis sur la console, comme Samurai Shodown et King of Fighters R-1.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Il Neo Geo Pocket e' una console portatile monocromatica rilasciata da SNK. e' stata la prima console portatile dell'azienda e fa parte della famiglia Neo Geo. Ha debuttato in Giappone alla fine del 1998, ma non ha mai visto un'uscita americana, essendo un'esclusiva di Giappone, Asia ed Europa. Il Neo Geo Pocket e' considerato una console di scarso successo. Le vendite inferiori alle aspettative ne determinarono l'interruzione nel 1999 e fu immediatamente sostituito dal Neo Geo Pocket Color, un dispositivo a colori che permetteva al sistema di competere piU' facilmente con la console portatile Game Boy Color, anch'essa dominante, e che vide un'uscita americana. Sebbene il sistema abbia avuto una vita breve, vi sono stati pubblicati alcuni giochi significativi come Samurai Shodown e King of Fighters R-1.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




