<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>DXX-Rebirth is an open-source source port of the Descent and Descent II game engines, with some key features such as improved OpenGL graphics and effects, advanced multiplayer, stability and enhancements. DXX-Rebirth preserves the classic Descent gameplay while offering modern features and compatibility.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">DXX-Rebirth e' un porting open-source dei motori di gioco Descent e Descent II, con alcune caratteristiche chiave come grafica ed effetti OpenGL migliorati, multiplayer avanzato, stabilita' e miglioramenti. DXX-Rebirth conserva il classico gameplay di Descent, offrendo al contempo funzionalita' e compatibilita' moderne.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">DXX-Rebirth est un portage open-source des moteurs de jeu Descent e Descent II, avec quelques caracte'ristiques cle's telles que des graphismes et des effets OpenGL ame'liore's, un multijoueur avance', de la stabilite' et des ame'liorations. DXX-Rebirth pre'serve le gameplay classique de Descent tout en offrant des fonctionnalite's et une compatibilite' modernes.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">DXX-Rebirth ist eine quelloffene Portierung der Descent- und Descent II-Spiele-Engines mit einigen wichtigen Funktionen wie verbesserten OpenGL-Grafiken und -Effekten, erweitertem Multiplayer-Modus, Stabilität und Erweiterungen. DXX-Rebirth bewahrt das klassische Descent-Gameplay und bietet gleichzeitig moderne Funktionen und Kompatibilität.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">DXX-Rebirth es un port de código abierto de los motores de juego Descent y Descent II, con algunas características clave como gráficos y efectos OpenGL mejorados, multijugador avanzado, estabilidad y mejoras. DXX-Rebirth conserva la jugabilidad clásica de Descent a la vez que ofrece características modernas y compatibilidad.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




