<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>TheXTech is an open-source engine that allows you to play the classic Super Mario Bros. X (SMBX) games from 1.0 to 1.3. It is a recreation of the original SMBX engine that was written in Visual Basic 6 and later ported to C++ and SDL2. The project is hosted on GitHub and is actively developed by Wohlstand and other contributors.  TheXTech is available as a standalone version for Windows, Linux, macOS, Android, and Nintendo Switch. The engine also supports LunaDLL Autocode (LunaScript) via a memory emulator, allowing you to play more old episodes on TheXTech even on non-x86 processors.</text>
			<text lang="it">TheXTech e' un motore open-source che consente di giocare ai classici giochi di Super Mario Bros. X (SMBX) dalla 1.0 alla 1.3. Si tratta di una ricreazione del motore SMBX originale, scritto in Visual Basic 6 e successivamente portato in C++ e SDL2. Il progetto e' ospitato su GitHub ed e' attivamente sviluppato da Wohlstand e da altri collaboratori. TheXTech e' disponibile in versione standalone per Windows, Linux, macOS, Android e Nintendo Switch. Il motore supporta anche LunaDLL Autocode (LunaScript) tramite un emulatore di memoria, consentendo di giocare a piU' vecchi episodi di TheXTech anche su processori non-x86.</text>
			<text lang="fr">TheXTech est un moteur open-source qui vous permet de jouer aux jeux classiques Super Mario Bros. X (SMBX) de 1.0 a' 1.3. Il s'agit d'une recre'ation du moteur SMBX original, e'crit en Visual Basic 6, puis porte' en C++ et SDL2. Le projet est he'berge' sur GitHub et est activement de'veloppe' par Wohlstand et d'autres contributeurs. TheXTech est disponible en version autonome pour Windows, Linux, macOS, Android et Nintendo Switch. Le moteur prend e'galement en charge l'autocode LunaDLL (LunaScript) via un e'mulateur de me'moire, ce qui vous permet de jouer a' plus d'anciens e'pisodes sur TheXTech, même sur des processeurs non-x86.</text>
			<text lang="de">TheXTech ist eine Open-Source-Engine, mit der Sie die klassischen Super Mario Bros. X (SMBX)-Spiele von 1.0 bis 1.3 spielen können. Es ist eine Nachbildung der ursprünglichen SMBX-Engine, die in Visual Basic 6 geschrieben und später auf C++ und SDL2 portiert wurde. Das Projekt wird auf GitHub gehostet und von Wohlstand und anderen Mitwirkenden aktiv weiterentwickelt. TheXTech ist als eigenständige Version für Windows, Linux, macOS, Android und Nintendo Switch erhältlich. Die Engine unterstützt auch LunaDLL Autocode (LunaScript) über einen Speicheremulator, so dass Sie mehr alte Episoden auf TheXTech auch auf nicht-x86-Prozessoren spielen können.</text>
			<text lang="es">TheXTech es un motor de código abierto que permite jugar a los juegos clásicos de Super Mario Bros. X (SMBX) desde la versión 1.0 a la 1.3. Se trata de una recreación del motor SMBX original, escrito en Visual Basic 6 y portado posteriormente a C++ y SDL2. El proyecto está alojado en GitHub y es desarrollado activamente por Wohlstand y otros colaboradores. TheXTech está disponible como versión independiente para Windows, Linux, macOS, Android y Nintendo Switch. El motor tambie'n es compatible con LunaDLL Autocode (LunaScript) a trave's de un emulador de memoria, lo que permite reproducir más episodios antiguos en TheXTech incluso en procesadores no x86.</text>
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>
				<multiLine>false</multiLine>
				<autoScrollDelay>3000</autoScrollDelay>
				<singleLineScroll>true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>

