<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>The Enterprise is a Zilog Z80-based home computer announced in 1983, but through a series of delays, not commercially available until 1985. It was developed by British company Intelligent Software and marketed by Enterprise Computers.
The specification as released was powerful and one of the higher end in its class (though not by the margin envisaged in 1983). This was due to the use of custom ASICs for graphics and sound which took workload away from the CPU, an extensive implementation of ANSI BASIC and a bank switching system to allow for larger amounts of RAM than the Z80 natively supported. It also featured a distinctive and colourful case design, and promise of multiple expansion options. Its two variants are the Enterprise 64, with 64 KB of RAM, and the Enterprise 128, with 128 KB of RAM.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">El Enterprise es un ordenador dome'stico basado en el Z80 de Zilog anunciado en 1983, pero que, debido a una serie de retrasos, no estuvo disponible comercialmente hasta 1985. Fue desarrollado por la empresa británica Intelligent Software y comercializado por Enterprise Computers. La especificación con la que salió al mercado era potente y una de las más avanzadas de su clase (aunque no por el margen previsto en 1983). Esto se debía al uso de ASIC personalizados para gráficos y sonido que quitaban carga de trabajo a la CPU, una amplia implementación de ANSI BASIC y un sistema de conmutación de bancos para permitir mayores cantidades de RAM de las que el Z80 soportaba de forma nativa. Tambie'n presentaba un diseño de carcasa distintivo y colorido, y prometía múltiples opciones de expansión. Sus dos variantes son el Enterprise 64, con 64 KB de RAM, y el Enterprise 128, con 128 KB de RAM.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Der Enterprise ist ein Zilog Z80-basierter Heimcomputer, der 1983 angekündigt wurde, aber aufgrund einer Reihe von Verzögerungen erst 1985 auf den Markt kam. Er wurde von der britischen Firma Intelligent Software entwickelt und von Enterprise Computers vermarktet. Die Spezifikation in der veröffentlichten Form war leistungsfähig und gehörte zu den Spitzenreitern seiner Klasse (wenn auch nicht in dem Maße, wie es 1983 geplant war). Dies war auf die Verwendung von kundenspezifischen ASICs für Grafik und Sound zurückzuführen, die die CPU entlasteten, sowie auf eine umfangreiche Implementierung von ANSI BASIC und ein Bank-Switching-System, das größere Mengen an RAM ermöglichte, als der Z80 von Haus aus unterstützte. Außerdem zeichnete er sich durch ein markantes und farbenfrohes Gehäusedesign aus und versprach zahlreiche Erweiterungsmöglichkeiten. Es gibt zwei Varianten: den Enterprise 64 mit 64 KB RAM und den Enterprise 128 mit 128 KB RAM.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">L'Enterprise est un ordinateur domestique base' sur le Zilog Z80 annonce' en 1983, mais qui, en raison d'une se'rie de retards, n'a e'te' commercialise' qu'en 1985. Il a e'te' de'veloppe' par la socie'te' britannique Intelligent Software et commercialise' par Enterprise Computers. La spe'cification publie'e e'tait puissante et l'une des plus haut de gamme de sa cate'gorie (bien que pas avec la marge envisage'e en 1983). Cela e'tait dû a' l'utilisation d'ASIC personnalise's pour les graphiques et le son, ce qui re'duisait la charge de travail de l'unite' centrale, a' une imple'mentation e'tendue du BASIC ANSI et a' un syste'me de commutation de banque permettant d'utiliser des quantite's de RAM plus importantes que celles que le Z80 prenait en charge de manie're native. Il se caracte'risait e'galement par un boîtier distinctif et colore', et promettait de multiples options d'extension. Ses deux variantes sont l'Enterprise 64, avec 64 Ko de RAM, et l'Enterprise 128, avec 128 Ko de RAM.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">L'Enterprise e' un home computer basato sullo Zilog Z80 annunciato nel 1983, ma che, a causa di una serie di ritardi, non fu disponibile in commercio fino al 1985. Fu sviluppato dalla societa' britannica Intelligent Software e commercializzato da Enterprise Computers. Le specifiche cosi' come sono state rilasciate erano potenti e di fascia alta nella sua categoria (anche se non con il margine previsto nel 1983). Cio' era dovuto all'uso di ASIC personalizzati per la grafica e il suono, che sottraevano carico di lavoro alla CPU, a un'implementazione estesa dell'ANSI BASIC e a un sistema di commutazione dei banchi che consentiva di utilizzare quantita' di RAM superiori a quelle supportate dallo Z80. Inoltre, presentava un design distintivo e colorato e prometteva molteplici opzioni di espansione. Le due varianti sono Enterprise 64, con 64 KB di RAM, e Enterprise 128, con 128 KB di RAM.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




