<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>ZiNc is a command-line Windows emulator for arcade hardware based on Sony PlayStation hardware. These hardware systems include Sony ZiNc (ZN1 &amp; ZN2) and Namco System 11. These games are also supported in MAME, but ZiNc can frequently run them faster and with graphics and sound enhancements. The last version of ZiNc from original authors named 'Duddie' (Marcin Dudar; aka TheD / The Author) and 'Tratax' (DynaChicken) was v0.9; after that, they went on to create GCEmu (a Nintendo GameCube emulator) and R.Belmont / SMF took over ZiNc development. The source code was lost and it thus will never receive any further updates.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
		<text lang="it">ZiNc e' un emulatore Windows a riga di comando per hardware arcade basato su hardware Sony PlayStation. Questi sistemi hardware includono Sony ZiNc (ZN1 e ZN2) e Namco System 11. Questi giochi sono supportati anche da MAME, ma ZiNc e' spesso in grado di eseguirli piU' velocemente e con miglioramenti grafici e sonori. L'ultima versione di ZiNc degli autori originali 'Duddie' (Marcin Dudar; alias TheD / The Author) e 'Tratax' (DynaChicken) e' stata la v0.9; in seguito, i due hanno creato GCEmu (un emulatore per Nintendo GameCube) e R.Belmont / SMF si e' occupato dello sviluppo di ZiNc. Il codice sorgente e' andato perso e quindi non ricevera' mai ulteriori aggiornamenti.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
		<text lang="fr">ZiNc est un e'mulateur Windows en ligne de commande pour le mate'riel d'arcade base' sur la PlayStation de Sony. Ces syste'mes incluent le Sony ZiNc (ZN1 &amp; ZN2) et le Namco System 11. Ces jeux sont e'galement supporte's par MAME, mais ZiNc peut souvent les exe'cuter plus rapidement et avec des ame'liorations graphiques et sonores. La dernie're version de ZiNc des auteurs originaux nomme's 'Duddie' (Marcin Dudar ; aka TheD / The Author) et 'Tratax' (DynaChicken) e'tait la v0.9 ; apre's cela, ils ont continue' a' cre'er GCEmu (un e'mulateur Nintendo GameCube) et R.Belmont / SMF a pris en charge le de'veloppement de ZiNc. Le code source a e'te' perdu et il ne recevra donc plus jamais de mises a' jour.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
		<text lang="de">ZiNc ist ein Befehlszeilen-Windows-Emulator für Arcade-Hardware, die auf Sony PlayStation-Hardware basiert. Diese Hardware-Systeme umfassen Sony ZiNc (ZN1 &amp; ZN2) und Namco System 11. Diese Spiele werden auch von MAME unterstützt, aber ZiNc kann sie häufig schneller und mit verbesserter Grafik und Sound ausführen. Die letzte Version von ZiNc von den ursprünglichen Autoren namens 'Duddie' (Marcin Dudar; auch bekannt als TheD / The Author) und 'Tratax' (DynaChicken) war v0.9; danach gingen sie dazu über, GCEmu (einen Nintendo GameCube-Emulator) zu erstellen und R.Belmont / SMF übernahm die Entwicklung von ZiNc. Der Quellcode ist verloren gegangen und wird daher nie mehr aktualisiert werden.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
		<text lang="es">ZiNc es un emulador Windows de línea de comandos para hardware arcade basado en hardware Sony PlayStation. Estos sistemas de hardware incluyen Sony ZiNc (ZN1 y ZN2) y Namco System 11. Estos juegos tambie'n son compatibles con MAME, pero con frecuencia ZiNc puede ejecutarlos más rápido y con mejoras gráficas y de sonido. La última versión de ZiNc de los autores originales llamados 'Duddie' (Marcin Dudar; alias TheD / El Autor) y 'Tratax' (DynaChicken) fue la v0.9; despue's de eso, pasaron a crear GCEmu (un emulador de Nintendo GameCube) y R.Belmont / SMF se hizo cargo del desarrollo de ZiNc. El código fuente se perdió y, por lo tanto, nunca recibirá más actualizaciones<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




