<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>

	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <pos>0.95 0.8</pos>
         <origin>1 0</origin>
         <size>0.90 0.1</size>
         <backgroundColor>00000000</backgroundColor>
         <color>F5F5F5</color>
         <fontPath>${themePath}/_inc/fonts/SF Slapstick Comic Bold.ttf</fontPath>
         <fontSize>0.055</fontSize>
         <text>The CP System III (CPシステムIII, shīpī shisutemu surī) or CPS-3 is an arcade system board that was first used by Capcom in 1996 with the arcade game Red Earth. It was the second successor to the CP System arcade hardware, following the CP System II. It would be the last proprietary system board Capcom would produce before moving on to the Dreamcast-based Naomi platform.</text>
			<text lang="es">El CP System III (CPシステムIII, shīpī shisutemu surī) o CPS-3 es una placa de sistema arcade que fue utilizada por primera vez por Capcom en 1996 con el juego arcade Red Earth. Fue la segunda sucesora del hardware arcade CP System, tras la CP System II. Sería la última placa de sistema propietaria que Capcom produciría antes de pasar a la plataforma Naomi basada en Dreamcast.</text>
			<text lang="de">Das CP System III (CPシステムIII, shīpī shisutemu surī) oder CPS-3 ist ein Arcade-System-Board, das erstmals 1996 von Capcom mit dem Arcade-Spiel Red Earth verwendet wurde. Es war der zweite Nachfolger der CP System Arcade-Hardware, nach dem CP System II. Es war die letzte proprietäre Systemplatine, die Capcom produzierte, bevor sie auf die Dreamcast-basierte Naomi-Plattform umstieg.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le CP System III (CPシステムIII, shīpī shisutemu surī) ou CPS-3 est une carte de système d'arcade qui a été utilisée pour la première fois par Capcom en 1996 avec le jeu d'arcade Red Earth. Il s'agit du deuxième successeur du système d'arcade CP System, après le CP System II. Il s'agit de la dernière carte système propriétaire que Capcom produira avant de passer à la plateforme Naomi basée sur la Dreamcast.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il CP System III (CPシステムIII, shīpī shisutemu surī) o CPS-3 è una scheda di sistema arcade utilizzata per la prima volta da Capcom nel 1996 con il gioco arcade Red Earth. È stato il secondo successore dell'hardware arcade CP System, dopo il CP System II. Sarebbe stata l'ultima scheda di sistema proprietaria che Capcom avrebbe prodotto prima di passare alla piattaforma Naomi basata su Dreamcast.</text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>
				<multiLine>false</multiLine>
				<autoScrollDelay>3000</autoScrollDelay>
				<singleLineScroll>true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>

</theme>