<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>

	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <pos>0.95 0.8</pos>
         <origin>1 0</origin>
         <size>0.90 0.1</size>
         <backgroundColor>00000000</backgroundColor>
         <color>F5F5F5</color>
         <fontPath>${themePath}/_inc/fonts/SF Slapstick Comic Bold.ttf</fontPath>
         <fontSize>0.055</fontSize>
         <text>SDLPoP stands for "Prince of Persia" linked to SDL. It is an open-source port of Prince of Persia that runs natively on Windows and Linux.
SDLPoP is based on a disassembly of the DOS version, and uses SDL, extending the game with new features.</text>
			<text lang="es">SDLPoP son las siglas de "Prince of Persia" vinculado a SDL. Se trata de un port de código abierto de Prince of Persia que se ejecuta de forma nativa en Windows y Linux.
SDLPoP se basa en un desensamblaje de la versión DOS y utiliza SDL, ampliando el juego con nuevas características.</text>
			<text lang="de">SDLPoP steht für "Prince of Persia" in Verbindung mit SDL. Es handelt sich um eine Open-Source-Portierung von Prince of Persia, die nativ auf Windows und Linux läuft.
SDLPoP basiert auf einer Disassemblierung der DOS-Version und nutzt SDL, um das Spiel mit neuen Funktionen zu erweitern.</text>
			<text lang="fr">SDLPoP signifie "Prince of Persia" lié à SDL. Il s'agit d'un portage open-source de Prince of Persia qui fonctionne nativement sous Windows et Linux.
SDLPoP est basé sur un désassemblage de la version DOS, et utilise SDL, étendant le jeu avec de nouvelles fonctionnalités.</text>
			<text lang="it">SDLPoP sta per "Prince of Persia" collegato a SDL. È un port open-source di Prince of Persia che gira in modo nativo su Windows e Linux.
SDLPoP si basa su un disassemblaggio della versione DOS e utilizza SDL, estendendo il gioco con nuove funzionalità.</text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>
				<multiLine>false</multiLine>
				<autoScrollDelay>3000</autoScrollDelay>
				<singleLineScroll>true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>

</theme>