<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>The Hitachi MB 6890, also known as the BASIC Master Level 3, emerged as a groundbreaking personal computer from Japan during the early 1980s. Notably, it was the first system to display Japanese characters, a significant achievement at the time. Operating on an 8-bit platform, it utilized Extended BASIC, which greatly improved performance and user-friendliness. The machine featured a color display, and optional peripherals included a printer and a mini floppy drive. Beyond individual use, it found applications in education, office work, data search, and simulation. Overall, the Hitachi MB 6890, completed in 1980, played a pivotal role in driving the adoption of personal computers in the business-oriented market.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">L'Hitachi MB 6890, noto anche come BASIC Master Level 3, e' stato un personal computer innovativo proveniente dal Giappone all'inizio degli anni '80. In particolare, e' stato il primo sistema a visualizzare i caratteri giapponesi, un risultato significativo per l'epoca. In particolare, fu il primo sistema a visualizzare i caratteri giapponesi, un risultato significativo per l'epoca. Funzionante su una piattaforma a 8 bit, utilizzava il BASIC esteso, che migliorava notevolmente le prestazioni e la facilita' d'uso. La macchina era dotata di un display a colori e le periferiche opzionali includevano una stampante e un mini drive floppy. Al di la' dell'uso individuale, ha trovato applicazione nell'istruzione, nel lavoro d'ufficio, nella ricerca di dati e nella simulazione. Nel complesso, l'MB 6890 di Hitachi, completato nel 1980, ha svolto un ruolo fondamentale nell'adozione dei personal computer nel mercato business-oriented.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Hitachi MB 6890, e'galement connu sous le nom de BASIC Master Level 3, est un ordinateur personnel japonais re'volutionnaire apparu au de'but des anne'es 1980. Il a notamment e'te' le premier syste'me a' afficher des caracte'res japonais, ce qui constituait une avance'e conside'rable a' l'e'poque. Fonctionnant sur une plate-forme 8 bits, il utilisait Extended BASIC, qui ame'liorait conside'rablement les performances et la convivialite'. La machine e'tait dote'e d'un e'cran couleur et les pe'riphe'riques optionnels comprenaient une imprimante et un mini lecteur de disquettes. Au-dela' de l'utilisation individuelle, il a trouve' des applications dans l'e'ducation, la bureautique, la recherche de donne'es et la simulation. Dans l'ensemble, l'Hitachi MB 6890, acheve' en 1980, a joue' un rôle essentiel dans l'adoption des ordinateurs personnels sur le marche' des entreprises.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Der Hitachi MB 6890, auch bekannt als BASIC Master Level 3, war in den frühen 1980er Jahren ein bahnbrechender Personal Computer aus Japan. Er war das erste System, das japanische Schriftzeichen anzeigen konnte, was zu dieser Zeit eine bedeutende Leistung war. Er lief auf einer 8-Bit-Plattform und nutzte Extended BASIC, das die Leistung und Benutzerfreundlichkeit erheblich verbesserte. Das Gerät verfügte über ein Farbdisplay, und zu den optionalen Peripheriegeräten gehörten ein Drucker und ein Mini-Diskettenlaufwerk. Über den individuellen Gebrauch hinaus fand er Anwendungen in den Bereichen Bildung, Büroarbeit, Datensuche und Simulation. Insgesamt spielte der 1980 fertig gestellte Hitachi MB 6890 eine entscheidende Rolle bei der Einführung von Personal Computern auf dem geschäftsorientierten Markt.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">El Hitachi MB 6890, tambie'n conocido como BASIC Master Level 3, surgió como un innovador ordenador personal de Japón a principios de la de'cada de 1980. En particular, fue el primer sistema que mostraba caracteres japoneses, todo un logro para la e'poca. Funcionaba en una plataforma de 8 bits y utilizaba el BASIC ampliado, que mejoraba enormemente el rendimiento y la facilidad de uso. La máquina contaba con una pantalla en color y, como perife'ricos opcionales, incluía una impresora y una minidisquetera. Más allá del uso individual, encontró aplicaciones en educación, trabajo de oficina, búsqueda de datos y simulación. En conjunto, el Hitachi MB 6890, terminado en 1980, desempeñó un papel fundamental en el impulso de la adopción de los ordenadores personales en el mercado orientado a las empresas.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




