<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>The TI-99/4 is a home computer released in late 1979 by Texas Instruments. Based on the Texas Instruments TMS9900 microprocessor originally used in minicomputers, it was the first 16-bit home computer. The associated video display controller provides color graphics and among the best sprite support of its era. It includes a simplified internal design, a full-travel keyboard, improved graphics, and a unique expansion system. At half the price of the original model, sales picked up significantly. TI supported the 4A with peripherals, including a speech synthesizer and a "Peripheral Expansion System" box to contain hardware add-ons. TI released developer information and tools, but the insistence on remaining sole publisher continued to starve the platform of software.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">La TI-99/4 es una computadora dome'stica lanzada a finales de 1979 por Texas Instruments. Basada en el microprocesador Texas Instruments TMS9900, originalmente utilizado en minicomputadoras, fue la primera computadora dome'stica de 16 bits. El controlador de pantalla de video asociado proporciona gráficos en color y una de las mejores compatibilidades con sprites de su e'poca. Incluye un diseño interno simplificado, un teclado de recorrido completo, gráficos mejorados y un sistema de expansión único. A mitad de precio que el modelo original, las ventas aumentaron significativamente. TI apoyó la 4A con perife'ricos, incluyendo un sintetizador de voz y una caja de "Sistema de Expansión de Perife'ricos" para alojar complementos de hardware. TI publicó información y herramientas para desarrolladores, pero la insistencia en seguir siendo el único editor continuó privando a la plataforma de software.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Der TI-99/4 ist ein Heimcomputer, der Ende 1979 von Texas Instruments auf den Markt gebracht wurde. Basierend auf dem Texas Instruments TMS9900 Mikroprozessor, der ursprünglich in Minicomputern verwendet wurde, war er der erste 16-Bit-Heimcomputer. Der zugehörige Video-Display-Controller bietet Farbgrafiken und eine der besten Sprite-Unterstützungen seiner Zeit. Er verfügt über ein vereinfachtes internes Design, eine Vollhubtastatur, verbesserte Grafiken und ein einzigartiges Erweiterungssystem. Zum halben Preis des ursprünglichen Modells zogen die Verkaufszahlen deutlich an. TI unterstützte den 4A mit Peripheriegeräten, einschließlich eines Sprachsynthesizers und einer "Peripheral Expansion System"-Box, die Hardware-Erweiterungen enthielt. TI gab Informationen und Tools für Entwickler heraus, aber das Beharren darauf, alleiniger Herausgeber zu bleiben, ließ die Plattform weiterhin in Bezug auf Software verarmen.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Le TI-99/4 est un ordinateur domestique commercialise' a' la fin de l'anne'e 1979 par Texas Instruments. Base' sur le microprocesseur Texas Instruments TMS9900 utilise' a' l'origine dans les mini-ordinateurs, il s'agit du premier ordinateur domestique 16 bits. Le contrôleur d'affichage vide'o associe' fournit des graphiques en couleur et l'un des meilleurs supports de sprites de l'e'poque. Il comprend une conception interne simplifie'e, un clavier a' course comple'te, des graphiques ame'liore's et un syste'me d'extension unique. a' la moitie' du prix du mode'le original, les ventes ont augmente' de manie're significative. TI a soutenu le 4A avec des pe'riphe'riques, y compris un synthe'tiseur vocal et une boîte "Peripheral Expansion System" pour contenir des comple'ments mate'riels. TI a publie' des informations et des outils pour les de'veloppeurs, mais l'insistance a' rester le seul e'diteur a continue' a' priver la plate-forme de logiciels.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Il TI-99/4 e' un home computer rilasciato alla fine del 1979 da Texas Instruments. Basato sul microprocessore Texas Instruments TMS9900, originariamente utilizzato nei minicomputer, e' stato il primo home computer a 16 bit. Il controller video associato fornisce grafica a colori e uno dei migliori supporti per gli sprite dell'epoca. Include un design interno semplificato, una tastiera a corsa completa, una grafica migliorata e un sistema di espansione unico. Con un prezzo dimezzato rispetto al modello originale, le vendite aumentarono notevolmente. TI supporto' il 4A con periferiche, tra cui un sintetizzatore vocale e un box "Peripheral Expansion System" per contenere componenti hardware aggiuntivi. TI rilascio' informazioni e strumenti per gli sviluppatori, ma l'insistenza nel voler rimanere l'unico editore continuo' a privare la piattaforma di software.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




