<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>

	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <pos>0.95 0.8</pos>
         <origin>1 0</origin>
         <size>0.90 0.1</size>
         <backgroundColor>00000000</backgroundColor>
         <color>F5F5F5</color>
         <fontPath>${themePath}/_inc/fonts/SF Slapstick Comic Bold.ttf</fontPath>
         <fontSize>0.055</fontSize>
         <text>The TurboGrafx-16, known as the PC Engine in Japan and France, is a 16-bit fourth-generation home video game console designed by Hudson Soft and sold by NEC Home Electronics. It was released in Japan in 1987 and in North America in 1989. The Japanese model was imported and distributed in France in 1989, and the United Kingdom and Spain received a version based on the American model known as simply TurboGrafx. It was the first console released in the 16-bit era, although it used a modified 8-bit CPU. In Japan, the system was launched as a competitor to the Famicom, but the delayed United States release meant that it ended up competing with the Sega Genesis and later the Super Nintendo Entertainment System. The TurboGrafx-16 has an 8-bit CPU, a 16-bit video color encoder, and a 16-bit video display controller. The GPUs are capable of displaying 482 colors simultaneously, out of 512. With dimensions of just 14 cm × 14 cm × 3.8 cm (5.5 in × 5.5 in × 1.5 in), the Japanese PC Engine is the smallest major home game console ever made. Games were released on HuCard cartridges and later the CD-ROM optical format with the TurboGrafx-CD add-on.</text>
			<text lang="es">La TurboGrafx-16, conocida como PC Engine en Japón y Francia, es una videoconsola doméstica de 16 bits de cuarta generación diseñada por Hudson Soft y comercializada por NEC Home Electronics. Salió a la venta en Japón en 1987 y en Norteamérica en 1989. El modelo japonés se importó y distribuyó en Francia en 1989, y el Reino Unido y España recibieron una versión basada en el modelo americano conocida simplemente como TurboGrafx. Fue la primera consola lanzada en la era de los 16 bits, aunque utilizaba una CPU modificada de 8 bits. En Japón, la consola se lanzó como competidora de la Famicom, pero el retraso en su lanzamiento en Estados Unidos hizo que acabara compitiendo con la Sega Genesis y, más tarde, con la Super Nintendo Entertainment System. El TurboGrafx-16 tiene una CPU de 8 bits, un codificador de color de vídeo de 16 bits y un controlador de pantalla de vídeo de 16 bits. La GPU es capaz de mostrar 482 colores simultáneamente, de un total de 512. Con unas dimensiones de sólo 14 cm × 14 cm × 3,8 cm (5,5 in × 5,5 in × 1,5 in), la PC Engine japonesa es la videoconsola doméstica más pequeña jamás fabricada. Los juegos se lanzaron en cartuchos HuCard y, más tarde, en formato óptico CD-ROM con el complemento TurboGrafx-CD.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der TurboGrafx-16, in Japan und Frankreich als PC Engine bekannt, ist eine 16-Bit-Heimvideospielkonsole der vierten Generation, die von Hudson Soft entwickelt und von NEC Home Electronics verkauft wurde. Sie wurde 1987 in Japan und 1989 in Nordamerika veröffentlicht. Das japanische Modell wurde 1989 nach Frankreich importiert und dort vertrieben, und das Vereinigte Königreich und Spanien erhielten eine Version, die auf dem amerikanischen Modell basierte und einfach TurboGrafx genannt wurde. Es war die erste Konsole, die in der 16-Bit-Ära veröffentlicht wurde, obwohl sie eine modifizierte 8-Bit-CPU verwendete. In Japan wurde das System als Konkurrent des Famicom auf den Markt gebracht, aber die verzögerte Veröffentlichung in den USA bedeutete, dass es schließlich mit dem Sega Genesis und später dem Super Nintendo Entertainment System konkurrierte. Der TurboGrafx-16 hat eine 8-Bit-CPU, einen 16-Bit-Videofarbcodierer und einen 16-Bit-Videobildschirm-Controller. Die Grafikprozessoren sind in der Lage, 482 von 512 Farben gleichzeitig darzustellen. Mit Abmessungen von nur 14 cm × 14 cm × 3,8 cm ist die japanische PC-Engine die kleinste große Heimspielkonsole, die je hergestellt wurde. Die Spiele wurden auf HuCard-Kassetten und später im optischen CD-ROM-Format mit dem TurboGrafx-CD-Add-on veröffentlicht.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La TurboGrafx-16, connue sous le nom de PC Engine au Japon et en France, est une console de jeux vidéo 16 bits de quatrième génération conçue par Hudson Soft et vendue par NEC Home Electronics. Elle est sortie au Japon en 1987 et en Amérique du Nord en 1989. Le modèle japonais a été importé et distribué en France en 1989, et le Royaume-Uni et l'Espagne ont reçu une version basée sur le modèle américain, connue sous le nom de TurboGrafx. Il s'agit de la première console de l'ère 16 bits, bien qu'elle utilise un processeur 8 bits modifié. Au Japon, la console a été lancée pour concurrencer la Famicom, mais sa sortie retardée aux États-Unis l'a mise en concurrence avec la Sega Genesis et, plus tard, avec la Super Nintendo Entertainment System. Le TurboGrafx-16 possède un processeur 8 bits, un encodeur de couleurs vidéo 16 bits et un contrôleur d'affichage vidéo 16 bits. Les GPU sont capables d'afficher 482 couleurs simultanément, sur 512. Avec des dimensions de seulement 14 cm × 14 cm × 3,8 cm (5,5 in × 5,5 in × 1,5 in), la PC Engine japonaise est la plus petite console de jeu de salon jamais fabriquée. Les jeux ont été publiés sur des cartouches HuCard et, plus tard, au format optique CD-ROM avec l'extension TurboGrafx-CD.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il TurboGrafx-16, noto come PC Engine in Giappone e Francia, è una console per videogiochi domestici di quarta generazione a 16 bit progettata da Hudson Soft e venduta da NEC Home Electronics. È stata rilasciata in Giappone nel 1987 e in Nord America nel 1989. Il modello giapponese è stato importato e distribuito in Francia nel 1989, mentre il Regno Unito e la Spagna hanno ricevuto una versione basata sul modello americano, nota semplicemente come TurboGrafx. Fu la prima console rilasciata nell'era dei 16 bit, sebbene utilizzasse una CPU modificata a 8 bit. In Giappone, la console fu lanciata come concorrente del Famicom, ma il ritardo nell'uscita negli Stati Uniti fece sì che finisse per competere con il Sega Genesis e successivamente con il Super Nintendo Entertainment System. l TurboGrafx-16 è dotato di una CPU a 8 bit, un codificatore video a 16 bit e un controller video a 16 bit. Le GPU sono in grado di visualizzare 482 colori simultaneamente, su 512. Con dimensioni di soli 14 cm × 14 cm × 3,8 cm (5,5 in × 5,5 in × 1,5 in), il PC Engine giapponese è la più piccola console per videogiochi mai realizzata. I giochi sono stati rilasciati su cartucce HuCard e successivamente sul formato ottico CD-ROM con il componente aggiuntivo TurboGrafx-CD.</text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>
				<multiLine>false</multiLine>
				<autoScrollDelay>3000</autoScrollDelay>
				<singleLineScroll>true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>

</theme>