<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>

	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <pos>0.95 0.8</pos>
         <origin>1 0</origin>
         <size>0.90 0.1</size>
         <backgroundColor>00000000</backgroundColor>
         <color>F5F5F5</color>
         <fontPath>${themePath}/_inc/fonts/SF Slapstick Comic Bold.ttf</fontPath>
         <fontSize>0.055</fontSize>
         <text>A source port of Majora's Mask. 2Ship2Harkinian (aka SoH2) features extensive and significant enhancements over the original game, such as improved performance, increased frame-rate, native ultra-widescreen support, and extensive mod support (especially compared to emulated versions of the original), among other features.</text>
			<text lang="it">Un porting sorgente di Majora's Mask. 2Ship2Harkinian (noto anche come SoH2) presenta miglioramenti significativi ed estesi rispetto al gioco originale, come prestazioni migliorate, frame rate aumentato, supporto nativo ultra-widescreen e ampio supporto mod (soprattutto rispetto alle versioni emulate dell'originale), tra le altre caratteristiche.</text>
			<text lang="de">Ein Source-Port von Majora's Mask. 2Ship2Harkinian (auch bekannt als SoH2) bietet umfangreiche und bedeutende Verbesserungen gegenüber dem Originalspiel, wie z. B. eine verbesserte Performance, eine höhere Bildrate, native Unterstützung für Ultra-Breitbildformate und umfangreiche Mod-Unterstützung (insbesondere im Vergleich zu emulierten Versionen des Originals), neben anderen Funktionen.</text> 
			<text lang="fr">2Ship2Harkinian (alias SoH2) est un portage du jeu Majora's Mask. Il propose des améliorations importantes par rapport au jeu original, notamment des performances optimisées, une fréquence d'images plus élevée, une compatibilité native avec les écrans ultra-larges et une prise en charge étendue des mods (surtout comparée aux versions émulées).</text>
			<text lang="es">Un puerto fuente de Majora's Mask. 2Ship2Harkinian (también conocido como SoH2) presenta mejoras extensas y significativas con respecto al juego original, como un rendimiento mejorado, una mayor velocidad de cuadros, compatibilidad nativa con pantalla ultra ancha y una amplia compatibilidad con mods (especialmente en comparación con las versiones emuladas del original), entre otras características.</text>         
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>
				<multiLine>false</multiLine>
				<autoScrollDelay>3000</autoScrollDelay>
				<singleLineScroll>true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>

</theme>