<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>The Commodore VIC-20 (known as the VC-20 in Germany and the VIC-1001 in Japan) is an 8-bit home computer that was sold by Commodore Business Machines. The VIC-20 was announced in 1980, roughly three years after Commodore's first personal computer, the PET. The VIC-20 was the first computer of any description to sell one million units. It was described as "one of the first anti-spectatorial, non-esoteric computers by design...no longer relegated to hobbyist/enthusiasts or those with money, the computer Commodore developed was the computer of the future. The VIC-20 was called VC-20 in Germany because the pronunciation of VIC with a German accent sounds like the German expletives "fick" or "wichsen". The term VC was marketed as though it was an abbreviation of VolksComputer ("people's computer," similar to Volkswagen and Volksempfänger).<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">El Commodore VIC-20 (conocido como VC-20 en Alemania y VIC-1001 en Japón) es un ordenador dome'stico de 8 bits comercializado por Commodore Business Machines. El VIC-20 fue anunciado en 1980, aproximadamente tres años despue's del primer ordenador personal de Commodore, el PET. El VIC-20 fue el primer ordenador de cualquier tipo en vender un millón de unidades. Fue descrito como "uno de los primeros ordenadores antiespectadores, no esote'ricos por diseño... ya no relegado a los aficionados/entusiastas o a los que tienen dinero, el ordenador desarrollado por Commodore era el ordenador del futuro". El VIC-20 se llamó VC-20 en Alemania porque la pronunciación de VIC con acento alemán suena como los improperios alemanes "fick" o "wichsen". El te'rmino VC se comercializó como si fuera una abreviatura de VolksComputer ("ordenador del pueblo", similar a Volkswagen y Volksempfänger).<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Der Commodore VIC-20 (in Deutschland als VC-20 und in Japan als VIC-1001 bekannt) ist ein 8-Bit-Heimcomputer, der von Commodore Business Machines verkauft wurde. Der VIC-20 wurde 1980 angekündigt, etwa drei Jahre nach dem ersten Personal Computer von Commodore, dem PET. Der VIC-20 war der erste Computer, von dem eine Million Stück verkauft wurden. Er wurde als "einer der ersten antispektakulären, nicht-esoterischen Computer beschrieben... der von Commodore entwickelte Computer war der Computer der Zukunft und nicht mehr nur etwas für Hobbyisten/Enthusiasten oder Leute mit Geld. Der VIC-20 wurde in Deutschland VC-20 genannt, weil die Aussprache von VIC mit deutschem Akzent wie die deutschen Schimpfwörter "fick" oder "wichsen" klingt. Der Begriff VC wurde so vermarktet, als sei er eine Abkürzung für VolksComputer (ähnlich wie Volkswagen und Volksempfänger).<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Commodore VIC-20 (connu sous le nom de VC-20 en Allemagne et de VIC-1001 au Japon) est un ordinateur domestique 8 bits vendu par Commodore Business Machines. Le VIC-20 a e'te' annonce' en 1980, environ trois ans apre's le premier ordinateur personnel de Commodore, le PET. Le VIC-20 a e'te' le premier ordinateur, toutes cate'gories confondues, a' se vendre a' un million d'exemplaires. Il a e'te' de'crit comme "l'un des premiers ordinateurs anti-spectateurs, non e'sote'riques de par sa conception... n'e'tant plus rele'gue' aux amateurs/enthousiastes ou a' ceux qui ont de l'argent, l'ordinateur de'veloppe' par Commodore e'tait l'ordinateur de l'avenir". Le VIC-20 e'tait appele' VC-20 en Allemagne parce que la prononciation de VIC avec un accent allemand ressemble aux jurons allemands "fick" ou "wichsen". Le terme VC a e'te' commercialise' comme s'il s'agissait d'une abre'viation de VolksComputer ("ordinateur du peuple", similaire a' Volkswagen et Volksempfänger).<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Il Commodore VIC-20 (noto come VC-20 in Germania e VIC-1001 in Giappone) e' stato un home computer a 8 bit venduto da Commodore Business Machines. Il VIC-20 fu annunciato nel 1980, circa tre anni dopo il primo personal computer di Commodore, il PET. Il VIC-20 e' stato il primo computer di qualsiasi tipo a vendere un milione di unita'. e' stato descritto come "uno dei primi computer anti-speculatori, non esoterici per concezione... non piU' relegato agli hobbisti/entusiasti o a chi ha soldi, il computer sviluppato da Commodore era il computer del futuro". Il VIC-20 era chiamato VC-20 in Germania perche' la pronuncia di VIC con accento tedesco assomiglia alle imprecazioni tedesche "fick" o "wichsen". Il termine VC fu commercializzato come se fosse un'abbreviazione di VolksComputer ("computer del popolo", simile a Volkswagen e Volksempfänger).<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




