<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>Here is a collection of all the games created by Exidy and featured on this machine.                                                                   Exidy was an American arcade manufacturer, one of the most important in the early days of video games. During its existence, from 1974 to 1996, it created over 50 games, including Chiller, Mouse Trap, Crossbow, Targ, Circus, Venture, Death Race, Fire One, and Star Fire.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Ecco una raccolta di tutti i giochi creati dalla Exidy e presenti su questa macchina.                                                                   Exidy e' stata un'azienda produttrice di arcade statunitense, una delle piU' importanti del primo periodo dei videogiochi. Durante la sua attivita', dal 1974 al 1996, ha realizzato piU' di 50 giochi, tra cui Chiller, Mouse Trap, Crossbow, Targ, Circus, Venture, Death Race, Fire One e Star Fire.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Voici une collection de tous les jeux cre'e's par Exidy et disponibles sur cette machine.                                                                   Exidy e'tait un fabricant ame'ricain de bornes d'arcade, l'un des plus importants des de'buts du jeu vide'o. De 1974 a' 1996, il a cre'e' plus de 50 jeux, dont Chiller, Mouse Trap, Crossbow, Targ, Circus, Venture, Death Race, Fire One et Star Fire.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Hier ist eine Sammlung aller von Exidy entwickelten und auf dieser Maschine enthaltenen Spiele.                                                                   Exidy war ein US-amerikanischer Hersteller von Arcade-Automaten und einer der wichtigsten in den Anfängen der Videospiele. Während seines Bestehens von 1974 bis 1996 entwickelte das Unternehmen über 50 Spiele, darunter Chiller, Mouse Trap, Crossbow, Targ, Circus, Venture, Death Race, Fire One und Star Fire.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">Aquí tene'is una recopilación de todos los juegos creados por Exidy e incluidos en esta máquina.                                                                   Exidy fue un fabricante estadounidense de máquinas recreativas, uno de los más importantes en los inicios de los videojuegos. Durante su existencia, desde 1974 hasta 1996, creó más de 50 juegos, entre ellos Chiller, Mouse Trap, Crossbow, Targ, Circus, Venture, Death Race, Fire One y Star Fire.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>





