<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>In the late 1980s, Nintendo’s Game &amp; Watch handheld devices had already established themselves as popular portable gaming gadgets. Konami, known for its arcade hits and console games, recognized the potential of the handheld market. To challenge Nintendo’s dominance, Konami decided to create its own line of handheld LCD games. They wanted to reach a broader audience beyond arcades and consoles. Their LCD games featured licensed characters, sports themes, and unique scenarios. Titles like “Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles” and “Top Gun” showcased their commitment to quality. While they didn’t surpass Nintendo’s Game &amp; Watch in sales, Konami’s handheld LCD games left a lasting impact. They added diversity and excitement to the portable gaming landscape, contributing to the overall growth of handheld gaming.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Alla fine degli anni '80, i dispositivi portatili Game &amp; Watch di Nintendo si erano gia' affermati come popolari gadget di gioco portatili. Konami, nota per i suoi successi arcade e per i giochi per console, riconobbe il potenziale del mercato delle console portatili. Per sfidare il dominio di Nintendo, Konami decise di creare una propria linea di giochi LCD portatili. Voleva raggiungere un pubblico piU' ampio al di la' delle sale giochi e delle console. I loro giochi LCD presentavano personaggi su licenza, temi sportivi e scenari unici. Titoli come "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles" e "Top Gun" dimostrano il loro impegno per la qualita'. Pur non avendo superato il Game &amp; Watch di Nintendo in termini di vendite, i giochi LCD portatili di Konami hanno lasciato un impatto duraturo. Hanno aggiunto diversita' ed eccitazione al panorama dei giochi portatili, contribuendo alla crescita complessiva dei giochi portatili.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">a' la fin des anne'es 1980, les appareils portables Game &amp; Watch de Nintendo s'e'taient de'ja' impose's comme des gadgets de jeu portables tre's populaires. Konami, connu pour ses jeux d'arcade et ses jeux de console, a reconnu le potentiel du marche' des appareils portables. Pour contester la domination de Nintendo, Konami a de'cide' de cre'er sa propre ligne de jeux LCD portables. La socie'te' souhaitait toucher un public plus large que celui des salles d'arcade et des consoles. Leurs jeux LCD pre'sentaient des personnages sous licence, des the'mes sportifs et des sce'narios uniques. Des titres comme "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles" et "Top Gun" te'moignent de leur engagement en faveur de la qualite'. Bien qu'ils n'aient pas de'passe' le Game &amp; Watch de Nintendo en termes de ventes, les jeux LCD portables de Konami ont laisse' un impact durable. Ils ont ajoute' de la diversite' et de l'enthousiasme au paysage des jeux portables, contribuant ainsi a' la croissance globale de ce type de jeux.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">In den späten 1980er Jahren hatten sich Nintendos Game &amp; Watch-Handhelds bereits als beliebte tragbare Spielgeräte etabliert. Konami, bekannt für seine Arcade-Hits und Konsolenspiele, erkannte das Potenzial des Handheld-Marktes. Um Nintendos Dominanz herauszufordern, beschloss Konami, eine eigene Reihe von LCD-Handheld-Spielen zu entwickeln. Das Unternehmen wollte ein breiteres Publikum als das der Spielhallen und Konsolen erreichen. Ihre LCD-Spiele enthielten lizenzierte Charaktere, Sportthemen und einzigartige Szenarien. Titel wie "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles" und "Top Gun" zeugten von dem hohen Qualitätsanspruch des Unternehmens. Obwohl sie die Verkaufszahlen von Nintendos Game &amp; Watch nicht übertrafen, hinterließen die LCD-Handheld-Spiele von Konami einen bleibenden Eindruck. Sie brachten Abwechslung und Spannung in die tragbare Spielelandschaft und trugen zum allgemeinen Wachstum der Handheld-Spiele bei.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">A finales de la de'cada de 1980, los dispositivos portátiles Game &amp; Watch de Nintendo ya se habían consolidado como populares aparatos de juego portátiles. Konami, conocida por sus e'xitos arcade y sus juegos de consola, reconoció el potencial del mercado de las portátiles. Para desafiar el dominio de Nintendo, Konami decidió crear su propia línea de juegos LCD portátiles. Querían llegar a un público más amplio, más allá de los salones recreativos y las consolas. Sus juegos LCD incluían personajes con licencia, temas deportivos y escenarios únicos. Títulos como "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles" y "Top Gun" demostraron su compromiso con la calidad. Aunque no superaron en ventas a Game &amp; Watch de Nintendo, los juegos LCD portátiles de Konami dejaron un impacto duradero. Aportaron diversidad y emoción al panorama de los juegos portátiles, contribuyendo al crecimiento general de este tipo de juegos.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>    
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




