<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>The Bally Astrocade (also known as Bally Arcade or initially as Bally ABA-1000) is a second-generation home video game console and simple computer system designed by a team at Midway, at that time the videogame division of Bally. It was originally announced as the "Bally Home Library Computer" in October 1977 and initially made available for mail order in December 1977. But due to production delays, the units were first released to stores in April 1978 and its branding changed to "Bally Professional Arcade". It was marketed only for a limited time before Bally decided to exit the market. The rights were later picked up by a third-party company, who re-released it and sold it until around 1984. The Astrocade is particularly notable for its very powerful graphics capabilities for the time of release and for the difficulty in accessing those capabilities.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">La Bally Astrocade (tambie'n conocida como Bally Arcade o inicialmente como Bally ABA-1000) es una videoconsola dome'stica de segunda generación y un sencillo sistema informático diseñado por un equipo de Midway, en aquel momento la división de videojuegos de Bally. Se anunció originalmente como "Bally Home Library Computer" en octubre de 1977 y se puso inicialmente a la venta por correo en diciembre de 1977. Pero debido a retrasos en la producción, las unidades se pusieron a la venta por primera vez en las tiendas en abril de 1978 y su marca cambió a "Bally Professional Arcade". Sólo se comercializó durante un tiempo limitado antes de que Bally decidiera abandonar el mercado. Posteriormente, los derechos fueron adquiridos por una tercera empresa, que volvió a comercializarla y venderla hasta 1984 aproximadamente. El Astrocade destaca especialmente por sus capacidades gráficas muy potentes para la e'poca de su lanzamiento y por la dificultad para acceder a esas capacidades.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Der Bally Astrocade (auch bekannt als Bally Arcade oder ursprünglich als Bally ABA-1000) ist eine Videospielkonsole der zweiten Generation für den Heimgebrauch und ein einfaches Computersystem, das von einem Team bei Midway, der damaligen Videospielabteilung von Bally, entwickelt wurde. Ursprünglich wurde es im Oktober 1977 als "Bally Home Library Computer" angekündigt und war ab Dezember 1977 im Versandhandel erhältlich. Aufgrund von Produktionsverzögerungen wurden die Geräte jedoch erst im April 1978 in die Läden gebracht und der Markenname in "Bally Professional Arcade" geändert. Das Gerät wurde nur für eine begrenzte Zeit vermarktet, bevor Bally beschloss, sich aus dem Markt zurückzuziehen. Die Rechte wurden später von einer Drittfirma übernommen, die das Gerät wieder auf den Markt brachte und bis etwa 1984 verkaufte. Das Astrocade zeichnet sich besonders durch seine für die damalige Zeit sehr leistungsfähigen Grafikfunktionen und die Schwierigkeit aus, auf diese Funktionen zuzugreifen.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">L'Astrocade de Bally (e'galement connu sous le nom de Bally Arcade ou initialement sous le nom de Bally ABA-1000) est une console de jeux vide'o domestique de deuxie'me ge'ne'ration et un syste'me informatique simple conçu par une e'quipe de Midway, a' l'e'poque la division jeux vide'o de Bally. Elle a e'te' initialement annonce'e sous le nom de "Bally Home Library Computer" en octobre 1977 et mise en vente par correspondance en de'cembre 1977. Mais en raison de retards de production, les unite's ont e'te' commercialise'es pour la premie're fois en avril 1978 et leur marque a e'te' modifie'e pour devenir "Bally Professional Arcade". Il n'a e'te' commercialise' que pendant une pe'riode limite'e avant que Bally ne de'cide de se retirer du marche'. Les droits ont ensuite e'te' repris par une socie'te' tierce, qui l'a re'e'dite' et vendu jusqu'en 1984 environ. L'Astrocade est particulie'rement remarquable pour ses capacite's graphiques tre's puissantes pour l'e'poque de sa sortie et pour la difficulte' d'acce's a' ces capacite's.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Il Bally Astrocade (noto anche come Bally Arcade o inizialmente come Bally ABA-1000) e' una console per videogiochi domestici di seconda generazione e un semplice sistema informatico progettato da un team di Midway, all'epoca la divisione videogiochi di Bally. Fu annunciata originariamente come "Bally Home Library Computer" nell'ottobre 1977 e resa disponibile per la vendita per corrispondenza nel dicembre 1977. Ma a causa di ritardi nella produzione, le unita' furono distribuite per la prima volta nei negozi nell'aprile del 1978 e il marchio fu cambiato in "Bally Professional Arcade". Fu commercializzato solo per un periodo limitato prima che Bally decidesse di uscire dal mercato. I diritti vennero poi acquisiti da un'azienda terza, che lo ripubblico' e lo vendette fino al 1984 circa. L'Astrocade e' particolarmente degno di nota per le sue capacita' grafiche molto potenti per l'epoca di uscita e per la difficolta' di accesso a tali capacita'.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




