<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap-it.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>Handheld electronic games are very small, portable devices for playing interactive electronic games, often miniaturized versions of video games. The controls, display and speakers are all part of a single unit. Rather than a general-purpose screen made up of a grid of small pixels, they usually have custom displays designed to play one game. This simplicity means they can be made as small as a smartwatch, and sometimes are. The visual output of these games can range from a few small light bulbs or LED lights to calculator-like alphanumerical screens; later these were mostly displaced by liquid crystal and vacuum fluorescent display screens with detailed images and in the case of VFD games, color. Handhelds' popularity was at its peak from the late 1970s into the early 1990s before declining. They are the precursors to the handheld game console.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">Los juegos electrónicos portátiles son dispositivos muy pequeños y portátiles para jugar a juegos electrónicos interactivos, a menudo versiones miniaturizadas de videojuegos. Los mandos, la pantalla y los altavoces forman parte de una sola unidad. En lugar de una pantalla de uso general formada por una cuadrícula de pequeños píxeles, suelen tener pantallas personalizadas diseñadas para jugar a un solo juego. Esta simplicidad hace que puedan ser tan pequeños como un smartwatch, y a veces lo son. La salida visual de estos juegos puede variar desde unas pequeñas bombillas o luces LED hasta pantallas alfanume'ricas similares a las de las calculadoras; más tarde, e'stas fueron desplazadas en su mayoría por pantallas de cristal líquido y fluorescentes al vacío con imágenes detalladas y, en el caso de los juegos VFD, en color. La popularidad de los dispositivos portátiles alcanzó su punto álgido entre finales de los años 70 y principios de los 90, antes de declinar. Son los precursores de las videoconsolas portátiles.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Elektronische Handheld-Spiele sind sehr kleine, tragbare Geräte zum Spielen interaktiver elektronischer Spiele, oft miniaturisierte Versionen von Videospielen. Die Bedienelemente, das Display und die Lautsprecher sind in einem einzigen Gerät untergebracht. Anstelle eines allgemeinen Bildschirms, der aus einem Gitter aus kleinen Pixeln besteht, verfügen sie in der Regel über spezielle Displays, die für ein bestimmtes Spiel entwickelt wurden. Diese Einfachheit bedeutet, dass sie so klein wie eine Smartwatch sein können, was sie manchmal auch sind. Die visuelle Ausgabe dieser Spiele kann von einigen kleinen Glühbirnen oder LED-Leuchten bis hin zu taschenrechnerähnlichen alphanumerischen Bildschirmen reichen; später wurden diese meist durch Flüssigkristall- und Vakuumfluoreszenzbildschirme mit detaillierten Bildern und im Fall von VFD-Spielen auch Farbe ersetzt. Die Popularität von Handhelds erreichte Ende der 1970er bis Anfang der 1990er Jahre ihren Höhepunkt, bevor sie zurückging. Sie sind die Vorläufer der Handheld-Konsolen.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Les jeux e'lectroniques de poche sont de tre's petits appareils portables permettant de jouer a' des jeux e'lectroniques interactifs, souvent des versions miniaturise'es de jeux vide'o. Les commandes, l'e'cran et les haut-parleurs font partie d'une seule unite'. Plutôt qu'un e'cran polyvalent compose' d'une grille de petits pixels, ils sont ge'ne'ralement dote's d'un affichage personnalise' conçu pour jouer a' un seul jeu. Cette simplicite' signifie qu'ils peuvent être aussi petits qu'une smartwatch, et le sont parfois. La sortie visuelle de ces jeux peut aller de quelques petites ampoules ou lumie'res LED a' des e'crans alphanume'riques de type calculatrice. Plus tard, ces e'crans ont e'te' remplace's par des e'crans a' cristaux liquides et des e'crans fluorescents a' vide avec des images de'taille'es et, dans le cas des jeux VFD, en couleur. La popularite' des ordinateurs de poche a atteint son apoge'e de la fin des anne'es 1970 au de'but des anne'es 1990, avant de de'cliner. Ils sont les pre'curseurs de la console de jeu portable.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">I giochi elettronici portatili sono dispositivi molto piccoli e facilmente trasportabili per giocare a giochi elettronici interattivi, spesso versioni miniaturizzate di videogiochi. I comandi, il display e gli altoparlanti fanno parte di un'unica unita'. Invece di uno schermo generico composto da una griglia di piccoli pixel, di solito hanno display personalizzati progettati per la riproduzione di un solo gioco. Grazie a questa semplicita', possono essere realizzati con le dimensioni di uno smartwatch, e a volte lo sono. L'output visivo di questi giochi puo' variare da alcune piccole lampadine o luci LED a schermi alfanumerici simili a quelli di una calcolatrice; in seguito questi schermi sono stati sostituiti da schermi a cristalli liquidi e a fluorescenza sottovuoto con immagini dettagliate e, nel caso dei giochi VFD, a colori. La popolarita' dei giochi portatili ha raggiunto il suo apice tra la fine degli anni '70 e l'inizio degli anni '90, prima di diminuire. Sono i precursori delle console di gioco portatili.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




