<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>The Atari 2600, originally branded as the Atari Video Computer System (Atari VCS) until November 1982, is a home video game console developed and produced by Atari, Inc. Released on September 11, 1977, it is credited with popularizing the use of microprocessor-based hardware and games stored on ROM cartridges (a format first used with the Fairchild Channel F in 1976). The VCS was bundled with two joystick controllers, a conjoined pair of paddle controllers, and a game cartridge: initially Combat, and later Pac-Man.
The Atari VCS launched with nine simple, low-resolution games in 2 KiB cartridges. The system found its killer app with the home conversion of Taito's arcade game Space Invaders in 1980 and became widely successful, leading to the creation of Activision and other third-party game developers as well as competition from home console manufacturers Mattel and Coleco. By the end of its primary lifecycle in 1983–84, games for the 2600 were using more than four times the ROM of the launch titles with significantly more advanced visuals and gameplay than the system was designed for, such as Pitfall! and its scrolling sequel Pitfall II: Lost Caverns.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">La Atari 2600, originalmente conocida como Atari Video Computer System (Atari VCS) hasta noviembre de 1982, es una videoconsola dome'stica desarrollada y producida por Atari, Inc. Lanzada el 11 de septiembre de 1977, se le atribuye el me'rito de popularizar el uso de hardware basado en microprocesadores y juegos almacenados en cartuchos ROM (un formato utilizado por primera vez con el Fairchild Channel F en 1976). La VCS se suministraba con dos joysticks, un par de palas y un cartucho de juego: inicialmente Combat y más tarde Pac-Man. La Atari VCS se lanzó con nueve juegos sencillos de baja resolución en cartuchos de 2 KiB. En 1980, la conversión dome'stica de Space Invaders, el juego arcade de Taito, supuso el lanzamiento definitivo del sistema, que alcanzó un gran e'xito y dio lugar a la creación de Activision y otros desarrolladores de juegos, así como a la competencia de los fabricantes de consolas dome'sticas Mattel y Coleco. Al final de su ciclo de vida en 1983-84, los juegos para la 2600 utilizaban más del cuádruple de ROM que los títulos de lanzamiento, con gráficos y jugabilidad mucho más avanzados que para los que se había diseñado el sistema, como Pitfall! y su secuela de desplazamiento Pitfall II: Lost Caverns.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Der Atari 2600, der bis November 1982 unter dem Namen Atari Video Computer System (Atari VCS) bekannt war, ist eine Videospielkonsole für den Heimgebrauch, die von Atari, Inc. entwickelt und hergestellt wurde. Es wurde am 11. September 1977 auf den Markt gebracht und gilt als Wegbereiter für die Verwendung von mikroprozessorgesteuerter Hardware und Spielen, die auf ROM-Kassetten gespeichert sind (ein Format, das erstmals 1976 mit dem Fairchild Channel F verwendet wurde). Das VCS wurde mit zwei Joystick-Controllern, einem Paar Paddle-Controllern und einer Spielekassette ausgeliefert: zunächst Combat, später Pac-Man. Das Atari VCS kam mit neun einfachen, niedrig aufgelösten Spielen auf 2-KiB-Cartridges auf den Markt. Mit der Heimkonvertierung des Spielhallenspiels Space Invaders von Taito fand das System 1980 seinen Durchbruch und wurde zu einem großen Erfolg, der zur Gründung von Activision und anderen Spieleentwicklern sowie zur Konkurrenz durch die Heimkonsolenhersteller Mattel und Coleco führte. Am Ende des ersten Lebenszyklus in den Jahren 1983-84 benötigten die Spiele für das 2600 mehr als das Vierfache des ROMs der Starttitel mit deutlich fortschrittlicheren Grafiken und Spielabläufen, als für das System vorgesehen waren, wie z. B. Pitfall! und seine Scrolling-Fortsetzung Pitfall II: Lost Caverns.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">L'Atari 2600, initialement appele' Atari Video Computer System (Atari VCS) jusqu'en novembre 1982, est une console de jeux vide'o de salon de'veloppe'e et produite par Atari, Inc. Sortie le 11 septembre 1977, elle a popularise' l'utilisation de mate'riel a' microprocesseur et de jeux stocke's sur des cartouches ROM (un format utilise' pour la premie're fois avec la Fairchild Channel F en 1976). Le VCS e'tait livre' avec deux joysticks, une paire de palettes et une cartouche de jeu : initialement Combat, puis Pac-Man. L'Atari VCS a e'te' lance' avec neuf jeux simples, a' faible re'solution, sur des cartouches de 2 KiB. Le syste'me a trouve' son "killer app" avec la conversion domestique du jeu d'arcade Space Invaders de Taito en 1980 et a connu un grand succe's, entraînant la cre'ation d'Activision et d'autres de'veloppeurs de jeux tiers, ainsi que la concurrence des fabricants de consoles de salon Mattel et Coleco. a' la fin de son cycle de vie primaire, en 1983-1984, les jeux pour la 2600 utilisaient plus de quatre fois la me'moire morte des titres de lancement, avec des graphismes et un gameplay nettement plus avance's que ceux pour lesquels le syste'me avait e'te' conçu, comme Pitfall ! et sa suite a' de'filement Pitfall II : Lost Caverns.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">L'Atari 2600, originariamente chiamato Atari Video Computer System (Atari VCS) fino al novembre 1982, e' una console per videogiochi domestica sviluppata e prodotta da Atari, Inc. Rilasciata l'11 settembre 1977, e' accreditata per aver reso popolare l'uso di hardware basato su microprocessore e giochi memorizzati su cartucce ROM (un formato utilizzato per la prima volta con il Fairchild Channel F nel 1976). Il VCS veniva fornito con due controller joystick, una coppia di controller paddle e una cartuccia di giochi: inizialmente Combat e successivamente Pac-Man. L'Atari VCS fu lanciato con nove semplici giochi a bassa risoluzione in cartucce da 2 KiB. Il sistema trovo' la sua killer app con la conversione domestica del gioco arcade Space Invaders di Taito nel 1980 e ottenne un grande successo, portando alla creazione di Activision e di altri sviluppatori di giochi di terze parti, nonche' alla concorrenza dei produttori di console domestiche Mattel e Coleco. Alla fine del suo ciclo di vita primario, nel 1983-84, i giochi per il 2600 utilizzavano piU' di quattro volte la ROM dei titoli di lancio, con una grafica e un gameplay molto piU' avanzati di quelli per cui il sistema era stato progettato, come Pitfall! e il suo seguito a scorrimento Pitfall II: Lost Caverns.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




