<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>The Force Engine is a project with the goal to reverse engineer and rebuild the Jedi Engine for modern systems and the games that used that engine - Dark Forces and Outlaws. The project will include modern, built-in tools, such as a level editor and will make it easy to play Dark Forces and Outlaws on modern systems as well as the many community mods designed to work with the original games. Playing Dark Forces or, in the future, Outlaws using the Force Engine will add ease of use and modern features such as higher resolutions and modern control schemes such as mouse-look. Using the built-in tools, once they are available, will allow for easier modding with more modern UI, greater flexibility and the ability to use enhancements made to the Jedi Engine for Outlaws in custom Dark Forces levels - such as slopes, stacked sectors, per-sector color maps and more.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">El Motor de la Fuerza es un proyecto cuyo objetivo es realizar ingeniería inversa y reconstruir el Motor Jedi para sistemas modernos y los juegos que utilizaban ese motor: Dark Forces y Outlaws. El proyecto incluirá herramientas modernas integradas, como un editor de niveles, y facilitará el juego de Dark Forces y Outlaws en sistemas modernos, así como los numerosos mods de la comunidad diseñados para funcionar con los juegos originales. Jugar a Dark Forces o, en el futuro, a Outlaws utilizando el motor Force Engine añadirá facilidad de uso y características modernas, como resoluciones más altas y esquemas de control modernos, como la vista de ratón. El uso de las herramientas integradas, una vez que este'n disponibles, facilitará la creación de mods con una interfaz de usuario más moderna, mayor flexibilidad y la posibilidad de utilizar las mejoras realizadas en el motor Jedi para Outlaws en niveles personalizados de Dark Forces, como pendientes, sectores apilados, mapas de color por sector y mucho más.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">The Force Engine ist ein Projekt mit dem Ziel, die Jedi-Engine für moderne Systeme und die Spiele, die diese Engine verwendet haben - Dark Forces und Outlaws - nachzubauen. Das Projekt wird moderne, eingebaute Tools wie einen Level-Editor enthalten und es einfach machen, Dark Forces und Outlaws auf modernen Systemen zu spielen, ebenso wie die vielen Community-Mods, die für die Originalspiele entwickelt wurden. Das Spielen von Dark Forces oder, in Zukunft, Outlaws mit der Force Engine wird die Benutzerfreundlichkeit erhöhen und moderne Features wie höhere Auflösungen und moderne Steuerungsschemata wie Mouse-Look ermöglichen. Die Verwendung der eingebauten Tools, sobald sie verfügbar sind, wird eine einfachere Modifikation mit modernerer Benutzeroberfläche, größerer Flexibilität und der Möglichkeit, die Verbesserungen der Jedi-Engine für Outlaws in benutzerdefinierten Dark Forces-Levels zu verwenden, ermöglichen - wie z. B. Abhänge, gestapelte Sektoren, Farbkarten für jeden Sektor und mehr.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">The Force Engine est un projet dont l'objectif est de reconstruire le Jedi Engine pour les syste'mes modernes et les jeux qui utilisaient ce moteur - Dark Forces et Outlaws. Le projet inclura des outils modernes inte'gre's, tels qu'un e'diteur de niveaux, et permettra de jouer facilement a' Dark Forces et Outlaws sur des syste'mes modernes, ainsi qu'aux nombreux mods communautaires conçus pour fonctionner avec les jeux originaux. Jouer a' Dark Forces ou, a' l'avenir, a' Outlaws en utilisant le moteur Force ajoutera une facilite' d'utilisation et des fonctionnalite's modernes telles que des re'solutions plus e'leve'es et des sche'mas de contrôle modernes tels que l'apparence de la souris. L'utilisation des outils inte'gre's, une fois qu'ils seront disponibles, facilitera le modding avec une interface plus moderne, une plus grande flexibilite' et la possibilite' d'utiliser les ame'liorations apporte'es au moteur Jedi pour Outlaws dans les niveaux personnalise's de Dark Forces - comme les pentes, les secteurs empile's, les cartes de couleurs par secteur et bien plus encore.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">The Force Engine e' un progetto che ha l'obiettivo di decodificare e ricostruire il Jedi Engine per i sistemi moderni e i giochi che lo utilizzavano - Dark Forces e Outlaws. Il progetto includera' strumenti moderni e integrati, come un editor di livelli, e rendera' facile giocare a Dark Forces e Outlaws sui sistemi moderni, cosi' come alle numerose mod della comunita' progettate per funzionare con i giochi originali. Giocare a Dark Forces o, in futuro, a Outlaws utilizzando il Force Engine aggiungera' facilita' d'uso e caratteristiche moderne come risoluzioni piU' elevate e schemi di controllo moderni come il mouse-look. L'utilizzo degli strumenti integrati, una volta disponibili, consentira' un modding piU' semplice con un'interfaccia utente piU' moderna, una maggiore flessibilita' e la possibilita' di utilizzare i miglioramenti apportati al Jedi Engine per Outlaws nei livelli personalizzati di Dark Forces, come pendenze, settori impilati, mappe di colore per settore e altro ancora.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




