<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>

	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <pos>0.95 0.8</pos>
         <origin>1 0</origin>
         <size>0.90 0.1</size>
         <backgroundColor>00000000</backgroundColor>
         <color>F5F5F5</color>
         <fontPath>${themePath}/_inc/fonts/SF Slapstick Comic Bold.ttf</fontPath>
         <fontSize>0.055</fontSize>
         <text>The Neo Geo MVS, stylised as NEO•GEO MVS, also written as NEOGEO MVS, is a coin-operated arcade machine released in 1990 by Japanese game company SNK Corporation. Its CPU is technically a 16/32-bit 68000-based system with an 8/16-bit Z80 coprocessor, while its GPU chipset has a 24-bit graphics data bus. The MVS offers owners the ability to put up to six different cartridges into a single cabinet, a unique feature that was also a key economic consideration for operators with limited floorspace, as well as saving money long-term. With its games stored on self-contained cartridges, a game cabinet can be exchanged for a different game title by swapping the game's ROM cartridge and cabinet artwork. The Neo Geo MVS was a worldwide commercial success upon release in arcades, becoming one of the highest-earning machines at various arcades across markets. A home console version was also made, called Advanced Entertainment System (AES). Unlike earlier systems, the Neo Geo AES was intended to reproduce the same quality of game as the arcade MVS system.
</text>
			<text lang="es">La Neo Geo MVS, estilizada como NEO-GEO MVS, también escrita como NEOGEO MVS, es una máquina recreativa de monedas lanzada en 1990 por la compañía japonesa de juegos SNK Corporation. Su CPU es técnicamente un sistema basado en 68000 de 16/32 bits con un coprocesador Z80 de 8/16 bits, mientras que su chipset GPU tiene un bus de datos gráficos de 24 bits. La MVS ofrece a los propietarios la posibilidad de colocar hasta seis cartuchos diferentes en un solo armario, una característica única que también era una consideración económica clave para los operadores con espacio limitado, además de ahorrar dinero a largo plazo. Con sus juegos almacenados en cartuchos independientes, un mueble de juego puede cambiarse por otro título intercambiando el cartucho ROM del juego y la carátula del mueble. La Neo Geo MVS fue un éxito comercial en todo el mundo tras su lanzamiento en los salones recreativos, convirtiéndose en una de las máquinas con mayores ganancias en los salones de todos los mercados. También se fabricó una versión para consolas domésticas, llamada Advanced Entertainment System (AES). A diferencia de los sistemas anteriores, el Neo Geo AES pretendía reproducir la misma calidad de juego que el sistema arcade MVS.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Neo Geo MVS, stilisiert als NEO-GEO MVS, auch als NEOGEO MVS geschrieben, ist ein münzbetriebener Arcade-Automat, der 1990 von der japanischen Spielefirma SNK Corporation herausgebracht wurde. Seine CPU ist technisch gesehen ein 16/32-Bit-System auf 68000-Basis mit einem 8/16-Bit-Z80-Coprozessor, während sein GPU-Chipsatz einen 24-Bit-Grafikdatenbus hat. Der MVS bietet den Besitzern die Möglichkeit, bis zu sechs verschiedene Kassetten in einem einzigen Gehäuse unterzubringen, ein einzigartiges Merkmal, das für Betreiber mit begrenztem Platzangebot auch ein wichtiger wirtschaftlicher Aspekt war und langfristig Geld spart. Da die Spiele auf eigenständigen Kassetten gespeichert sind, kann eine Spielkonsole gegen einen anderen Titel ausgetauscht werden, indem die ROM-Kassette des Spiels und das Gehäusedesign ausgetauscht werden. Der Neo Geo MVS war bei seinem Erscheinen in den Spielhallen ein weltweiter kommerzieller Erfolg und wurde zu einem der umsatzstärksten Geräte in verschiedenen Spielhallen auf allen Märkten. Es wurde auch eine Heimkonsolenversion hergestellt, die Advanced Entertainment System (AES) genannt wurde. Im Gegensatz zu früheren Systemen sollte das Neo Geo AES die gleiche Spielqualität bieten wie das MVS-System für Spielhallen.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Neo Geo MVS, stylisé en NEO-GEO MVS, également écrit NEOGEO MVS, est une machine d'arcade à pièces commercialisée en 1990 par la société de jeux japonaise SNK Corporation. Son processeur est techniquement un système à base de 68000 16/32 bits avec un coprocesseur Z80 8/16 bits, tandis que son chipset GPU dispose d'un bus de données graphiques 24 bits. Le MVS offre aux propriétaires la possibilité de placer jusqu'à six cartouches différentes dans une seule armoire, une caractéristique unique qui était également une considération économique clé pour les opérateurs disposant d'un espace limité, ainsi qu'une économie d'argent à long terme. Les jeux étant stockés sur des cartouches autonomes, il est possible de remplacer un boîtier par un autre jeu en échangeant la cartouche ROM du jeu et l'illustration du boîtier. Le Neo Geo MVS a connu un succès commercial mondial dès sa sortie dans les salles d'arcade, devenant l'une des machines les plus rentables dans les salles d'arcade de tous les marchés. Une version pour console de salon a également été produite, appelée Advanced Entertainment System (AES). Contrairement aux systèmes précédents, le Neo Geo AES était destiné à reproduire la même qualité de jeu que le système d'arcade MVS.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Neo Geo MVS, stilizzato come NEO-GEO MVS, scritto anche come NEOGEO MVS, è una macchina arcade a gettoni rilasciata nel 1990 dalla società giapponese SNK Corporation. La sua CPU è tecnicamente un sistema a 16/32 bit basato su 68000 con un coprocessore Z80 a 8/16 bit, mentre il chipset GPU ha un bus dati grafico a 24 bit. L'MVS offre ai proprietari la possibilità di inserire fino a sei cartucce diverse in un singolo cabinet, una caratteristica unica che è stata anche una considerazione economica fondamentale per gli operatori con spazi limitati, oltre che un risparmio a lungo termine. Grazie ai giochi memorizzati su cartucce autonome, un mobile può essere sostituito con un titolo diverso scambiando la cartuccia ROM del gioco e la grafica del mobile. Il Neo Geo MVS è stato un successo commerciale mondiale al momento dell'uscita nelle sale giochi, diventando una delle macchine che ha guadagnato di più nei vari mercati.Fu realizzata anche una versione per console domestica, chiamata Advanced Entertainment System (AES). A differenza dei sistemi precedenti, il Neo Geo AES era destinato a riprodurre la stessa qualità di gioco del sistema arcade MVS.</text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>
				<multiLine>false</multiLine>
				<autoScrollDelay>3000</autoScrollDelay>
				<singleLineScroll>true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>

</theme>