<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>In 1984, a few months after presenting the M24, Olivetti put on the market the M21, the first and only transportable personal computer produced by the Ivrea-based company. The technical features are basically the same as those of the M24, from which the motherboard is also derived with a few modifications. The M21 mounts a monitor with amber phosphors, a real novelty for the time. The Olivetti Personal Computer M21 was a complete computer system, providing the full range of hardware and software options normally associated only with desktop personal computers. Based on the Intel 8086 microprocessor, the M21 supports MS-DOS, CP/M-86 and UCSD operating systems. The system supports an integrated 9" monochrome video, this video provides advanced graphics features with a maximum resolution of 640 x 400 pixels. If a larger screen is required, or colour output is wanted, either of the M24's 12" videos can be connected. The keyboard is a compact, industry-standard 83-key input device. During transit the keyboard is attached to the front of the basic module, thus protecting the video.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">En 1984, pocos meses despue's de presentar el M24, Olivetti saca al mercado el M21, el primer y único ordenador personal transportable producido por la empresa de Ivrea. Las características te'cnicas son básicamente las mismas que las del M24, del que tambie'n deriva la placa base con algunas modificaciones. El M21 monta un monitor con fósforo ámbar, toda una novedad para la e'poca. El Olivetti Personal Computer M21 era un sistema informático completo, que ofrecía toda la gama de opciones de hardware y software normalmente asociadas sólo a los ordenadores personales de sobremesa. Basado en el microprocesador Intel 8086, el M21 es compatible con los sistemas operativos MS-DOS, CP/M-86 y UCSD. El sistema soporta un vídeo monocromo integrado de 9", este vídeo proporciona funciones gráficas avanzadas con una resolución máxima de 640 x 400 píxeles. Si se necesita una pantalla más grande, o se desea una salida en color, se puede conectar cualquiera de los dos vídeos de 12" del M24. El teclado es un dispositivo de entrada compacto y estándar de 83 teclas. Durante el transporte, el teclado se fija a la parte frontal del módulo básico, protegiendo así el vídeo.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">1984, wenige Monate nach der Vorstellung des M24, brachte Olivetti den M21 auf den Markt, den ersten und einzigen transportablen Personal Computer des Unternehmens aus Ivrea. Die technischen Merkmale entsprechen im Wesentlichen denen des M24, von dem auch die Hauptplatine mit einigen Änderungen abgeleitet ist. Der M21 verfügt über einen Monitor mit bernsteinfarbenem Phosphor, eine echte Neuheit für die damalige Zeit. Der Olivetti Personal Computer M21 war ein komplettes Computersystem, das alle Hardware- und Softwareoptionen bot, die man normalerweise nur mit Desktop-Personalcomputern in Verbindung bringt. Der M21 basiert auf dem Intel 8086 Mikroprozessor und unterstützt die Betriebssysteme MS-DOS, CP/M-86 und UCSD. Das System unterstützt ein integriertes 9"-Monochrom-Video, das erweiterte Grafikfunktionen mit einer maximalen Auflösung von 640 x 400 Pixeln bietet. Wenn ein größerer Bildschirm benötigt wird oder eine Farbausgabe gewünscht ist, kann eines der beiden 12"-Videos des M24 angeschlossen werden. Bei der Tastatur handelt es sich um ein kompaktes, dem Industriestandard entsprechendes Eingabegerät mit 83 Tasten. Während des Transports ist die Tastatur an der Vorderseite des Basismoduls angebracht und schützt so das Video.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">En 1984, quelques mois apre's avoir pre'sente' le M24, Olivetti a mis sur le marche' le M21, le premier et le seul ordinateur personnel transportable produit par la socie'te' d'Ivrea. Les caracte'ristiques techniques sont fondamentalement les mêmes que celles du M24, dont la carte me're est e'galement de'rive'e avec quelques modifications. Le M21 est e'quipe' d'un moniteur a' phosphores ambre's, une ve'ritable nouveaute' pour l'e'poque. L'ordinateur personnel Olivetti M21 e'tait un syste'me informatique complet, offrant toute la gamme d'options mate'rielles et logicielles normalement associe'es aux ordinateurs personnels de bureau. Base' sur le microprocesseur Intel 8086, le M21 supporte les syste'mes d'exploitation MS-DOS, CP/M-86 et UCSD. Le syste'me est e'quipe' d'un e'cran vide'o monochrome inte'gre' de 9 pouces, qui offre des fonctions graphiques avance'es avec une re'solution maximale de 640 x 400 pixels. Si un e'cran plus grand est ne'cessaire, ou si une sortie couleur est souhaite'e, l'une des vide'os 12" du M24 peut être connecte'e. Le clavier est un dispositif d'entre'e compact de 83 touches, conforme aux normes industrielles. Pendant le transport, le clavier est fixe' a' l'avant du module de base, prote'geant ainsi la vide'o.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Nel 1984, pochi mesi dopo aver presentato l'M24, Olivetti immette sul mercato l'M21, il primo e unico personal computer trasportabile prodotto dall'azienda di Ivrea. Le caratteristiche tecniche sono sostanzialmente le stesse dell'M24, da cui deriva anche la scheda madre con alcune modifiche. L'M21 monta un monitor con fosfori color ambra, una vera novita' per l'epoca. L'Olivetti Personal Computer M21 era un sistema informatico completo, che offriva l'intera gamma di opzioni hardware e software normalmente associate solo ai personal computer desktop. Basato sul microprocessore Intel 8086, l'M21 supporta i sistemi operativi MS-DOS, CP/M-86 e UCSD. Il sistema supporta un video monocromatico integrato da 9", che offre funzioni grafiche avanzate con una risoluzione massima di 640 x 400 pixel. Se e' necessario uno schermo piU' grande o si desidera un'uscita a colori, e' possibile collegare uno dei due video da 12" dell'M24. La tastiera e' un dispositivo di input compatto e standard del settore a 83 tasti. Durante il trasporto, la tastiera e' fissata alla parte anteriore del modulo base, proteggendo cosi' il video.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




