<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>The 64DD is a magnetic floppy disk drive peripheral for the Nintendo 64 game console developed by Nintendo. It was announced in 1995, prior to the Nintendo 64's 1996 launch, and after numerous delays was released in Japan on December 13, 1999. The "64" references both the Nintendo 64 console and the 64MB storage capacity of the disks, and "DD" is short for "disk drive" or "dynamic drive". Plugging into the extension port on the underside of the console, the 64DD allows the Nintendo 64 to use proprietary 64MB magnetic disks for expanded and rewritable data storage, a real-time clock for persistent game world design, and a standard font and audio library for further storage efficiency. Its games and hardware accessories let the user create movies, characters, and animations to use within various other games and shared online. The system could connect to the Internet through a dedicated online service, Randnet, for e-commerce, online gaming, and media sharing. Describing it as "the first writable bulk data storage device for a modern video game console", Nintendo designed the 64DD as an enabling technology platform for the development of new genres of games and applications, dozens of which were in development for several years.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">El 64DD es un perife'rico de disquetera magne'tica para la videoconsola Nintendo 64 desarrollado por Nintendo. Se anunció en 1995, antes del lanzamiento de Nintendo 64 en 1996, y tras numerosos retrasos salió a la venta en Japón el 13 de diciembre de 1999. El "64" hace referencia tanto a la consola Nintendo 64 como a la capacidad de almacenamiento de 64 MB de los discos, y "DD" es la abreviatura de "disk drive" o "dynamic drive". El 64DD, que se conecta al puerto de extensión situado en la parte inferior de la consola, permite a Nintendo 64 utilizar discos magne'ticos propios de 64 MB para ampliar y reescribir el almacenamiento de datos, un reloj en tiempo real para diseñar mundos de juego persistentes y una biblioteca estándar de fuentes y audio para aumentar la eficiencia del almacenamiento. Sus juegos y accesorios de hardware permiten al usuario crear películas, personajes y animaciones para utilizarlos en otros juegos y compartirlos en línea. El sistema puede conectarse a Internet a trave's de un servicio en línea específico, Randnet, para el comercio electrónico, los juegos en línea y el intercambio de archivos multimedia. Nintendo describió la 64DD como "el primer dispositivo de almacenamiento de datos en masa grabable para una videoconsola moderna" y la diseñó como una plataforma tecnológica que permitiera el desarrollo de nuevos ge'neros de juegos y aplicaciones, docenas de los cuales estuvieron en desarrollo durante varios años.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Das 64DD ist ein von Nintendo entwickeltes Magnetdiskettenlaufwerk für die Spielkonsole Nintendo 64. Es wurde 1995, vor der Markteinführung des Nintendo 64 im Jahr 1996, angekündigt und nach zahlreichen Verzögerungen am 13. Dezember 1999 in Japan veröffentlicht. Das "64" bezieht sich sowohl auf die Nintendo 64-Konsole als auch auf die 64 MB Speicherkapazität der Disketten, und "DD" ist die Abkürzung für "disk drive" oder "dynamic drive". Das 64DD wird in den Erweiterungsanschluss an der Unterseite der Konsole eingesteckt und ermöglicht es dem Nintendo 64, proprietäre 64-MB-Magnetplatten für erweiterte und wiederbeschreibbare Datenspeicherung, eine Echtzeituhr für die dauerhafte Gestaltung der Spielwelt und eine Standard-Schrift- und Audiobibliothek für weitere Speichereffizienz zu verwenden. Mit den Spielen und dem Hardware-Zubehör konnte der Benutzer Filme, Charaktere und Animationen erstellen, die er in verschiedenen anderen Spielen verwenden und online teilen konnte. Das System kann über einen speziellen Online-Dienst, Randnet, mit dem Internet verbunden werden, um E-Commerce, Online-Spiele und die gemeinsame Nutzung von Medien zu ermöglichen. Nintendo beschrieb es als "das erste beschreibbare Massenspeichergerät für eine moderne Videospielkonsole" und konzipierte das 64DD als Technologieplattform für die Entwicklung neuer Spielgenres und Anwendungen, von denen Dutzende mehrere Jahre lang in Entwicklung waren.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Le 64DD est un pe'riphe'rique de lecteur de disquettes magne'tiques pour la console de jeu Nintendo 64 de'veloppe' par Nintendo. Il a e'te' annonce' en 1995, avant le lancement de la Nintendo 64 en 1996, et apre's de nombreux retards, il est sorti au Japon le 13 de'cembre 1999. Le terme "64" fait re'fe'rence a' la fois a' la console Nintendo 64 et a' la capacite' de stockage de 64 Mo des disques, et "DD" est l'abre'viation de "disk drive" (lecteur de disquettes) ou "dynamic drive" (lecteur dynamique). Branche' sur le port d'extension situe' sous la console, le 64DD permet a' la Nintendo 64 d'utiliser des disques magne'tiques proprie'taires de 64 Mo pour un stockage de donne'es e'tendu et re'inscriptible, une horloge en temps re'el pour la conception d'un univers de jeu persistant et une bibliothe'que de polices et de sons standard pour une efficacite' de stockage accrue. Ses jeux et accessoires mate'riels permettent a' l'utilisateur de cre'er des films, des personnages et des animations a' utiliser dans d'autres jeux et a' partager en ligne. Le syste'me peut se connecter a' l'internet par l'interme'diaire d'un service en ligne spe'cialise', Randnet, pour le commerce e'lectronique, les jeux en ligne et le partage de me'dias. En le de'crivant comme "le premier dispositif de stockage de donne'es en masse inscriptible pour une console de jeu vide'o moderne", Nintendo a conçu le 64DD comme une plate-forme technologique permettant le de'veloppement de nouveaux genres de jeux et d'applications, dont des douzaines e'taient en cours de de'veloppement depuis plusieurs anne'es.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Il 64DD e' una periferica per lettore di dischi magnetici per la console Nintendo 64, sviluppata da Nintendo. Fu annunciato nel 1995, prima del lancio del Nintendo 64 nel 1996, e dopo numerosi ritardi e' stato rilasciato in Giappone il 13 dicembre 1999. Il termine "64" si riferisce sia alla console Nintendo 64 che alla capacita' di memorizzazione dei dischi di 64 MB, mentre "DD" e' l'abbreviazione di "disk drive" o "dynamic drive". Collegato alla porta di estensione sul lato inferiore della console, il 64DD consente al Nintendo 64 di utilizzare dischi magnetici proprietari da 64 MB per la memorizzazione estesa e riscrivibile di dati, un orologio in tempo reale per la progettazione di mondi di gioco persistenti e una libreria di font e audio standard per un'ulteriore efficienza di memorizzazione. I giochi e gli accessori hardware consentono all'utente di creare filmati, personaggi e animazioni da utilizzare in altri giochi e da condividere online. Il sistema poteva connettersi a Internet attraverso un servizio online dedicato, Randnet, per il commercio elettronico, il gioco online e la condivisione dei media. Descritto come "il primo dispositivo di archiviazione dati scrivibile per una moderna console per videogiochi", Nintendo progetto' il 64DD come piattaforma tecnologica abilitante per lo sviluppo di nuovi generi di giochi e applicazioni, decine dei quali furono in fase di sviluppo per diversi anni.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




