<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>

	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <pos>0.95 0.8</pos>
         <origin>1 0</origin>
         <size>0.90 0.1</size>
         <backgroundColor>00000000</backgroundColor>
         <color>F5F5F5</color>
         <fontPath>${themePath}/_inc/fonts/SF Slapstick Comic Bold.ttf</fontPath>
         <fontSize>0.055</fontSize>
         <text>The Namco System 12 is an arcade motherboard developed by Namco and released in late 1996. It is an upgrade of the previous System 11, based on Sony’s PlayStation, featuring a MIPS R3000A microprocessor that is 50% faster and a new Hitachi H8/3002 sound processor. This hardware powered iconic titles like Tekken 3, Soulcalibur, and Mr. Driller, renowned for their advanced 3D graphics and smooth gameplay.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Namco System 12 è una scheda madre arcade sviluppata da Namco e rilasciata alla fine del 1996. Si tratta di un aggiornamento della precedente System 11, basata sulla PlayStation di Sony, con un microprocessore MIPS R3000A più veloce del 50% e un nuovo processore audio Hitachi H8/3002. Questo hardware ha alimentato titoli iconici come Tekken 3, Soulcalibur e Mr. Driller, rinomati per la loro grafica 3D avanzata e la fluidità di gioco.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Namco System 12 est une carte mère d'arcade développée par Namco et sortie fin 1996. Il s'agit d'une mise à jour du précédent System 11, basé sur la PlayStation de Sony, avec un microprocesseur MIPS R3000A 50% plus rapide et un nouveau processeur de son Hitachi H8/3002. Ce matériel a alimenté des titres emblématiques tels que Tekken 3, Soulcalibur et Mr. Driller, réputés pour leurs graphismes 3D avancés et leur fluidité de jeu.</text>
			<text lang="de">Das Namco System 12 ist ein Arcade-Motherboard, das von Namco entwickelt und Ende 1996 veröffentlicht wurde. Es ist ein Upgrade des vorherigen System 11, das auf Sonys PlayStation basierte, mit einem MIPS R3000A Mikroprozessor, der 50 % schneller ist, und einem neuen Hitachi H8/3002 Soundprozessor. Auf dieser Hardware liefen Kulttitel wie Tekken 3, Soulcalibur und Mr. Driller, die für ihre fortschrittliche 3D-Grafik und ihr flüssiges Gameplay bekannt waren.</text>
			<text lang="es">El Namco System 12 es una placa base arcade desarrollada por Namco y lanzada a finales de 1996. Se trata de una actualización de la anterior System 11, basada en la PlayStation de Sony, que incorpora un microprocesador MIPS R3000A un 50% más rápido y un nuevo procesador de sonido Hitachi H8/3002. Este hardware impulsó títulos emblemáticos como Tekken 3, Soulcalibur y Mr. Driller, famosos por sus avanzados gráficos en 3D y su fluida jugabilidad.</text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>
				<multiLine>false</multiLine>
				<autoScrollDelay>3000</autoScrollDelay>
				<singleLineScroll>true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>

</theme>