<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>Palm was a line of personal digital assistants (PDAs) and mobile phones developed by California-based Palm, Inc., originally called Palm Computing, Inc. Palm devices are often remembered as the first wildly popular handheld computers, responsible for ushering in the smartphone era. The first Palm device, the PalmPilot 1000, was released in 1996 and proved to be popular. It led a growing market for portable computing devices where previous attempts such as Apple's Newton failed or others like Hewlett-Packard's 200LX only serving a niche target market. Most of Palm's PDAs and mobile phones ran the in-house Palm OS software which was later also licensed to other OEMs.
<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">Palm fue una línea de asistentes personales digitales (PDA) y tele'fonos móviles desarrollada por la empresa californiana Palm, Inc, originalmente llamada Palm Computing, Inc. Los dispositivos Palm se recuerdan a menudo como los primeros ordenadores de mano tremendamente populares, responsables del inicio de la era de los smartphones. El primer dispositivo Palm, el PalmPilot 1000, salió al mercado en 1996 y demostró su popularidad. Encabezó un mercado creciente de dispositivos informáticos portátiles donde intentos anteriores como el Newton de Apple fracasaron u otros como el 200LX de Hewlett-Packard sólo sirvieron a un nicho de mercado objetivo. La mayoría de las PDA y tele'fonos móviles de Palm funcionaban con el software Palm OS, que más tarde se licenció a otros fabricantes.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Palm war eine Reihe von Personal Digital Assistants (PDAs) und Mobiltelefonen, die von der in Kalifornien ansässigen Palm, Inc. entwickelt wurden, die ursprünglich Palm Computing, Inc. hieß. Palm-Geräte werden oft als die ersten sehr beliebten Handheld-Computer bezeichnet, die das Zeitalter der Smartphones einleiteten. Das erste Palm-Gerät, der PalmPilot 1000, wurde 1996 auf den Markt gebracht und erwies sich als sehr beliebt. Es führte einen wachsenden Markt für tragbare Computer an, wo frühere Versuche wie der Newton von Apple scheiterten oder andere wie der 200LX von Hewlett-Packard nur einen Nischenmarkt bedienten. Die meisten PDAs und Mobiltelefone von Palm liefen mit der hauseigenen Palm OS-Software, die später auch an andere OEMs lizenziert wurde.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Palm est une gamme d'assistants nume'riques personnels (PDA) et de te'le'phones mobiles de'veloppe'e par la socie'te' californienne Palm, Inc. qui s'appelait a' l'origine Palm Computing, Inc. Les appareils Palm sont souvent conside're's comme les premiers ordinateurs de poche tre's populaires, qui ont inaugure' l'e're des smartphones. Le premier appareil Palm, le PalmPilot 1000, est sorti en 1996 et s'est ave're' tre's populaire. Il a e'te' a' l'origine d'un marche' en pleine expansion pour les appareils informatiques portables, alors que les tentatives pre'ce'dentes, comme le Newton d'Apple, avaient e'choue' ou que d'autres, comme le 200LX de Hewlett-Packard, n'avaient servi qu'un marche' cible de niche. La plupart des PDA et des te'le'phones mobiles de Palm fonctionnent avec le logiciel interne Palm OS, qui a ensuite e'te' ce'de' sous licence a' d'autres fabricants de mate'riel informatique.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Palm e' stata una linea di assistenti digitali personali (PDA) e telefoni cellulari sviluppata dalla societa' californiana Palm, Inc., originariamente chiamata Palm Computing, Inc. I dispositivi Palm sono spesso ricordati come i primi computer palmari estremamente popolari, responsabili di aver dato il via all'era degli smartphone. Il primo dispositivo Palm, il PalmPilot 1000, e' stato rilasciato nel 1996 e si e' rivelato molto popolare. Ha guidato un mercato in crescita per i dispositivi informatici portatili dove i tentativi precedenti, come il Newton di Apple, sono falliti o altri, come il 200LX di Hewlett-Packard, hanno servito solo una nicchia di mercato. La maggior parte dei PDA e dei telefoni cellulari di Palm utilizzava il software Palm OS interno, che in seguito e' stato concesso in licenza anche ad altri OEM.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




