<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>The PlayChoice-10 is an arcade machine with 10 games, previously released only for the NES. The games for this system are in the form of modular circuits that plug into one of the ten slots on the PlayChoice-10's motherboard. Unlike the original NES cartridges, the modular cards available for the PlayChoice-10 also contain an additional portion of ROM, which in turn contains information and hints about the game in use. Otherwise, the gameplay is the same, but NES cartridges are generally not compatible with the PlayChoice-10. Unlike standard arcade games, each game session had a time limit, after which the credits in use ran out. However, it was possible to switch games during the session. The machine is based on the same hardware as the NES, but with some differences. The chip that controls the RGB video output offers slightly different color rendering than the original console, and it also features an additional CPU. The latter is primarily used to manage the game selection menu and especially the timer, but it also displays, in cabinets equipped with a secondary screen, the information contained in the additional ROM present only on the "naked" PlayChoice-10 cartridges. Shortly before the release of the Super Nintendo Entertainment System in the United States, the company launched the Nintendo Super System, an arcade system created to make some of the flagship games of its new home console playable in arcades. Like the PlayChoice-10, each game has a time limit, which depends on the player's available credits. A maximum of three games can be installed, again in the form of modular cards.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">PlayChoice-10 e' una macchina arcade con 10 giochi disponibili, precedentemente pubblicati soltanto per NES. I giochi per questo sistema sono in forma di circuiti modulari collegati in una delle dieci slot della scheda madre del PlayChoice-10. Rispetto alle cartucce originali del NES, le schede modulari disponibili per il PlayChoice-10 contengono anche una porzione aggiuntiva di ROM, contenente a sua volta informazioni e suggerimenti sul gioco in uso. Per il resto il gioco e' lo stesso, ma in linea di massima le cartucce per il NES non sono compatibili con il PlayChoice-10. A differenza dei comuni giochi arcade, ogni sessione di gioco aveva un tempo limite, oltre il quale il credit in uso si esauriva. In compenso, durante la sessione era possibile cambiare gioco. La macchina e' basata sul medesimo hardware del NES, ma con alcune differenze. Il chip da cui dipende l'uscita video RGB offre una resa cromatica leggermente diversa rispetto a quella della console originale, inoltre e' presente una CPU supplementare. Quest'ultima serve principalmente a gestire il menu di selezione dei giochi e soprattutto il timer, ma serve anche a mostrare, nei cabinati dotati di schermo secondario, le informazioni contenute nella ROM aggiuntiva presente solo nelle "cartucce nude" del PlayChoice-10. Poco prima dell'uscita del Super Nintendo Entertainment System negli Stati Uniti, la compagnia ha lanciato il Nintendo Super System, sistema arcade creato per rendere giocabili in sala giochi alcuni dei giochi di punta della sua nuova console casalinga. Come il PlayChoice-10, ogni partita ha un tempo limite, che dipende dai crediti a disposizione del giocatore. I giochi installabili sono al massimo tre, anche in questo caso sotto forma di schede modulari.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">La PlayChoice-10 est une borne d'arcade proposant 10 jeux, initialement sortie uniquement sur NES. Les jeux se pre'sentent sous forme de modules qui s'inse'rent dans l'un des dix emplacements de la carte me're de la PlayChoice-10. Contrairement aux cartouches NES originales, les modules de la PlayChoice-10 contiennent une ROM supple'mentaire, renfermant des informations et des astuces sur le jeu en cours. Le gameplay reste identique, mais les cartouches NES sont ge'ne'ralement incompatibles avec la PlayChoice-10. a' la diffe'rence des bornes d'arcade classiques, chaque partie est limite'e dans le temps, apre's quoi le cre'dit en cours est e'puise'. Il est toutefois possible de changer de jeu en cours de partie. La borne utilise le même mate'riel que la NES, avec quelques diffe'rences. La puce ge'rant la sortie vide'o RGB offre un rendu des couleurs le'ge'rement diffe'rent de celui de la console originale, et elle inte'gre e'galement un processeur supple'mentaire. Ce dernier sert principalement a' ge'rer le menu de se'lection des jeux et surtout le chronome'tre, mais il affiche e'galement, dans les bornes e'quipe'es d'un e'cran secondaire, les informations contenues dans la ROM supple'mentaire pre'sente uniquement sur les cartouches PlayChoice-10 « nues ». Peu avant la sortie de la Super Nintendo Entertainment System aux e'tats-Unis, Nintendo a lance' la Nintendo Super System, un syste'me d'arcade conçu pour rendre jouables en salle d'arcade certains des jeux phares de sa nouvelle console de salon. Comme pour la PlayChoice-10, chaque jeu a une limite de temps, qui de'pend des cre'dits disponibles du joueur. On peut installer jusqu'a' trois jeux, toujours sous forme de cartes modulaires.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Der PlayChoice-10 ist ein Arcade-Automat mit zehn Spielen, die zuvor nur für das NES erschienen waren. Die Spiele liegen als Modulkarten vor, die in einen der zehn Steckplätze auf dem Motherboard des PlayChoice-10 gesteckt werden. Anders als die originalen NES-Module enthalten die Modulkarten des PlayChoice-10 zusätzlich einen ROM-Speicher, der Informationen und Hinweise zum jeweiligen Spiel enthält. Ansonsten ist das Gameplay identisch, allerdings sind NES-Module in der Regel nicht mit dem PlayChoice-10 kompatibel. Im Gegensatz zu herkömmlichen Arcade-Spielen war jede Spielsitzung zeitlich begrenzt; nach Ablauf dieser Zeit waren die verwendeten Credits aufgebraucht. Es war jedoch möglich, während der Sitzung das Spiel zu wechseln. Der Automat basiert auf der gleichen Hardware wie das NES, weist aber einige Unterschiede auf. Der Chip, der die RGB-Videoausgabe steuert, bietet eine etwas andere Farbwiedergabe als die Originalkonsole, und er verfügt außerdem über eine zusätzliche CPU. Letzteres dient primär der Steuerung des Spielauswahlmenüs und insbesondere des Timers. In Automaten mit Zweitbildschirm werden darüber außerdem die Informationen des zusätzlichen ROMs angezeigt, das nur auf den „nackten“ PlayChoice-10-Modulen vorhanden ist. Kurz vor der Veröffentlichung des Super Nintendo Entertainment System in den USA brachte Nintendo das Nintendo Super System auf den Markt, ein Arcade-System, das einige der wichtigsten Spiele der neuen Heimkonsole in Spielhallen spielbar machen sollte. Wie beim PlayChoice-10 hat jedes Spiel ein Zeitlimit, das von den verfügbaren Credits des Spielers abhängt. Es können maximal drei Spiele installiert werden, wiederum in Form von Modulkarten.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">La PlayChoice-10 es una máquina recreativa con 10 juegos, originalmente lanzada solo para la NES. Los juegos para este sistema son circuitos modulares que se conectan a una de las diez ranuras de la placa base de la PlayChoice-10. A diferencia de los cartuchos originales de la NES, las tarjetas modulares disponibles para la PlayChoice-10 tambie'n contienen una porción adicional de ROM, que a su vez contiene información y pistas sobre el juego en uso. Por lo demás, la jugabilidad es la misma, pero los cartuchos de la NES generalmente no son compatibles con la PlayChoice-10. A diferencia de los juegos arcade estándar, cada sesión de juego tenía un límite de tiempo, tras el cual se agotaban los cre'ditos utilizados. Sin embargo, era posible cambiar de juego durante la sesión. La máquina se basa en el mismo hardware que la NES, pero con algunas diferencias. El chip que controla la salida de vídeo RGB ofrece una reproducción de color ligeramente diferente a la de la consola original, y tambie'n cuenta con una CPU adicional. Este último se utiliza principalmente para gestionar el menú de selección de juegos y, sobre todo, el temporizador, pero tambie'n muestra, en máquinas recreativas equipadas con una pantalla secundaria, la información contenida en la ROM adicional presente únicamente en los cartuchos PlayChoice-10 originales. Poco antes del lanzamiento de la Super Nintendo Entertainment System en Estados Unidos, la compañía lanzó la Nintendo Super System, un sistema arcade creado para que algunos de los juegos estrella de su nueva consola dome'stica pudieran jugarse en salones recreativos. Al igual que en la PlayChoice-10, cada juego tiene un límite de tiempo, que depende de los cre'ditos disponibles del jugador. Se pueden instalar un máximo de tres juegos, tambie'n en forma de tarjetas modulares.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>





