<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>

	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <pos>0.95 0.8</pos>
         <origin>1 0</origin>
         <size>0.90 0.1</size>
         <backgroundColor>00000000</backgroundColor>
         <color>F5F5F5</color>
         <fontPath>${themePath}/_inc/fonts/SF Slapstick Comic Bold.ttf</fontPath>
         <fontSize>0.055</fontSize>
         <text>The Nintendo Switch is a video game console, developed by Nintendo and released worldwide in most regions on March 3, 2017. It is a hybrid console that can be used as either a home console or a portable device. Its wireless Joy-Con controllers, with standard buttons and directional analog sticks for user input, motion sensing, and tactile feedback, can attach to both sides of the console to support handheld-style play. They can also connect to a grip accessory to provide a traditional home console gamepad form, or be used individually in the hand like the Wii Remote and Nunchuk, supporting local multiplayer modes. The Nintendo Switch's software supports online gaming through Internet connectivity, as well as local wireless ad hoc connectivity with other consoles. Nintendo Switch games and software are available on both physical flash-based ROM cartridges and digital distribution via Nintendo eShop; the system has no region lockout. A handheld-focused revision of the system, called the Nintendo Switch Lite, was released on September 20, 2019.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Nintendo Switch es una videoconsola, desarrollada por Nintendo y lanzada mundialmente en la mayoría de las regiones el 3 de marzo de 2017. Es una consola híbrida que puede utilizarse como consola doméstica o como dispositivo portátil. Sus mandos inalámbricos Joy-Con, con botones estándar y sticks analógicos direccionales para la entrada del usuario, detección de movimiento y retroalimentación táctil, pueden acoplarse a ambos lados de la consola para soportar el juego de estilo portátil. También pueden conectarse a un accesorio de agarre para ofrecer una forma de gamepad de consola doméstica tradicional, o utilizarse individualmente en la mano como el mando de Wii y el Nunchuk, con soporte para modos multijugador locales. El software de Nintendo Switch admite el juego en línea a través de la conectividad a Internet, así como la conectividad ad hoc inalámbrica local con otras consolas. Los juegos y el software de Nintendo Switch están disponibles tanto en cartuchos ROM físicos basados en flash como en distribución digital a través de Nintendo eShop; la consola no tiene bloqueo regional. El 20 de septiembre de 2019 se lanzó una revisión de la consola centrada en la consola portátil, llamada Nintendo Switch Lite.</text>
			<text lang="de">Die Nintendo Switch ist eine Videospielkonsole, die von Nintendo entwickelt und am 3. März 2017 weltweit in den meisten Regionen veröffentlicht wurde. Es ist eine Hybridkonsole, die entweder als Heimkonsole oder als tragbares Gerät verwendet werden kann. Die kabellosen Joy-Con-Controller mit Standardtasten und richtungsabhängigen Analogsticks für Benutzereingaben, Bewegungserkennung und taktilem Feedback können an beiden Seiten der Konsole befestigt werden, um das Spielen im Handheld-Stil zu unterstützen. Sie können auch an ein Griffzubehör angeschlossen werden, um eine traditionelle Heimkonsolen-Gamepad-Form zu erhalten, oder sie können einzeln in der Hand wie die Wii-Fernbedienung und das Nunchuk verwendet werden und unterstützen lokale Multiplayer-Modi. Die Software der Nintendo Switch unterstützt Online-Spiele über eine Internetverbindung sowie eine lokale drahtlose Ad-hoc-Verbindung mit anderen Konsolen. Nintendo Switch-Spiele und -Software sind sowohl auf physischen Flash-basierten ROM-Kassetten als auch digital über den Nintendo eShop erhältlich; das System hat keine Regionalsperre. Eine auf Handhelds fokussierte Version des Systems, die Nintendo Switch Lite, wurde am 20. September 2019 veröffentlicht.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Nintendo Switch est une console de jeux vidéo, développée par Nintendo et sortie mondialement dans la plupart des régions le 3 mars 2017. Il s'agit d'une console hybride qui peut être utilisée comme console de salon ou comme appareil portable. Ses manettes Joy-Con sans fil, dotées de boutons standard et de sticks analogiques directionnels pour la saisie par l'utilisateur, la détection de mouvement et le retour tactile, peuvent se fixer des deux côtés de la console pour prendre en charge le jeu de type portable. Elles peuvent également se connecter à un accessoire de préhension pour prendre la forme d'une manette de jeu de console de salon traditionnelle, ou être utilisées individuellement dans la main, comme la télécommande Wii et le Nunchuk, et prendre en charge les modes multijoueurs locaux. Le logiciel de la Nintendo Switch prend en charge le jeu en ligne via la connectivité Internet, ainsi que la connectivité locale sans fil ad hoc avec d'autres consoles. Les jeux et logiciels de la Nintendo Switch sont disponibles à la fois sur des cartouches ROM physiques à mémoire flash et en distribution numérique via Nintendo eShop ; la console n'a pas de verrouillage régional. Une révision de la console axée sur la console portable, appelée Nintendo Switch Lite, est sortie le 20 septembre 2019.</text>
			<text lang="it">Nintendo Switch è una console per videogiochi, sviluppata da Nintendo e rilasciata in tutto il mondo nella maggior parte delle regioni il 3 marzo 2017. È una console ibrida che può essere utilizzata sia come console domestica che come dispositivo portatile. I suoi controller Joy-Con wireless, con pulsanti standard e stick analogici direzionali per l'input dell'utente, il rilevamento del movimento e il feedback tattile, possono essere collegati a entrambi i lati della console per supportare il gioco in stile portatile. Possono anche essere collegati a un accessorio per l'impugnatura per ottenere una forma tradizionale di gamepad per console domestica, o essere usati singolarmente nella mano come il telecomando Wii e il Nunchuk, supportando le modalità multiplayer locali. Il software di Nintendo Switch supporta il gioco online attraverso la connettività Internet e la connettività locale wireless ad hoc con altre console. I giochi e i software di Nintendo Switch sono disponibili sia su cartucce ROM fisiche basate su flash che in distribuzione digitale tramite il Nintendo eShop; la console non ha il blocco regionale. Il 20 settembre 2019 è stata rilasciata una versione della console incentrata sulla modalità portatile, chiamata Nintendo Switch Lite.</text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>
				<multiLine>false</multiLine>
				<autoScrollDelay>3000</autoScrollDelay>
				<singleLineScroll>true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>

</theme>