<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>Here is a collection of all the games created by Banpresto and featured on this machine.                                                             Banpresto Co., Ltd. (株式会社バンプレスト, Kabushiki-gaisha Banpuresuto) is a Japanese software development company based in Shinagawa, Tokyo. The company was founded in April 1977 as Hoei Sangyo, Co. Ltd., and renamed Coreland in 1982. During the 1980s, it primarily produced SEGA and arcade video games. In 1989, it was partially acquired by Bandai, which gave it its current name. Since March 2006, it has been a subsidiary of Namco Bandai. Banpresto's video game division was absorbed by Namco Bandai Games on April 1, 2008. As part of the merger, two of Banpresto's subsidiaries, Pleasure Cast Co. Ltd. and Hanayashiki Co. Ltd., became subsidiaries of Namco. Banpresto itself now focuses primarily on arcade game production. The company also operates in the publication of action figures inspired by anime and manga.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Ecco una raccolta di tutti i giochi creati dalla Banpresto e presenti su questa macchina.                                                             Banpresto Co., Ltd. (株式会社バンプレスト?, Kabushiki-gaisha Banpuresuto) e' una software house giapponese con sede a Shinagawa, Tokyo. L'azienda e' stata fondata nell'aprile 1977 con il nome di Hoei Sangyo, Co. Ltd., per poi essere ribattezzata nel 1982 Coreland. Durante gli anni ottanta lavoro' principalmente nella produzione di videogiochi SEGA e Arcade. Sin dal 1989 e' stata rilevata in parte dalla Bandai che gli ha dato l'attuale nome. Dal marzo 2006 e' diventata una sussidiaria della Namco Bandai. La sezione della Banpresto che si occupava dei videogiochi e' stata assorbita dalla Namco Bandai Games il 1º aprile 2008. Come parte della fusione, due delle sussidiarie della banpresto, la Pleasure Cast Co. Ltd e la Hanayashiki Co. Ltd, sono diventate sussidiarie della Namco. La Banpresto stessa adesso si occupa principalmente della produzione di giochi arcade. Altro settore in cui l'azienda e' operativa sono le pubblicazioni di action figure ispirate ad anime e manga.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Voici une collection de tous les jeux cre'e's par Banpresto et disponibles sur cette machine.                                                             Banpresto Co., Ltd. (株式会社バンプレスト, Kabushiki-gaisha Banpuresuto) est une socie'te' japonaise de de'veloppement de logiciels base'e a' Shinagawa, Tokyo. Fonde'e en avril 1977 sous le nom de Hoei Sangyo, Co., Ltd., elle est rebaptise'e Coreland en 1982. Dans les anne'es 1980, elle produisait principalement des jeux vide'o pour SEGA et des jeux d'arcade. En 1989, elle est partiellement rachete'e par Bandai, qui lui donne son nom actuel. Depuis mars 2006, elle est une filiale de Namco Bandai. La division jeux vide'o de Banpresto est absorbe'e par Namco Bandai Games le 1er avril 2008. Dans le cadre de cette fusion, deux filiales de Banpresto, Pleasure Cast Co., Ltd. et Hanayashiki Co., Ltd., deviennent des filiales de Namco. Banpresto se concentre de'sormais principalement sur la production de jeux d'arcade. L'entreprise est e'galement active dans l'e'dition de figurines inspire'es des anime's et des mangas.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Hier ist eine Sammlung aller von Banpresto entwickelten und auf dieser Maschine enthaltenen Spiele.                                                             Banpresto Co., Ltd. (株式会社バンプレスト, Kabushiki-gaisha Banpuresuto) ist ein japanisches Softwareentwicklungsunternehmen mit Sitz in Shinagawa, Tokio. Das Unternehmen wurde im April 1977 als Hoei Sangyo, Co. Ltd. gegründet und 1982 in Coreland umbenannt. In den 1980er Jahren produzierte es hauptsächlich Videospiele für SEGA und Arcade-Automaten. 1989 wurde es teilweise von Bandai übernommen, wodurch es seinen heutigen Namen erhielt. Seit März 2006 ist es eine Tochtergesellschaft von Namco Bandai. Die Videospielsparte von Banpresto wurde am 1. April 2008 von Namco Bandai Games übernommen. Im Zuge dieser Fusion wurden zwei Banpresto-Tochtergesellschaften, Pleasure Cast Co. Ltd. und Hanayashiki Co. Ltd., ebenfalls Tochtergesellschaften von Namco. Banpresto konzentriert sich mittlerweile hauptsächlich auf die Produktion von Arcade-Spielen. Das Unternehmen ist außerdem im Bereich der Veröffentlichung von Actionfiguren tätig, die von Anime und Manga inspiriert sind.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">Aquí tene'is una recopilación de todos los juegos creados por Banpresto e incluidos en esta máquina.                                                             Banpresto Co., Ltd. (株式会社バンプレスト, Kabushiki-gaisha Banpuresuto) es una empresa japonesa de desarrollo de software con sede en Shinagawa, Tokio. La empresa fue fundada en abril de 1977 como Hoei Sangyo, Co. Ltd., y renombrada Coreland en 1982. Durante la de'cada de 1980, produjo principalmente videojuegos para SEGA y máquinas recreativas. En 1989, fue adquirida parcialmente por Bandai, que le dio su nombre actual. Desde marzo de 2006, es una filial de Namco Bandai. La división de videojuegos de Banpresto fue absorbida por Namco Bandai Games el 1 de abril de 2008. Como parte de la fusión, dos de las filiales de Banpresto, Pleasure Cast Co. Ltd. y Hanayashiki Co. Ltd., se convirtieron en filiales de Namco. Actualmente, Banpresto se centra principalmente en la producción de videojuegos arcade. La compañía tambie'n se dedica a la publicación de figuras de acción inspiradas en el anime y el manga.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>





