<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>Here is a collection of all the games created by Amcoe and featured on this machine. - Amcoe is a well-known developer of classic coin-operated "8-liner" and video slot arcade boards, widely celebrated by retrogaming collectors. Their flagship hardware typically utilizes standard 36/10 pin "Cherry Master" harnesses to power mechanical-style reel or screen-based fruit games. -<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Ecco una raccolta di tutti i giochi creati dalla Amcoe e presenti su questa macchina. -Amcoe è un noto sviluppatore di schede arcade classiche a gettoni "8-liner" e video slot, molto apprezzate dai collezionisti di retrogaming. Il loro hardware di punta utilizza in genere cablaggi standard "Cherry Master" a 36/10 pin per alimentare giochi di slot a rulli o a schermo in stile meccanico. -<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Voici une collection de tous les jeux créés par Amcoe et disponibles sur cette machine. - Amcoe est un développeur renommé de bornes d'arcade classiques à pièces (« 8-liner ») et de machines à sous vidéo, très appréciées des collectionneurs de jeux rétro. Leurs machines phares utilisent généralement des connecteurs « Cherry Master » standard à 36/10 broches pour alimenter des jeux de machines à sous mécaniques ou à écran tactile. -<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Hier ist eine Sammlung aller von Amcoe entwickelten und auf dieser Maschine enthaltenen Spiele. - Amcoe ist ein bekannter Entwickler klassischer, münzbetriebener „8-Liner“- und Video-Slot-Arcade-Automaten, die bei Sammlern von Retro-Spielen sehr beliebt sind. Ihre Flaggschiff-Hardware verwendet typischerweise Standard-36/10-Pin-„Cherry Master“-Kabelbäume zur Ansteuerung von mechanischen Walzen- oder bildschirmbasierten Fruchtspielen. -<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">Aquí tenéis una recopilación de todos los juegos creados por Amcoe e incluidos en esta máquina. - Amcoe es un reconocido desarrollador de placas arcade clásicas de máquinas tragamonedas de 8 líneas y video, muy apreciadas por los coleccionistas de juegos retro. Su hardware insignia suele utilizar conectores estándar "Cherry Master" de 36/10 pines para alimentar juegos de frutas mecánicos, ya sean de rodillos o de pantalla. -<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




