<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>

	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <pos>0.95 0.8</pos>
         <origin>1 0</origin>
         <size>0.90 0.1</size>
         <backgroundColor>00000000</backgroundColor>
         <color>F5F5F5</color>
         <fontPath>${themePath}/_inc/fonts/SF Slapstick Comic Bold.ttf</fontPath>
         <fontSize>0.055</fontSize>
         <text>Bermuda Syndrome is a platform game developed by Century Interactive and published by BMG Interactive in 1995. The game is similar in gameplay and appearance to the classic Flashback from 1992. The player controls the main character from a third person side-scrolling perspective. The main character is Jack Thompson, a member of a US air force strategic bomber squadron during World War 2. During a mission above Germany his plane gets attacked by German fighters and catches fire. Somehow, a portal opens up as the plane is going down, and it enters what is presumably a parallel universe or an alternate timeline. Jack finds himself descending not upon the German countryside, but on a strange, unfamiliar jungle landscape. Meanwhile, on the ground, we see a tied up young woman, struggling to get loose as a gigantic carnivorous dinosaur approaches. Jacks plane luckily hits and decapitates the creature, preventing the woman from being eaten. At the last second Jack bails out, and at the beginning of the game he dangles in his parachute from a tree, with a boot-knife as his only weapon. After cutting the woman loose, she is revealed to be a princess who was going to be sacrificed by her father. She becomes Jacks companion throughout the game. The adventure consists of a large number of static panels in which the player moves to solve puzzles and battle dinosaurs that attack. Objects can be picked up, and using them in the right context is often required to progress to the next screen. Other problems are often solved by jumping or interacting with the princess.</text>
         <text lang="it">Bermuda Syndrome è un gioco platform sviluppato da Century Interactive e pubblicato da BMG Interactive nel 1995. Il gioco è simile, sia nel gameplay che nell'aspetto, al classico Flashback del 1992. Il giocatore controlla il personaggio principale da una prospettiva a scorrimento laterale in terza persona. Il personaggio principale è Jack Thompson, membro di uno squadrone di bombardieri strategici dell'aeronautica militare statunitense durante la Seconda Guerra Mondiale. Durante una missione sopra la Germania, il suo aereo viene attaccato dai caccia tedeschi e prende fuoco. In qualche modo, mentre l'aereo sta precipitando, si apre un portale che conduce a quello che presumibilmente è un universo parallelo o una linea temporale alternativa. Jack si ritrova a scendere non nella campagna tedesca, ma in uno strano e sconosciuto paesaggio di giungla. Nel frattempo, a terra, vediamo una giovane donna legata, che lotta per liberarsi mentre un gigantesco dinosauro carnivoro si avvicina. L'aereo di Jack fortunatamente colpisce e decapita la creatura, impedendo alla donna di essere mangiata. All'ultimo secondo Jack si lancia con il paracadute e all'inizio del gioco penzola da un albero con il suo paracadute, con un coltello da stivale come unica arma. Dopo aver liberato la donna, si scopre che si tratta di una principessa che stava per essere sacrificata dal padre. Diventa la compagna di Jack per tutto il gioco. L'avventura consiste in un gran numero di pannelli statici in cui il giocatore si muove per risolvere enigmi e combattere i dinosauri che attaccano. Gli oggetti possono essere raccolti e il loro utilizzo nel giusto contesto è spesso necessario per passare alla schermata successiva. Altri problemi vengono spesso risolti saltando o interagendo con la principessa.</text>
         <text lang="de">Bermuda Syndrome ist ein Jump-’n’-Run-Spiel, entwickelt von Century Interactive und 1995 von BMG Interactive veröffentlicht. Es ähnelt in Gameplay und Grafik dem Klassiker Flashback von 1992. Der Spieler steuert die Hauptfigur aus der Third-Person-Perspektive in einem Side-Scrolling-Modus. Die Hauptfigur ist Jack Thompson, ein Mitglied einer strategischen Bomberstaffel der US-Luftwaffe im Zweiten Weltkrieg. Während eines Einsatzes über Deutschland wird sein Flugzeug von deutschen Jagdflugzeugen angegriffen und gerät in Brand. Im Absturz öffnet sich aus unerklärlichen Gründen ein Portal, durch das Jack in ein Paralleluniversum oder eine alternative Zeitlinie gelangt. Er landet nicht in der deutschen Landschaft, sondern in einem fremden Dschungel. Am Boden sieht man eine gefesselte junge Frau, die verzweifelt versucht, sich zu befreien, während sich ein gigantischer fleischfressender Dinosaurier nähert. Jacks Flugzeug trifft das Ungeheuer und enthauptet es, wodurch die Frau vor dem Tod bewahrt wird. Im letzten Moment springt Jack ab und hängt zu Beginn des Spiels mit einem Stiefelmesser als einziger Waffe an seinem Fallschirm von einem Baum. Nachdem er die Frau befreit hat, stellt sich heraus, dass sie eine Prinzessin ist, die von ihrem Vater geopfert werden sollte. Sie wird Jacks Begleiterin im gesamten Spiel. Das Abenteuer besteht aus zahlreichen statischen Panels, in denen sich der Spieler bewegt, um Rätsel zu lösen und angreifende Dinosaurier zu bekämpfen. Gegenstände können aufgesammelt werden, und ihre Verwendung im richtigen Kontext ist oft notwendig, um zum nächsten Bildschirm zu gelangen. Andere Probleme lassen sich häufig durch Springen oder die Interaktion mit der Prinzessin lösen.</text>
         <text lang="fr">Bermuda Syndrome est un jeu de plateforme développé par Century Interactive et édité par BMG Interactive en 1995. Son gameplay et son esthétique rappellent le classique Flashback de 1992. Le joueur contrôle le personnage principal, Jack Thompson, membre d'une escadrille de bombardiers stratégiques de l'US Air Force pendant la Seconde Guerre mondiale, en vue à la troisième personne et à défilement horizontal. Lors d'une mission au-dessus de l'Allemagne, son avion est attaqué par des chasseurs allemands et prend feu. Un portail s'ouvre alors que l'appareil s'écrase, le propulsant dans ce qui semble être un univers parallèle ou une réalité alternative. Jack se retrouve non pas au-dessus de la campagne allemande, mais dans une jungle étrange et inconnue. Au sol, une jeune femme, ligotée, tente de se libérer tandis qu'un gigantesque dinosaure carnivore approche. Par chance, l'avion de Jack percute et décapite la créature, sauvant ainsi la femme d'une mort certaine. Au dernier moment, Jack saute en parachute. Au début du jeu, il est suspendu à un arbre, son parachute à la main, armé d'un simple couteau de botte. Après avoir secouru la femme, il découvre qu'il s'agit d'une princesse que son père devait sacrifier. Elle deviendra sa compagne tout au long de l'aventure. Celle-ci se compose de nombreux panneaux fixes où le joueur se déplace pour résoudre des énigmes et combattre des dinosaures. Il peut ramasser des objets, et les utiliser à bon escient est souvent nécessaire pour accéder au niveau suivant. D'autres problèmes se résolvent généralement en sautant ou en interagissant avec la princesse.</text>
         <text lang="es">Bermuda Syndrome es un juego de plataformas desarrollado por Century Interactive y publicado por BMG Interactive en 1995. El juego es similar en jugabilidad y apariencia al clásico Flashback de 1992. El jugador controla al personaje principal desde una perspectiva de desplazamiento lateral en tercera persona. El personaje principal es Jack Thompson, miembro de un escuadrón de bombarderos estratégicos de la fuerza aérea estadounidense durante la Segunda Guerra Mundial. Durante una misión sobre Alemania, su avión es atacado por cazas alemanes y se incendia. De alguna manera, un portal se abre mientras el avión cae y entra en lo que presumiblemente es un universo paralelo o una línea de tiempo alternativa. Jack se encuentra descendiendo no sobre la campiña alemana, sino sobre un extraño y desconocido paisaje selvático. Mientras tanto, en el suelo, vemos a una joven atada, luchando por soltarse mientras se acerca un gigantesco dinosaurio carnívoro. El avión de Jack, afortunadamente, golpea y decapita a la criatura, evitando que la mujer sea devorada. En el último segundo, Jack se lanza en paracaídas y, al principio del juego, cuelga de un árbol en paracaídas, con un cortabotas como única arma. Tras liberar a la mujer, se revela que es una princesa que iba a ser sacrificada por su padre. Se convierte en la compañera de Jack durante todo el juego. La aventura consta de numerosos paneles estáticos en los que el jugador se mueve para resolver puzles y luchar contra dinosaurios que atacan. Se pueden recoger objetos, y a menudo es necesario usarlos en el contexto adecuado para avanzar a la siguiente pantalla. Otros problemas suelen resolverse saltando o interactuando con la princesa.</text>
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>
				<multiLine>false</multiLine>
				<autoScrollDelay>3000</autoScrollDelay>
				<singleLineScroll>true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>

</theme>