<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>V1 was known as Win3xO, however the project has been renamed to fit within the other projects we are releasing. V1 was released in 2015 using MEAGRE as the front end, and it was compatible with eXoDOS v3 which was released around the same time. eXoWin3x has been modified to run in LaunchBox and is compatible with eXoDOS v5. This pack includes 1,138 Windows 3x games. Windows 3x was an "operating environment" that ran on DOS. It preceded Windows 95 which was a proper operating system and did not run on DOS (although it had a DOS mode it could pass over to when needed). While Windows 3.x (the X standing for either 3.0, 3.1, or 3.11) ran on DOS, it was much more capable of running multi media content. As CD-ROMs were just beginning to become main stream at this time, this led to an influx of reference, productivity, educational, and FMV games released for the platform. The focus of the main project is on games & MPC CD-ROMs that were either released in English or are fairly easy to play without a knowledge of their native language. This project is a bit different in scope from eXoDOS in that it extends beyond just games. This is primarily due to the fact that the variety of commercial releases for this platform were much more varied and much less preserved. The software included in eXoWin3x is already setup using DOSBox, with a handful of games relying on VHD's due to their need of true DOS 6.22 files. The launching of games is seamless for the end user however, and no prior knowledge of DOSBox is required.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">La versione 1 era nota come Win3xO, tuttavia il progetto è stato rinominato per essere compatibile con gli altri progetti che stiamo rilasciando. La versione 1 è stata rilasciata nel 2015 utilizzando MEAGRE come interfaccia utente ed era compatibile con eXoDOS v3, rilasciato all'incirca nello stesso periodo. eXoWin3x è stato modificato per funzionare in LaunchBox ed è compatibile con eXoDOS v5. Questo pacchetto include 1.138 giochi per Windows 3x. Windows 3x era un "ambiente operativo" che girava su DOS. Precedette Windows 95, che era un vero e proprio sistema operativo e non girava su DOS (sebbene avesse una modalità DOS a cui poteva passare quando necessario). Mentre Windows 3.x (la X sta per 3.0, 3.1 o 3.11) girava su DOS, era molto più capace di eseguire contenuti multimediali. Poiché i CD-ROM stavano appena iniziando a diffondersi, ciò portò a un'ondata di giochi di riferimento, di produttività, educativi e FMV rilasciati per questa piattaforma. Il progetto principale si concentra su giochi e CD-ROM per MPC pubblicati in inglese o comunque facili da giocare anche senza conoscere la lingua originale. Questo progetto si differenzia da eXoDOS per la sua portata, in quanto va oltre i semplici giochi. Ciò è dovuto principalmente al fatto che la varietà di titoli commerciali per questa piattaforma era molto più ampia e meno conservata. Il software incluso in eXoWin3x è già configurato per utilizzare DOSBox, con alcuni giochi che si basano su file VHD per la necessità di file DOS 6.22 originali. L'avvio dei giochi è comunque immediato per l'utente finale e non è richiesta alcuna conoscenza pregressa di DOSBox.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">La version 1 était connue sous le nom de Win3xO, mais le projet a été renommé pour s'intégrer aux autres projets que nous publions. Sortie en 2015, la version 1 utilisait MEAGRE comme interface et était compatible avec eXoDOS v3, sorti à peu près à la même époque. eXoWin3x a été modifié pour fonctionner sous LaunchBox et est compatible avec eXoDOS v5. Ce pack contient 1 138 jeux Windows 3x. Windows 3x était un environnement d'exploitation fonctionnant sous DOS. Il a précédé Windows 95, un véritable système d'exploitation qui ne fonctionnait pas sous DOS (bien qu'il disposât d'un mode DOS auquel il pouvait basculer en cas de besoin). Si Windows 3.x (le x représentant 3.0, 3.1 ou 3.11) fonctionnait sous DOS, il était bien plus performant pour la lecture de contenu multimédia. Alors que les CD-ROM commençaient tout juste à se démocratiser, une multitude de jeux de référence, de productivité, éducatifs et FMV ont été commercialisés sur cette plateforme. Le projet principal se concentre sur les jeux et les CD-ROM MPC sortis en anglais ou relativement faciles à jouer sans connaître leur langue d'origine. Ce projet diffère quelque peu d'eXoDOS par son ampleur, qui dépasse le simple cadre des jeux. Cela s'explique principalement par la plus grande variété de titres commerciaux disponibles sur cette plateforme, et leur conservation bien moindre. Les logiciels inclus dans eXoWin3x sont déjà configurés avec DOSBox, quelques jeux utilisant des fichiers VHD car ils requièrent des fichiers DOS 6.22 natifs. Le lancement des jeux est cependant transparent pour l'utilisateur final, et aucune connaissance préalable de DOSBox n'est nécessaire.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Version 1 war unter dem Namen Win3xO bekannt, wurde aber umbenannt, um besser zu den anderen veröffentlichten Projekten zu passen. Version 1 erschien 2015 mit MEAGRE als Benutzeroberfläche und war mit eXoDOS v3 kompatibel, das etwa zur gleichen Zeit veröffentlicht wurde. eXoWin3x wurde für die Ausführung in LaunchBox angepasst und ist mit eXoDOS v5 kompatibel. Dieses Paket enthält 1.138 Windows-3x-Spiele. Windows 3x war eine Betriebsumgebung für DOS. Es war der Vorgänger von Windows 95, einem vollwertigen Betriebssystem, das nicht unter DOS lief (obwohl es einen DOS-Modus besaß, in den es bei Bedarf wechseln konnte). Obwohl Windows 3.x (das X steht für 3.0, 3.1 oder 3.11) unter DOS lief, war es deutlich besser für die Wiedergabe von Multimedia-Inhalten geeignet. Da CD-ROMs zu dieser Zeit gerade erst populär wurden, erschienen zahlreiche Nachschlagewerke, Produktivitäts-, Lern- und FMV-Spiele für die Plattform. Der Schwerpunkt dieses Projekts liegt auf Spielen und MPC-CD-ROMs, die entweder auf Englisch veröffentlicht wurden oder auch ohne Englischkenntnisse relativ einfach zu spielen sind. Dieses Projekt unterscheidet sich vom eXoDOS-Projekt insofern, als es über Spiele hinausgeht. Dies liegt vor allem daran, dass die kommerziellen Veröffentlichungen für diese Plattform deutlich vielfältiger und weniger gut erhalten waren. Die in eXoWin3x enthaltene Software ist bereits mit DOSBox eingerichtet, wobei einige Spiele aufgrund der benötigten DOS-6.22-Dateien auf VHDs angewiesen sind. Das Starten der Spiele ist für den Endbenutzer jedoch problemlos, und es sind keine Vorkenntnisse in DOSBox erforderlich.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">V1 se conocía como Win3xO, pero el proyecto se renombró para que encajara con los demás proyectos que estamos publicando. V1 se publicó en 2015 usando MEAGRE como interfaz y era compatible con eXoDOS v3, que se publicó casi al mismo tiempo. eXoWin3x se ha modificado para ejecutarse en LaunchBox y es compatible con eXoDOS v5. Este paquete incluye 1138 juegos de Windows 3x. Windows 3x era un "entorno operativo" que se ejecutaba en DOS. Precedió a Windows 95, que era un sistema operativo propiamente dicho y no se ejecutaba en DOS (aunque tenía un modo DOS al que podía cambiar cuando era necesario). Si bien Windows 3.x (la X representa 3.0, 3.1 o 3.11) se ejecutaba en DOS, era mucho más capaz de ejecutar contenido multimedia. Como los CD-ROM estaban empezando a popularizarse en ese momento, esto dio lugar a una afluencia de juegos de referencia, productividad, educativos y FMV publicados para la plataforma. El objetivo principal del proyecto son los juegos y CD-ROMs para MPC que se lanzaron en inglés o que son relativamente fáciles de jugar sin conocer su idioma original. Este proyecto tiene un alcance ligeramente diferente al de eXoDOS, ya que va más allá de los juegos. Esto se debe principalmente a que la variedad de lanzamientos comerciales para esta plataforma era mucho mayor y se conservaron mucho menos. El software incluido en eXoWin3x ya está configurado con DOSBox, aunque algunos juegos dependen de VHD debido a que requieren archivos DOS 6.22 originales. Sin embargo, el inicio de los juegos es sencillo para el usuario final y no se requieren conocimientos previos de DOSBox.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




