<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>Here is a collection of all the games created by Irem Software Engineering, Inc and featured on this machine.                                                             Irem Software Engineering, Inc. is a Japanese video game development and publishing company and pachinko manufacturer. Its headquarters are located in Chiyoda, Tokyo. The full name of the company using the brand name is Irem Software Engineering. It was founded in 1997 by its parent company Nanao (now Eizo) to take over the development division of the original Irem Corporation, which had exited the video game industry in 1994 to focus on the rental and sale of coin-operated electronic equipment. Irem Corporation was founded in 1974 as IPM and still exists today under the name Apies. Irem is internationally known for three arcade games from the 1980s: Moon Patrol (1982; licensed to Williams Electronics in North America), the first scrolling beat 'em up, Kung-Fu Master (1984), and the scrolling shoot 'em up R-Type (1987). In Japan, Irem achieved great success with games such as Gekibo: Gekisha Boy for the PC Engine and In the Hunt and Undercover Cops for arcades. Since the 2010s, Irem has largely abandoned console game development, focusing on pachinko-based games.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Ecco una raccolta di tutti i giochi creati dall' Irem Software Engineering, Inc e presenti su questa macchina.                           Irem Software Engineering, Inc. e' un'azienda giapponese di sviluppo e pubblicazione di videogiochi e produttrice di pachinko. La sede centrale si trova a Chiyoda, Tokyo. Il nome completo dell'azienda che utilizza il marchio e' Irem Software Engineering. e' stata fondata nel 1997 dalla sua societa' madre Nanao (ora Eizo) con lo scopo di rilevare il reparto di sviluppo della Irem Corporation originale, che aveva abbandonato l'industria dei videogiochi nel 1994 per concentrarsi sul noleggio e la vendita di apparecchiature elettroniche a gettoni. La Irem Corporation fu fondata nel 1974 come IPM ed esiste ancora oggi con il nome di Apies. Irem e' conosciuta a livello internazionale per tre giochi arcade degli anni '80: Moon Patrol (1982; concesso in licenza a Williams Electronics in Nord America), il primo picchiaduro a scorrimento, Kung-Fu Master (1984), e lo sparatutto a scorrimento R-Type (1987). In Giappone, Irem ha riscosso grande successo con giochi come Gekibo: Gekisha Boy per PC Engine e In the Hunt e Undercover Cops per le sale giochi. Dagli anni 2010, Irem ha in gran parte abbandonato lo sviluppo di videogiochi per console, concentrandosi su giochi basati sulle macchine pachinko.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Voici une collection de tous les jeux cre'e's par Irem Software Engineering, Inc et disponibles sur cette machine.                                                             Irem Software Engineering, Inc. est une socie'te' japonaise de de'veloppement et d'e'dition de jeux vide'o, ainsi que fabricant de pachinko. Son sie'ge social se situe a' Chiyoda, a' Tokyo. La socie'te', qui utilise la marque Irem Software Engineering, a e'te' fonde'e en 1997 par sa maison me're Nanao (aujourd'hui Eizo) pour reprendre la division de'veloppement de l'ancienne Irem Corporation, qui s'e'tait retire'e du secteur du jeu vide'o en 1994 pour se concentrer sur la location et la vente de jeux d'arcade. Irem Corporation, fonde'e en 1974 sous le nom d'IPM, existe toujours sous le nom d'Apies. Irem est internationalement connue pour trois jeux d'arcade des anne'es 1980 : Moon Patrol (1982 ; distribue' sous licence par Williams Electronics en Ame'rique du Nord), le premier beat'em up a' de'filement horizontal, Kung-Fu Master (1984), et le shoot'em up a' de'filement horizontal R-Type (1987). Au Japon, Irem a connu un grand succe's avec des jeux tels que Gekibo: Gekisha Boy sur PC Engine et In the Hunt et Undercover Cops sur bornes d'arcade. Depuis les anne'es 2010, Irem a largement abandonne' le de'veloppement de jeux pour consoles, se concentrant sur les jeux de pachinko.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Hier ist eine Sammlung aller von Irem Software Engineering, Inc entwickelten und auf dieser Maschine enthaltenen Spiele.                                                             Irem Software Engineering, Inc. ist ein japanisches Unternehmen für Videospielentwicklung und -veröffentlichung sowie Pachinko-Automaten. Der Hauptsitz befindet sich in Chiyoda, Tokio. Der vollständige Name des Unternehmens, das den Markennamen verwendet, lautet Irem Software Engineering. Es wurde 1997 von seiner Muttergesellschaft Nanao (heute Eizo) gegründet, um die Entwicklungsabteilung der ursprünglichen Irem Corporation zu übernehmen. Diese hatte sich 1994 aus der Videospielbranche zurückgezogen, um sich auf den Verleih und Verkauf von münzbetriebenen elektronischen Geräten zu konzentrieren. Die Irem Corporation wurde 1974 als IPM gegründet und existiert heute noch unter dem Namen Apies. Irem ist international bekannt für drei Arcade-Spiele aus den 1980er-Jahren: Moon Patrol (1982; in Nordamerika an Williams Electronics lizenziert), das erste Scrolling-Beat-'em-up Kung-Fu Master (1984) und das Scrolling-Shoot-'em-up R-Type (1987). In Japan feierte Irem große Erfolge mit Spielen wie Gekibo: Gekisha Boy für den PC Engine und In the Hunt und Undercover Cops für Spielhallen. Seit den 2010er-Jahren hat Irem die Entwicklung von Konsolenspielen weitgehend aufgegeben und konzentriert sich stattdessen auf Pachinko-Spiele.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">Aquí tene'is una recopilación de todos los juegos creados por Irem Software Engineering, Inc e incluidos en esta máquina.                                                             Irem Software Engineering, Inc. es una empresa japonesa de desarrollo y publicación de videojuegos y fabricante de pachinko. Su sede central se encuentra en Chiyoda, Tokio. El nombre completo de la empresa que utiliza la marca es Irem Software Engineering. Fue fundada en 1997 por su empresa matriz Nanao (ahora Eizo) para hacerse cargo de la división de desarrollo de la Irem Corporation original, que había abandonado la industria de los videojuegos en 1994 para centrarse en el alquiler y la venta de equipos electrónicos que funcionan con monedas. Irem Corporation fue fundada en 1974 como IPM y aún existe hoy bajo el nombre de Apies. Irem es conocida internacionalmente por tres juegos arcade de la de'cada de 1980: Moon Patrol (1982; con licencia de Williams Electronics en Norteame'rica), el primer juego de lucha de desplazamiento lateral, Kung-Fu Master (1984), y el juego de disparos de desplazamiento lateral R-Type (1987). En Japón, Irem alcanzó un gran e'xito con juegos como Gekibo: Gekisha Boy para PC Engine e In the Hunt y Undercover Cops para máquinas recreativas. Desde la de'cada de 2010, Irem ha abandonado en gran medida el desarrollo de videojuegos para consolas, centrándose en juegos basados ​​en pachinko.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>





