<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>Virtual reality (VR) is a technologically created world that is transmitted to a person through their senses: sight, hearing, touch and others. Virtual reality simulates both the impact and reactions to the impact. To create a convincing set of reality sensations, computer synthesis of virtual reality properties and reactions is performed in real time. Virtual reality objects typically behave closely to the behavior of similar material reality objects. The user can influence these objects in accordance with the real laws of physics (gravity, water properties, collision with objects, reflection, etc.). However, often for entertainment purposes, users of virtual worlds are allowed to do more than is possible in real life (for example: fly, create any objects, etc.). Virtual reality should not be confused with augmented reality (AR) or mixed reality (MR). Their fundamental difference is that virtual reality constructs a new artificial world, while augmented reality only introduces some artificial elements into the perception of the real world.</text>
			<text lang="it">La realta' virtuale (VR) e' un mondo creato tecnologicamente che viene trasmesso a una persona attraverso i suoi sensi: vista, udito, tatto e altri. La realta' virtuale simula sia l'impatto che le reazioni all'impatto. Per creare un insieme convincente di sensazioni di realta', la sintesi computerizzata delle proprieta' e delle reazioni della realta' virtuale viene eseguita in tempo reale. Gli oggetti della realta' virtuale si comportano in genere in modo molto simile a quello di oggetti simili della realta' materiale. L'utente puo' influenzare questi oggetti secondo le reali leggi della fisica (gravita', proprieta' dell'acqua, collisione con gli oggetti, riflessione, ecc.) Tuttavia, spesso a scopo di intrattenimento, agli utenti dei mondi virtuali e' consentito fare piU' di quanto sia possibile nella vita reale (ad esempio: volare, creare qualsiasi oggetto, ecc.). La realta' virtuale non deve essere confusa con la realta' aumentata (AR) o la realta' mista (MR). La loro differenza fondamentale e' che la realta' virtuale costruisce un nuovo mondo artificiale, mentre la realta' aumentata introduce solo alcuni elementi artificiali nella percezione del mondo reale.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La re'alite' virtuelle (VR) est un monde cre'e' par la technologie qui est transmis a' une personne par ses sens : la vue, l'ouïe, le toucher et d'autres. La re'alite' virtuelle simule a' la fois l'impact et les re'actions a' l'impact. Pour cre'er un ensemble convaincant de sensations re'elles, la synthe'se informatique des proprie'te's et des re'actions de la re'alite' virtuelle est effectue'e en temps re'el. Le comportement des objets de re'alite' virtuelle est ge'ne'ralement proche de celui d'objets de re'alite' mate'rielle similaires. L'utilisateur peut influencer ces objets conforme'ment aux ve'ritables lois de la physique (gravite', proprie'te's de l'eau, collision avec des objets, re'flexion, etc.) Cependant, souvent a' des fins de divertissement, les utilisateurs des mondes virtuels sont autorise's a' faire plus que ce qui est possible dans la vie re'elle (par exemple : voler, cre'er n'importe quel objet, etc.) La re'alite' virtuelle ne doit pas être confondue avec la re'alite' augmente'e (AR) ou la re'alite' mixte (MR). Leur diffe'rence fondamentale re'side dans le fait que la re'alite' virtuelle construit un nouveau monde artificiel, alors que la re'alite' augmente'e ne fait qu'introduire certains e'le'ments artificiels dans la perception du monde re'el.</text>
			<text lang="de">Virtuelle Realität (VR) ist eine technologisch geschaffene Welt, die dem Menschen durch seine Sinne vermittelt wird: Sehen, Hören, Tasten und andere. Die virtuelle Realität simuliert sowohl den Aufprall als auch die Reaktionen auf den Aufprall. Um einen überzeugenden Realitätseindruck zu erzeugen, werden die Eigenschaften und Reaktionen in der virtuellen Realität in Echtzeit am Computer synthetisiert. Objekte der virtuellen Realität verhalten sich in der Regel ähnlich wie ähnliche Objekte der materiellen Realität. Der Benutzer kann diese Objekte entsprechend den realen physikalischen Gesetzen beeinflussen (Schwerkraft, Wassereigenschaften, Zusammenstoß mit Objekten, Reflexion usw.). Zu Unterhaltungszwecken ist es den Nutzern virtueller Welten jedoch oft erlaubt, mehr zu tun, als im wirklichen Leben möglich ist (z. B. fliegen, beliebige Objekte erschaffen usw.). Die virtuelle Realität sollte nicht mit der erweiterten Realität (AR) oder der gemischten Realität (MR) verwechselt werden. Ihr grundlegender Unterschied besteht darin, dass die virtuelle Realität eine neue künstliche Welt erschafft, während die erweiterte Realität nur einige künstliche Elemente in die Wahrnehmung der realen Welt einführt.</text>
			<text lang="es">La realidad virtual (VR) es un mundo creado tecnológicamente que se transmite a una persona a trave's de sus sentidos: vista, oído, tacto y otros. La realidad virtual simula tanto el impacto como las reacciones al mismo. Para crear un conjunto convincente de sensaciones de realidad, la síntesis informática de las propiedades y reacciones de la realidad virtual se realiza en tiempo real. Los objetos de realidad virtual suelen comportarse de forma muy similar a los objetos de realidad material similares. El usuario puede influir en estos objetos de acuerdo con las leyes reales de la física (gravedad, propiedades del agua, colisión con objetos, reflexión, etc.). Sin embargo, a menudo con fines de entretenimiento, a los usuarios de mundos virtuales se les permite hacer más de lo que es posible en la vida real (por ejemplo: volar, crear cualquier objeto, etc.). La realidad virtual no debe confundirse con la realidad aumentada (AR) o la realidad mixta (MR). Su diferencia fundamental es que la realidad virtual construye un nuevo mundo artificial, mientras que la realidad aumentada sólo introduce algunos elementos artificiales en la percepción del mundo real.</text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>
				<multiLine>false</multiLine>
				<autoScrollDelay>3000</autoScrollDelay>
				<singleLineScroll>true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>

