<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>CD-i (Compact Disc Interactive) is an interactive multimedia CD player manufactured by Royal Phillips Electronics N.V. The first Philips CD-i player was released in 1991, priced at around $700 at the time. The device played CD-i, CD-Audio, CD+G, karaoke CD and Video CD. For VCD playback, it was necessary to purchase a special video card to provide the player with MPEG-1 codecs. The player was produced in a dozen different versions, but they were all compatible with each other.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">CD-i (Compact Disc Interactive) es un reproductor de CD multimedia interactivo fabricado por Royal Phillips Electronics N.V. El primer reproductor CD-i de Philips salió a la venta en 1991, con un precio de unos 700 dólares de la e'poca. El aparato reproducía CD-i, CD-Audio, CD+G, CD karaoke y Vídeo CD. Para la reproducción de VCD, era necesario adquirir una tarjeta de vídeo especial para dotar al reproductor de códecs MPEG-1. El reproductor se fabricó en una docena de versiones diferentes, pero todas eran compatibles entre sí.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">CD-i (Compact Disc Interactive) ist ein interaktiver Multimedia-CD-Player, der von Royal Phillips Electronics N.V. hergestellt wird. Der erste Philips CD-i-Player kam 1991 auf den Markt und kostete damals etwa 700 Dollar. Das Gerät spielte CD-i, CD-Audio, CD+G, Karaoke-CD und Video-CD ab. Für die Wiedergabe von VCDs war der Kauf einer speziellen Videokarte erforderlich, um den Player mit MPEG-1-Codecs auszustatten. Der Player wurde in einem Dutzend verschiedener Versionen hergestellt, die jedoch alle miteinander kompatibel waren.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">CD-i (Compact Disc Interactive) est un lecteur de CD multime'dia interactif fabrique' par Royal Phillips Electronics N.V. Le premier lecteur CD-i de Philips est sorti en 1991, a' un prix d'environ 700 dollars a' l'e'poque. L'appareil lisait les CD-i, les CD-Audio, les CD+G, les CD karaoke' et les CD vide'o. Pour la lecture des VCD, il e'tait ne'cessaire d'acheter une carte vide'o spe'ciale pour doter le lecteur des codecs MPEG-1. Le lecteur a e'te' produit dans une douzaine de versions diffe'rentes, mais elles e'taient toutes compatibles entre elles.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">CD-i (Compact Disc Interactive) e' stato un lettore CD multimediale interattivo prodotto da Royal Phillips Electronics N.V. Il primo lettore Philips CD-i fu commercializzato nel 1991, al prezzo di circa 700 dollari. Il dispositivo riproduceva CD-i, CD-Audio, CD+G, CD karaoke e Video CD. Per la riproduzione di VCD, era necessario acquistare una scheda video speciale per dotare il lettore di codec MPEG-1. Il lettore e' stato prodotto in una dozzina di versioni diverse, ma tutte compatibili tra loro.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




