<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>Here is a collection of all the games created by Comad and featured on this machine.                                                             Founded in 1980, Ko Bong was the first company in Korea to be granted permission for the manufacturing of electromechanical amusement machines, which it started exporting to Lybia and Saudi Arabia in 1982. Ko Bong was one of six companies that joined Philko in forming the Korean Computer Graphics Research Association in 1987. Ko Bong first made video game news in 1989, but not in a good way: The company was being sued by Victor - not the Japanese company, but a Korean namesake led by none other than Kim Kaphwan, who later became chairman of Viccom and the Korea Computer Game Industrial Association - for producing, selling and exporting illegal copies of the SNK game Mechanized Attack since April of that year, only one month after it was originally released. Perhaps to wash itself of that stain, the company changed its name to Comad in March 1990 and started creating original titles - at least for a few years, before reverting to hacking other games. Comad is mostly known in the West for many raunchy variants on the game Qix. According to Jang In'gyeong, graphic designer for S.S. Mission, Gulf War II and Fantasia, these were made specifically for overseas markets and not released in Korea, where they wouldn't get past the rating board.6 Therefore, several of Comad's games have different versions for Korean and overseas markets. Comad contined producing video games at least until 2009, mostly for the overseas market, but it is uncertain if and where these were released. Mechanical amusement remains the company's main business.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Ecco una raccolta di tutti i giochi creati dalla Sega e presenti su questa macchina.                                                             Fondata nel 1980, Ko Bong e' stata la prima azienda in Corea a ottenere l'autorizzazione per la produzione di macchine da gioco elettromeccaniche, che inizio' a esportare in Libia e Arabia Saudita nel 1982. Ko Bong fu una delle sei aziende che, insieme a Philko, fondarono la Korean Computer Graphics Research Association nel 1987. Ko Bong fece parlare di se' nel mondo dei videogiochi per la prima volta nel 1989, ma non in senso positivo: l'azienda fu citata in giudizio da Victor - non la societa' giapponese, bensi' un'omonima azienda coreana guidata nientemeno che da Kim Kaphwan, che in seguito divenne presidente di Viccom e della Korea Computer Game Industrial Association - per aver prodotto, venduto ed esportato copie illegali del gioco SNK Mechanized Attack a partire dall'aprile di quell'anno, solo un mese dopo la sua uscita originale. Forse per ripulirsi da questa macchia, l'azienda cambio' nome in Comad nel marzo del 1990 e inizio' a creare titoli originali - almeno per alcuni anni, prima di tornare a modificare altri giochi. Comad e' nota in Occidente soprattutto per le numerose varianti a sfondo erotico del gioco Qix. Secondo Jang In'gyeong, graphic designer di S.S. Mission, Gulf War II e Fantasia, questi giochi furono realizzati specificamente per i mercati esteri e non distribuiti in Corea, dove non avrebbero superato il vaglio della commissione di classificazione.⁶ Pertanto, diversi giochi di Comad hanno versioni diverse per il mercato coreano e per quello estero. Comad ha continuato a produrre videogiochi almeno fino al 2009, principalmente per il mercato estero, ma non e' certo se e dove questi siano stati distribuiti. I giochi meccanici rimangono l'attivita' principale dell'azienda.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Voici une collection de tous les jeux cre'e's par Sega et disponibles sur cette machine.                                                             Fonde'e en 1980, Ko Bong fut la premie're entreprise core'enne a' obtenir l'autorisation de fabriquer des machines de divertissement e'lectrome'caniques, qu'elle commença a' exporter vers la Libye et l'Arabie saoudite en 1982. Ko Bong figurait parmi les six entreprises qui, avec Philko, fonde'rent l'Association core'enne de recherche en infographie en 1987. Ko Bong fit parler d'elle pour la premie're fois dans le monde du jeu vide'o en 1989, mais pas pour de bonnes raisons : l'entreprise e'tait poursuivie en justice par Victor – non pas la socie'te' japonaise, mais son homonyme core'en, dirige' par nul autre que Kim Kaphwan, qui devint plus tard pre'sident de Viccom et de l'Association core'enne de l'industrie du jeu vide'o – pour avoir produit, vendu et exporte' des copies ille'gales du jeu SNK Mechanized Attack depuis avril de cette anne'e-la', soit un mois seulement apre's sa sortie originale. Afin de se disculper, l'entreprise changea de nom pour devenir Comad en mars 1990 et commença a' cre'er des titres originaux – du moins pendant quelques anne'es, avant de se remettre au piratage de jeux existants. Comad est surtout connu en Occident pour ses nombreuses variantes grivoises du jeu Qix. Selon Jang In'gyeong, graphiste des jeux S.S. Mission, Gulf War II et Fantasia, ces titres ont e'te' conçus spe'cifiquement pour les marche's e'trangers et n'ont pas e'te' commercialise's en Core'e, oU' ils n'auraient pas obtenu l'autorisation de classification.⁶ Par conse'quent, plusieurs jeux de Comad existent en diffe'rentes versions pour les marche's core'en et international. Comad a continue' a' produire des jeux vide'o au moins jusqu'en 2009, principalement pour l'exportation, mais on ignore s'ils ont e'te' commercialise's et, le cas e'che'ant, oU'. Les jeux d'arcade restent l'activite' principale de l'entreprise.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Hier ist eine Sammlung aller von Sega entwickelten und auf dieser Maschine enthaltenen Spiele.                                                             Ko Bong wurde 1980 gegründet und war das erste koreanische Unternehmen, dem die Genehmigung zur Herstellung elektromechanischer Unterhaltungsautomaten erteilt wurde. Ab 1982 exportierte das Unternehmen diese nach Libyen und Saudi-Arabien. Ko Bong war eines von sechs Unternehmen, die sich 1987 mit Philko zur Koreanischen Gesellschaft für Computergrafikforschung zusammenschlossen. 1989 geriet Ko Bong erstmals in die Schlagzeilen der Videospielbranche – allerdings nicht im positiven Sinne: Das Unternehmen wurde von Victor verklagt – nicht von dem japanischen Unternehmen, sondern von einem koreanischen Namensvetter unter der Leitung von Kim Kaphwan, der später Vorsitzender von Viccom und der Koreanischen Computerspiel-Industrievereinigung wurde. Grund dafür war die Produktion, der Verkauf und der Export illegaler Kopien des SNK-Spiels „Mechanized Attack“ seit April desselben Jahres, nur einen Monat nach dessen Veröffentlichung. Um diesen Makel loszuwerden, benannte sich das Unternehmen im März 1990 in Comad um und begann – zumindest für einige Jahre – eigene Spiele zu entwickeln, bevor es wieder auf das Hacken anderer Spiele zurückgriff. Comad ist im Westen vor allem für seine freizügigen Varianten des Spiels Qix bekannt. Laut Jang In'gyeong, Grafikdesignerin von S.S. Mission, Gulf War II und Fantasia, wurden diese speziell für den internationalen Markt entwickelt und nicht in Korea veröffentlicht, da sie dort die Altersfreigabe nicht erhalten hätten.<sup>6</sup> Daher existieren von einigen Comad-Spielen unterschiedliche Versionen für den koreanischen und den internationalen Markt. Comad produzierte mindestens bis 2009 Videospiele, hauptsächlich für den internationalen Markt, es ist jedoch unklar, ob und wo diese veröffentlicht wurden. Mechanische Unterhaltungsautomaten bleiben das Kerngeschäft des Unternehmens.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">Aquí tene'is una recopilación de todos los juegos creados por Sega e incluidos en esta máquina.                                                             Fundada en 1980, Ko Bong fue la primera empresa en Corea en obtener permiso para la fabricación de máquinas recreativas electromecánicas, que comenzó a exportar a Libia y Arabia Saudita en 1982. Ko Bong fue una de las seis empresas que se unieron a Philko para formar la Asociación Coreana de Investigación en Gráficos por Computadora en 1987. Ko Bong apareció por primera vez en las noticias de videojuegos en 1989, pero no de forma positiva: la empresa fue demandada por Victor (no la empresa japonesa, sino una empresa coreana homónima dirigida por Kim Kaphwan, quien más tarde se convertiría en presidente de Viccom y de la Asociación Coreana de la Industria de los Videojuegos) por producir, vender y exportar copias ilegales del juego Mechanized Attack de SNK desde abril de ese año, solo un mes despue's de su lanzamiento original. Quizás para limpiar su imagen, la empresa cambió su nombre a Comad en marzo de 1990 y comenzó a crear títulos originales, al menos durante algunos años, antes de volver a piratear otros juegos. Comad es conocida principalmente en Occidente por sus numerosas variantes subidas de tono del juego Qix. Según Jang In'gyeong, diseñador gráfico de S.S. Mission, Gulf War II y Fantasia, estos juegos se crearon específicamente para mercados extranjeros y no se lanzaron en Corea, donde no habrían superado la clasificación por edades.⁶ Por lo tanto, varios juegos de Comad tienen versiones diferentes para los mercados coreano y extranjero. Comad continuó produciendo videojuegos al menos hasta 2009, principalmente para el mercado extranjero, pero se desconoce si se lanzaron y dónde. El entretenimiento mecánico sigue siendo el negocio principal de la compañía.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>





