<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>Here is a collection of all the games created by Cinematronics and featured on this machine. - Cinematronics was an American company that produced arcade video games; in particular, it was the first to produce titles using vector graphics, and introduced the first video games on laserdisc. -<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Ecco una raccolta di tutti i giochi creati dalla Cinematronics e presenti su questa macchina. - Cinematronics è stata un'azienda statunitense produttrice di videogiochi arcade; in particolare ha per prima prodotto titoli che utilizzano la grafica vettoriale, e ha introdotto i primi videogiochi su laserdisc. -<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Voici une collection de tous les jeux créés par Cinematronics et disponibles sur cette machine. - Cinematronics était une société américaine qui produisait des jeux vidéo d'arcade ; elle fut notamment la première à produire des titres utilisant des graphismes vectoriels et à introduire les premiers jeux vidéo sur laserdisc. -<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Hier ist eine Sammlung aller von Cinematronics entwickelten und auf dieser Maschine enthaltenen Spiele. - Cinematronics war ein amerikanisches Unternehmen, das Arcade-Videospiele herstellte; insbesondere war es das erste, das Titel mit Vektorgrafiken produzierte und die ersten Videospiele auf Laserdisc einführte. -<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">Aquí tenéis una recopilación de todos los juegos creados por Cinematronics e incluidos en esta máquina. - Cinematronics era una empresa estadounidense que producía videojuegos arcade; en particular, fue la primera en producir títulos utilizando gráficos vectoriales e introdujo los primeros videojuegos en laserdisc. -<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




