<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>Here is a collection of all the games created by Nintendo and featured on this machine.                                                             Nintendo Co. Ltd. (任天堂株式会社, Nintendō kabushiki-gaisha) is a Japanese company specializing in the production of video games and game consoles. Considered one of the largest companies in Japan, Nintendo was founded on September 23, 1889, by Yamauchi Fusajirō as a manufacturer and distributor of playing cards. Throughout its history, it has produced several mechanical and electronic games, entering the world of video games in the 1970s as a manufacturer of arcade games. In 1977, Nintendo successfully launched its own line of home consoles called the Color TV Game. Since the 1980s, Nintendo has produced numerous tabletop and handheld consoles, which have sold over 750 million units. Consoles that have sold more than 10 million units include the Nintendo Entertainment System, the Super Nintendo Entertainment System, the Nintendo 64, the Nintendo GameCube, the Wii, the Nintendo Switch, the Game Boy, the Game Boy Advance, the Nintendo DS, and the Nintendo 3DS. The company also developed the Game & Watch series and the Virtual Boy. Nintendo has published over five hundred games, often collaborating with other companies on development. In thirty years, it has sold over 577 million consoles and 3.5 billion copies of directly developed video games. On September 23, 2019, Nintendo celebrated its 130th anniversary. The company's CEO and president is Shuntaro Furukawa, while Nintendo's mascot is Mario, a character created in 1981 by Shigeru Miyamoto for the arcade game Donkey Kong. Nintendo has been listed on the Tokyo Stock Exchange since 1983.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Ecco una raccolta di tutti i giochi creati dalla Nintendo e presenti su questa macchina.                                                             Nintendo Co. Ltd. (任天堂株式会社?, Nintendō kabushiki-gaisha) e' un'azienda giapponese specializzata nella produzione di videogiochi e console. Considerata come una delle piU' grandi compagnie del Giappone, Nintendo fu fondata il 23 settembre 1889 da Yamauchi Fusajirō come produttore e distributore di carte da gioco. Nel corso della sua storia ha realizzato diversi giochi meccanici ed elettronici, entrando poi nel mondo dei videogiochi negli anni settanta, come produttore di giochi arcade. Nel 1977 Nintendo lancio' con successo la propria linea di console domestiche denominata Color TV Game. Dagli anni ottanta Nintendo ha prodotto numerose console da tavolo e portatili che hanno venduto oltre 750 milioni di unita'. Tra le console che hanno venduto piU' di 10 milioni figurano il Nintendo Entertainment System, il Super Nintendo Entertainment System, il Nintendo 64, il Nintendo GameCube, il Wii, il Nintendo Switch, il Game Boy, il Game Boy Advance, il Nintendo DS e il Nintendo 3DS. L'azienda ha realizzato inoltre la serie Game & Watch e il Virtual Boy. Nintendo ha pubblicato oltre cinquecento giochi, spesso avvalendosi della collaborazione di altre aziende per quanto riguarda lo sviluppo. In trent'anni ha venduto oltre 577 milioni di console e 3,5 miliardi di copie dei videogiochi direttamente sviluppati. Il 23 settembre 2019 Nintendo ha festeggiato il suo 130º anno di vita. L'amministratore delegato e presidente della societa' e' Shuntaro Furukawa, mentre la mascotte di Nintendo e' Mario, personaggio creato nel 1981 da Shigeru Miyamoto per il videogioco arcade Donkey Kong. Nintendo e' quotata sulla borsa di Tokyo dal 1983.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Voici une collection de tous les jeux cre'e's par Nintendo et disponibles sur cette machine.                                                             Nintendo Co., Ltd. (任天堂株式会社, Nintendō kabushiki-gaisha) est une entreprise japonaise spe'cialise'e dans la production de jeux vide'o et de consoles de jeux. Conside're'e comme l'une des plus grandes entreprises du Japon, Nintendo a e'te' fonde'e le 23 septembre 1889 par Yamauchi Fusajirō en tant que fabricant et distributeur de cartes a' jouer. Au cours de son histoire, elle a produit de nombreux jeux me'caniques et e'lectroniques, et a fait son entre'e dans le monde du jeu vide'o dans les anne'es 1970 en tant que fabricant de jeux d'arcade. En 1977, Nintendo a lance' avec succe's sa propre gamme de consoles de salon, la Color TV Game. Depuis les anne'es 1980, Nintendo a produit de nombreuses consoles de salon et portables, qui se sont vendues a' plus de 750 millions d'exemplaires. Parmi les consoles ayant de'passe' les 10 millions d'exemplaires vendus figurent la Nintendo Entertainment System (NES), la Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES), la Nintendo 64, la Nintendo GameCube, la Wii, la Nintendo Switch, la Game Boy, la Game Boy Advance, la Nintendo DS et la Nintendo 3DS. La socie'te' a e'galement de'veloppe' les se'ries Game & Watch et Virtual Boy. Nintendo a e'dite' plus de cinq cents jeux, souvent en collaboration avec d'autres entreprises pour leur de'veloppement. En trente ans, elle a vendu plus de 577 millions de consoles et 3,5 milliards d'exemplaires de jeux vide'o de'veloppe's en interne. Le 23 septembre 2019, Nintendo a ce'le'bre' son 130e anniversaire. Son PDG est Shuntaro Furukawa, et sa mascotte est Mario, un personnage cre'e' en 1981 par Shigeru Miyamoto pour le jeu d'arcade Donkey Kong. Nintendo est cote'e a' la Bourse de Tokyo depuis 1983.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Hier ist eine Sammlung aller von Nintendo entwickelten und auf dieser Maschine enthaltenen Spiele.                                                            Nintendo Co. Ltd. (任天堂株式会社, Nintendō kabushiki-gaisha) ist ein japanisches Unternehmen, das sich auf die Produktion von Videospielen und Spielkonsolen spezialisiert hat. Als eines der größten Unternehmen Japans wurde Nintendo am 23. September 1889 von Yamauchi Fusajirō als Hersteller und Vertreiber von Spielkarten gegründet. Im Laufe seiner Geschichte produzierte das Unternehmen zahlreiche mechanische und elektronische Spiele und stieg in den 1970er-Jahren als Hersteller von Arcade-Spielen in die Welt der Videospiele ein. 1977 brachte Nintendo mit der Color TV Game erfolgreich seine eigene Heimkonsolenreihe auf den Markt. Seit den 1980er-Jahren hat Nintendo zahlreiche Tisch- und Handheld-Konsolen produziert, von denen sich über 750 Millionen Einheiten verkauft haben. Zu den Konsolen, die sich über 10 Millionen Mal verkauft haben, gehören das Nintendo Entertainment System (NES), das Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES), der Nintendo 64, der Nintendo GameCube, die Wii, die Nintendo Switch, der Game Boy, der Game Boy Advance, der Nintendo DS und der Nintendo 3DS. Das Unternehmen entwickelte außerdem die Game & Watch-Serie und den Virtual Boy. Nintendo hat über 500 Spiele veröffentlicht und dabei häufig mit anderen Unternehmen zusammengearbeitet. In 30 Jahren verkaufte das Unternehmen über 577 Millionen Konsolen und 3,5 Milliarden Exemplare von direkt entwickelten Videospielen. Am 23. September 2019 feierte Nintendo sein 130-jähriges Bestehen. CEO und Präsident des Unternehmens ist Shuntaro Furukawa, das Maskottchen ist Mario, eine Figur, die 1981 von Shigeru Miyamoto für das Arcade-Spiel Donkey Kong erschaffen wurde. Nintendo ist seit 1983 an der Tokioter Börse notiert.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">Aquí tene'is una recopilación de todos los juegos creados por Nintendo e incluidos en esta máquina.                                                             Nintendo Co. Ltd. (任天堂株式会社, Nintendō kabushiki-gaisha) es una empresa japonesa especializada en la producción de videojuegos y consolas. Considerada una de las mayores empresas de Japón, Nintendo fue fundada el 23 de septiembre de 1889 por Yamauchi Fusajirō como fabricante y distribuidor de naipes. A lo largo de su historia, ha producido diversos juegos mecánicos y electrónicos, incursionando en el mundo de los videojuegos en la de'cada de 1970 como fabricante de máquinas recreativas. En 1977, Nintendo lanzó con e'xito su propia línea de consolas dome'sticas, la Color TV Game. Desde la de'cada de 1980, Nintendo ha producido numerosas consolas de sobremesa y portátiles, de las cuales se han vendido más de 750 millones de unidades. Las consolas que han vendido más de 10 millones de unidades incluyen la Nintendo Entertainment System, la Super Nintendo Entertainment System, la Nintendo 64, la Nintendo GameCube, la Wii, la Nintendo Switch, la Game Boy, la Game Boy Advance, la Nintendo DS y la Nintendo 3DS. La compañía tambie'n desarrolló la serie Game & Watch y la Virtual Boy. Nintendo ha publicado más de quinientos juegos, a menudo colaborando con otras compañías en su desarrollo. En treinta años, ha vendido más de 577 millones de consolas y 3.500 millones de copias de videojuegos desarrollados directamente. El 23 de septiembre de 2019, Nintendo celebró su 130 aniversario. El director ejecutivo y presidente de la compañía es Shuntaro Furukawa, mientras que la mascota de Nintendo es Mario, un personaje creado en 1981 por Shigeru Miyamoto para el juego arcade Donkey Kong. Nintendo cotiza en la Bolsa de Valores de Tokio desde 1983.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>





