<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>

	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <pos>0.95 0.8</pos>
         <origin>1 0</origin>
         <size>0.90 0.1</size>
         <backgroundColor>00000000</backgroundColor>
         <color>F5F5F5</color>
         <fontPath>${themePath}/_inc/fonts/SF Slapstick Comic Bold.ttf</fontPath>
         <fontSize>0.055</fontSize>
         <text>The Epoch Game Pocket Computer (Japanese: ゲームポケコン, Hepburn: Gēmupokekon) is a second-generation handheld game console released by Epoch Co. in Japan in 1984 for 12,800 Japanese yen. It is also known as Pokekon. The system was a commercial failure in Japan,[3] and as a result, only 7 games were made for it. A puzzle game and a paint program were built into the system. It was powered by 4 AA batteries, and screen's contrast could be adjusted by the user. Input and output controls included four buttons, an 8-way joypad, a contrast dial, and a sound on-off switch.</text>
         <text lang="it">L'Epoch Game Pocket Computer (giapponese: ゲームポケコン, Hepburn: Gēmupokekon) è una console portatile di seconda generazione distribuita dalla Epoch Co. in Giappone nel 1984 al prezzo di 12.800 yen giapponesi. È anche noto come Pokekon. Il sistema fu un fallimento commerciale in Giappone,[3] e di conseguenza, furono realizzati solo 7 giochi per esso. Un gioco di puzzle e un programma di disegno erano integrati nel sistema. Era alimentato da 4 batterie AA e il contrasto dello schermo poteva essere regolato dall'utente. I controlli di input e output includevano quattro pulsanti, un joypad a 8 direzioni, una manopola per il contrasto e un interruttore per l'attivazione e la disattivazione del suono.</text>
         <text lang="de">Der Epoch Game Pocket Computer (japanisch: ゲームポケコン, Hepburn: Gēmupokekon) ist eine tragbare Spielkonsole der zweiten Generation, die 1984 von Epoch Co. in Japan für 12.800 Yen veröffentlicht wurde. Sie ist auch unter dem Namen Pokekon bekannt. Das System war in Japan ein kommerzieller Misserfolg[3], weshalb nur sieben Spiele dafür entwickelt wurden. Ein Puzzlespiel und ein Malprogramm waren vorinstalliert. Die Konsole wurde mit vier AA-Batterien betrieben, und der Bildschirmkontrast konnte vom Benutzer angepasst werden. Zur Bedienung gehörten vier Tasten, ein 8-Wege-Joypad, ein Kontrastregler und ein Ton-Ein-/Ausschalter.</text>
         <text lang="fr">L'Epoch Game Pocket Computer (en japonais : ゲームポケコン, Hepburn : Gēmupokekon) est une console de jeux portable de deuxième génération, commercialisée par Epoch Co. au Japon en 1984 au prix de 12 800 yens. Également connue sous le nom de Pokekon, elle fut un échec commercial au Japon[3], et seuls sept jeux furent développés pour cette console. Un jeu de puzzle et un logiciel de dessin étaient intégrés. Alimentée par quatre piles AA, elle offrait un contraste d'écran réglable. Ses commandes comprenaient quatre boutons, une croix directionnelle à huit directions, une molette de réglage du contraste et un interrupteur pour activer/désactiver le son.</text>
         <text lang="es">La Epoch Game Pocket Computer (en japonés: ゲームポケコン, Hepburn: Gēmupokekon) es una consola portátil de segunda generación lanzada por Epoch Co. en Japón en 1984 por 12.800 yenes. También se conoce como Pokekon. El sistema fue un fracaso comercial en Japón[3], por lo que solo se crearon siete juegos. El sistema incluía un juego de rompecabezas y un programa de dibujo. Funcionaba con cuatro pilas AA y el contraste de la pantalla era ajustable. Los controles de entrada y salida incluían cuatro botones, un joystick de 8 direcciones, un dial de contraste y un interruptor de sonido.</text>
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>
				<multiLine>false</multiLine>
				<autoScrollDelay>3000</autoScrollDelay>
				<singleLineScroll>true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>

</theme>