<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>Dinothawr is a block pushing puzzle game on slippery surfaces. Our hero is a dinosaur whose friends are trapped in ice. Through puzzles it is your task to free the dinos from their ice prison. The Dinothawr core has been authored by - Themaister (programming, music, some level design) - Runar Heyer (art, level design, some code)<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">Dinothawr es un juego de puzzle de empujar bloques sobre superficies resbaladizas. Nuestro he'roe es un dinosaurio cuyos amigos están atrapados en el hielo. A trave's de rompecabezas es tu tarea liberar a los dinos de su prisión de hielo. El núcleo de Dinothawr ha sido creado por - Themaister (programación, música, algo de diseño de niveles) - Runar Heyer (arte, diseño de niveles, algo de código)<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Dinothawr ist ein Blockschiebe-Puzzlespiel auf rutschigen Oberflächen. Unser Held ist ein Dinosaurier, dessen Freunde im Eis gefangen sind. Durch Puzzles ist es deine Aufgabe, die Dinosaurier aus ihrem Eisgefängnis zu befreien. Der Dinothawr-Kern wurde verfasst von - Themaister (Programmierung, Musik, etwas Leveldesign) - Runar Heyer (Kunst, Leveldesign, etwas Code)<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Dinothawr est un jeu de puzzle qui consiste a' pousser des blocs sur des surfaces glissantes. Notre he'ros est un dinosaure dont les amis sont prisonniers de la glace. a' l'aide de puzzles, vous devez libe'rer les dinosaures de leur prison de glace. Le noyau de Dinothawr a e'te' e'crit par - Themaister (programmation, musique, conception de certains niveaux) - Runar Heyer (art, level design, un peu de code)<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Dinothawr e' un gioco di puzzle a spinta di blocchi su superfici scivolose. Il nostro eroe e' un dinosauro i cui amici sono intrappolati nel ghiaccio. Attraverso dei rompicapi, il nostro compito e' quello di liberare i dinosauri dalla loro prigione di ghiaccio. Il nucleo di Dinothawr e' stato realizzato da - Themaister (programmazione, musica, progettazione di alcuni livelli) - Runar Heyer (arte, progettazione dei livelli, parte del codice)<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




