<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>The PC Engine SuperGrafx (PCエンジンスーパーグラフィックス, Pī Shī Enjin SūpāGurafikkusu), also known as simply the SuperGrafx, is a fourth-generation home video game console manufactured by NEC Home Electronics and released in Japan and France in 1989. It is the successor system to the PC Engine, released two years prior. Originally known as the PC Engine 2 during production stages, it was purported as a true 16-bit home console, featuring improved graphics and audio capabilities over its predecessor. The console was rushed to market, released several months before its initial release date of 1990, only having modest updates to the hardware. With only six retail games released that took advantage of the console's hardware updates, the SuperGrafx was a commercial failure, selling only 75,000 units total in both regions. None of the hardware advancements it possessed were carried over to NEC's later consoles, such as the TurboDuo.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">La PC Engine SuperGrafx (PCエンジンスーパーグラフィックス, Pī Shī Enjin SūpāGurafikkusu), tambie'n conocida simplemente como SuperGrafx, es una videoconsola dome'stica de cuarta generación fabricada por NEC Home Electronics y lanzada en Japón y Francia en 1989. Es la sucesora de la PC Engine, lanzada dos años antes. Conocida originalmente como PC Engine 2 durante las fases de producción, se presentaba como una aute'ntica consola dome'stica de 16 bits, con capacidades gráficas y de audio mejoradas respecto a su predecesora. La consola salió al mercado con prisas, varios meses antes de su fecha inicial de lanzamiento en 1990, y sólo contaba con modestas actualizaciones de hardware. Con sólo seis juegos comercializados que aprovechaban las actualizaciones de hardware de la consola, la SuperGrafx fue un fracaso comercial, vendiendo sólo 75.000 unidades en total en ambas regiones. Ninguno de los avances de hardware que poseía se trasladó a las consolas posteriores de NEC, como la TurboDuo.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Der PC Engine SuperGrafx (PCエンジンスーパーグラフィックス, Pī Shī Enjin SūpāGurafikkusu), auch einfach SuperGrafx genannt, ist eine Heimvideospielkonsole der vierten Generation, die von NEC Home Electronics hergestellt und 1989 in Japan und Frankreich veröffentlicht wurde. Sie ist das Nachfolgesystem der PC Engine, die zwei Jahre zuvor veröffentlicht wurde. Ursprünglich während der Produktionsphase als PC Engine 2 bekannt, wurde sie als echte 16-Bit-Heimkonsole mit verbesserten Grafik- und Audiofunktionen gegenüber ihrem Vorgänger angepriesen. Die Konsole wurde im Eiltempo auf den Markt gebracht und kam mehrere Monate vor dem ursprünglichen Erscheinungsdatum 1990 auf den Markt, wobei die Hardware nur geringfügig aktualisiert wurde. Mit nur sechs im Handel erhältlichen Spielen, die die Hardware-Updates der Konsole nutzten, war der SuperGrafx ein kommerzieller Misserfolg, von dem in beiden Regionen insgesamt nur 75.000 Stück verkauft wurden. Keiner der Hardware-Fortschritte, die sie besaß, wurde auf die späteren Konsolen von NEC übertragen, wie z. B. die TurboDuo.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">La PC Engine SuperGrafx (PCエンジンスーパーグラフィックス, Pī Shī Enjin SūpāGurafikkusu), e'galement connue sous le nom de SuperGrafx, est une console de jeux vide'o de salon de quatrie'me ge'ne'ration fabrique'e par NEC Home Electronics et commercialise'e au Japon et en France en 1989. Elle succe'de a' la PC Engine, sortie deux ans plus tôt. Connue a' l'origine sous le nom de PC Engine 2 pendant les phases de production, elle e'tait pre'sente'e comme une ve'ritable console de salon 16 bits, dote'e de capacite's graphiques et audio ame'liore'es par rapport a' son pre'de'cesseur. La console a e'te' commercialise'e a' la hâte, plusieurs mois avant sa date de sortie initiale, fixe'e a' 1990, et n'a be'ne'ficie' que de modestes mises a' jour mate'rielles. Avec seulement six jeux commercialise's qui profitaient des mises a' jour mate'rielles de la console, le SuperGrafx a e'te' un e'chec commercial, ne se vendant qu'a' 75 000 exemplaires dans les deux re'gions. Aucune des ame'liorations mate'rielles apporte'es a' la SuperGrafx n'a e'te' reprise sur les consoles ulte'rieures de NEC, telles que la TurboDuo.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Il PC Engine SuperGrafx (PCエンジンスーパーグラフィックス, Pī Shī Enjin SūpāGurafikkusu), noto anche come semplicemente SuperGrafx, e' una console per videogiochi domestici di quarta generazione prodotta da NEC Home Electronics e rilasciata in Giappone e Francia nel 1989. e' il successore del PC Engine, uscito due anni prima. Conosciuto originariamente come PC Engine 2 durante le fasi di produzione, e' stato presentato come una vera console domestica a 16 bit, con capacita' grafiche e audio migliorate rispetto al suo predecessore. La console e' stata immessa sul mercato in fretta e furia, rilasciata diversi mesi prima della data di uscita iniziale del 1990, con solo modesti aggiornamenti all'hardware. Con solo sei giochi distribuiti al dettaglio che sfruttavano gli aggiornamenti hardware della console, il SuperGrafx fu un fallimento commerciale, vendendo solo 75.000 unita' in totale in entrambe le regioni. Nessuno dei miglioramenti hardware di cui disponeva fu trasferito alle console successive di NEC, come il TurboDuo.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




