<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>Adrenaline Arcade offers a thrilling collection of arcade games designed to deliver high-energy entertainment for all ages. Their games feature innovative concepts, vibrant graphics, and immersive experiences that keep players engaged and coming back for more.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Adrenaline Arcade offre un'emozionante collezione di giochi arcade progettati per offrire un intrattenimento ad alta energia per tutte le eta'. I loro giochi sono caratterizzati da concetti innovativi, grafiche vivaci ed esperienze coinvolgenti che impegnano i giocatori e li spingono a tornare.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Adrenaline Arcade propose une collection palpitante de jeux d'arcade conçus pour offrir un divertissement plein d'e'nergie a' tous les âges. Leurs jeux se caracte'risent par des concepts innovants, des graphismes e'clatants et des expe'riences immersives qui captent l'attention des joueurs et les incitent a' revenir.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Adrenaline Arcade bietet eine aufregende Sammlung von Arcade-Spielen an, die für alle Altersgruppen energiegeladene Unterhaltung bieten. Ihre Spiele zeichnen sich durch innovative Konzepte, lebendige Grafiken und fesselnde Erlebnisse aus, die die Spieler fesseln und sie immer wieder zurückkommen lassen.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">Adrenaline Arcade ofrece una emocionante colección de juegos arcade diseñados para proporcionar entretenimiento de alta energía para todas las edades. Sus juegos presentan conceptos innovadores, gráficos vibrantes y experiencias envolventes que mantienen a los jugadores enganchados y vuelven a por más.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>      
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




