<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>The APF Microcomputer System is a second generation 8-bit cartridge-based home video game console released in October 1978 by APF Electronics Inc. with six cartridges. The console is often referred to M-1000 or MP-1000, which are the two model numbers of the console. The APF-MP1000 comes built-in with the game Rocket Patrol. The APF-MP1000 is a part of the APF Imagination Machine. It is the successor to the APF TV Fun line of first generation consoles.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">El APF Microcomputer System es una videoconsola dome'stica de 8 bits basada en cartuchos de segunda generación lanzada en octubre de 1978 por APF Electronics Inc. con seis cartuchos. A menudo se hace referencia a la consola como M-1000 o MP-1000, que son los dos números de modelo de la consola. La APF-MP1000 viene incorporada con el juego Rocket Patrol. La APF-MP1000 forma parte de la APF Imagination Machine. Es la sucesora de la línea APF TV Fun de consolas de primera generación.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Das APF Microcomputer System ist eine 8-Bit-Cartridge-basierte Heimvideospielkonsole der zweiten Generation, die im Oktober 1978 von APF Electronics Inc. mit sechs Cartridges veröffentlicht wurde. Die Konsole wird oft als M-1000 oder MP-1000 bezeichnet, was die beiden Modellnummern der Konsole sind. Die APF-MP1000 wird mit dem Spiel Rocket Patrol ausgeliefert. Die APF-MP1000 ist ein Teil der APF Imagination Machine. Sie ist der Nachfolger der APF-TV-Fun-Reihe der ersten Konsolengeneration.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">L'APF Microcomputer System est une console de jeu vide'o de salon de deuxie'me ge'ne'ration a' cartouche 8 bits lance'e en octobre 1978 par APF Electronics Inc. avec six cartouches. La console est souvent appele'e M-1000 ou MP-1000, qui sont les deux nume'ros de mode'le de la console. L'APF-MP1000 est livre'e avec le jeu Rocket Patrol. L'APF-MP1000 fait partie de l'APF Imagination Machine. Elle succe'de a' la ligne de consoles de premie're ge'ne'ration APF TV Fun.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">L'APF Microcomputer System e' una console per videogiochi domestici a 8 bit di seconda generazione, rilasciata nell'ottobre 1978 da APF Electronics Inc. con sei cartucce. La console viene spesso indicata come M-1000 o MP-1000, che sono i due numeri di modello della console. L'APF-MP1000 veniva fornito con il gioco Rocket Patrol. L'APF-MP1000 fa parte della APF Imagination Machine. e' il successore della linea di console APF TV Fun di prima generazione.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




