<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>Here is a collection of all the games created by International Games System Co., Ltd. (IGS) and featured on this machine.                                                International Games System Co., Ltd. (IGS) is a prominent Taiwanese video game developer and publisher, headquartered in New Taipei City, Taiwan. Founded in 1989, they are widely known for creating popular arcade and PC online games, most notably the Knights of Valour (Sangoku Senki) series, Martial Masters, and Star 3缺1.The company is responsible for producing the PolyGame Master (PGM), an arcade system board akin to the Neo Geo that allows operators to swap games via cartridges. While primarily an arcade developer, IGS has expanded significantly into the PC online gaming and mobile gaming markets.For further details and a complete list of their published titles, you can visit the Wikipedia Category for International Games System.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Ecco una raccolta di tutti i giochi creati dalla International Games System Co., Ltd. (IGS) e presenti su questa macchina.   International Games System Co., Ltd. (IGS) e' un'importante azienda taiwanese di sviluppo e pubblicazione di videogiochi, con sede a New Taipei City, Taiwan. Fondata nel 1989, e' nota per la creazione di popolari giochi arcade e online per PC, tra cui spiccano la serie Knights of Valour (Sangoku Senki), Martial Masters e Star 3缺1. L'azienda e' responsabile della produzione del PolyGame Master (PGM), una scheda di sistema arcade simile al Neo Geo che permette agli operatori di scambiare i giochi tramite cartucce. Pur essendo principalmente un'azienda di sviluppo di giochi arcade, IGS si e' espansa significativamente nei mercati dei giochi online per PC e dei giochi per dispositivi mobili. Per ulteriori dettagli e un elenco completo dei titoli pubblicati, e' possibile visitare la pagina di Wikipedia dedicata a International Games System.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Voici une collection de tous les jeux cre'e's par International Games System Co., Ltd. (IGS) et disponibles sur cette machine.                                                                           International Games System Co., Ltd. (IGS) est un important de'veloppeur et e'diteur taïwanais de jeux vide'o, base' a' New Taipei City, a' Taïwan. Fonde'e en 1989, la socie'te' est re'pute'e pour ses jeux d'arcade et PC en ligne a' succe's, notamment les se'ries Knights of Valour (Sangoku Senki), Martial Masters et Star 3缺1. IGS produit e'galement le PolyGame Master (PGM), une carte me're pour borne d'arcade similaire a' la Neo Geo, permettant aux exploitants de changer de jeu grâce a' des cartouches. Bien que principalement actif dans le domaine des jeux d'arcade, IGS s'est conside'rablement de'veloppe' sur les marche's du jeu PC en ligne et du jeu mobile. Pour plus d'informations et la liste comple'te de ses titres publie's, consultez la page Wikipe'dia consacre'e a' International Games System.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Hier ist eine Sammlung aller von International Games System Co., Ltd. (IGS) entwickelten und auf dieser Maschine enthaltenen Spiele.                                                                                                International Games System Co., Ltd. (IGS) ist ein renommierter taiwanesischer Videospielentwickler und -publisher mit Hauptsitz in Neu-Taipeh, Taiwan. Das 1989 gegründete Unternehmen ist bekannt für seine beliebten Arcade- und PC-Online-Spiele, insbesondere für die Serien „Knights of Valour“ (Sangoku Senki), „Martial Masters“ und „Star 3缺1“. IGS entwickelte den PolyGame Master (PGM), eine Arcade-Systemplatine ähnlich dem Neo Geo, die es Betreibern ermöglicht, Spiele per Cartridge zu wechseln. Obwohl IGS primär Arcade-Spiele entwickelt, hat das Unternehmen sein Angebot auch auf den PC-Online- und Mobile-Gaming-Markt ausgeweitet. Weitere Informationen und eine vollständige Liste der veröffentlichten Titel finden Sie im Wikipedia-Artikel zu International Games System.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">Aquí tene'is una recopilación de todos los juegos creados por International Games System Co., Ltd. (IGS) e incluidos en esta máquina.                                                                                                   International Games System Co., Ltd. (IGS) es una destacada desarrolladora y editora de videojuegos taiwanesa, con sede en la ciudad de Nuevo Taipe'i, Taiwán. Fundada en 1989, es ampliamente conocida por crear populares juegos arcade y juegos online para PC, entre los que destacan la serie Knights of Valour (Sangoku Senki), Martial Masters y Star 3缺1. La compañía es responsable de la producción de PolyGame Master (PGM), una placa base para sistemas arcade similar a la Neo Geo que permite a los operadores intercambiar juegos mediante cartuchos. Si bien IGS se dedica principalmente al desarrollo de juegos arcade, se ha expandido significativamente a los mercados de juegos online para PC y juegos móviles. Para obtener más detalles y una lista completa de sus títulos publicados, puede visitar la categoría de Wikipedia sobre International Games System.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>





