<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>A handheld TV game or plug and play game is an integrated home video game console and game controller, usually battery powered, which connects directly to a television. The game software is built directly into the unit, which is typically designed to look like a toy or classic game console controller with the addition of a composite video cable to connect the unit. These systems usually contain either a collection of classic games or original games based on licensed properties. Because the game software is integrated into the game unit and almost never designed to be changed by the user, these game systems are typically marketed as electronic toys or collectibles rather than game consoles. Several manufacturers produced these devices beginning in the 1990s, though the concept became best known with the release in 2002 of Jakks Pacific's Atari Classic 10-in-1 TV. Most manufacturers have their own trademarked names for these systems, such as Radica's Play TV or Majesco's TV Arcade; however, most retailers refer to them as "TV games" or "plug and play" games.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Un gioco TV portatile o un gioco plug and play e' una console per videogiochi domestica integrata con un controller, solitamente alimentato a batteria, che si collega direttamente a un televisore. Il software di gioco e' integrato direttamente nell'unita', che in genere e' progettata per assomigliare a un giocattolo o a un controller di una console di gioco classica, con l'aggiunta di un cavo video composito per il collegamento. Questi sistemi contengono solitamente una raccolta di giochi classici o giochi originali basati su proprieta' concesse in licenza. Poiche' il software di gioco e' integrato nell'unita' di gioco e non e' quasi mai progettato per essere modificato dall'utente, questi sistemi di gioco sono generalmente commercializzati come giocattoli elettronici o oggetti da collezione piuttosto che come console di gioco. Diversi produttori hanno prodotto questi dispositivi a partire dagli anni '90, sebbene il concetto sia diventato piU' noto con l'uscita nel 2002 dell'Atari Classic 10-in-1 TV di Jakks Pacific. La maggior parte dei produttori ha registrato i propri marchi per questi sistemi, come Play TV di Radica o TV Arcade di Majesco; tuttavia, la maggior parte dei rivenditori li chiama "giochi TV" o giochi "plug and play".<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Ein tragbares TV-Spiel oder Plug-and-Play-Spiel ist eine integrierte Heimvideospielkonsole mit integriertem Controller, meist batteriebetrieben, die direkt an einen Fernseher angeschlossen wird. Die Spielsoftware ist fest im Gerät integriert, das typischerweise wie ein Spielzeug oder ein klassischer Konsolen-Controller aussieht und zusätzlich über ein Composite-Videokabel mit dem Fernseher verbunden wird. Diese Systeme enthalten in der Regel entweder eine Sammlung klassischer Spiele oder Originalspiele basierend auf lizenzierten Marken. Da die Spielsoftware fest im Gerät integriert und fast nie vom Benutzer veränderbar ist, werden diese Systeme eher als elektronisches Spielzeug oder Sammlerstück denn als Spielkonsole vermarktet. Verschiedene Hersteller produzierten diese Geräte ab den 1990er-Jahren, wobei das Konzept mit der Veröffentlichung des Atari Classic 10-in-1 TV von Jakks Pacific im Jahr 2002 die größte Bekanntheit erlangte. Die meisten Hersteller verwenden eigene Markennamen für diese Systeme, wie beispielsweise Play TV von Radica oder TV Arcade von Majesco; im Handel werden sie jedoch meist als „TV-Spiele“ oder „Plug-and-Play-Spiele“ bezeichnet.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Une console de jeux vide'o portable, ou console « plug and play », est une console de jeux vide'o de salon inte'grant une manette, ge'ne'ralement alimente'e par batterie, et se connectant directement a' un te'le'viseur. Le jeu est inte'gre' a' l'appareil, qui ressemble souvent a' un jouet ou a' une manette de console re'tro, avec un câble vide'o composite pour la connexion. Ces syste'mes proposent ge'ne'ralement une se'lection de jeux classiques ou des jeux originaux base's sur des licences. Le jeu e'tant inte'gre' et quasiment impossible a' modifier par l'utilisateur, ces consoles sont plutôt commercialise'es comme des jouets e'lectroniques ou des objets de collection. Plusieurs fabricants ont produit ces appareils de's les anne'es 1990, mais le concept a ve'ritablement explose' avec la sortie, en 2002, de l'Atari Classic 10-en-1 TV de Jakks Pacific. La plupart des fabricants posse'dent leurs propres marques de'pose'es, comme Play TV de Radica ou TV Arcade de Majesco ; cependant, la plupart des de'taillants les appellent simplement « consoles de jeux vide'o » ou « jeux « plug and play ».<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">Una consola portátil de videojuegos o consola plug and play es una consola de videojuegos dome'stica integrada y un mando, generalmente alimentado por pilas, que se conecta directamente a un televisor. El software del juego está integrado en la unidad, que suele estar diseñada para parecerse a un juguete o a un mando de consola clásica, con la adición de un cable de vídeo compuesto para conectarla. Estos sistemas suelen contener una colección de juegos clásicos o juegos originales basados ​​en licencias. Dado que el software del juego está integrado en la consola y casi nunca está diseñado para ser modificado por el usuario, estos sistemas suelen comercializarse como juguetes electrónicos o artículos de colección en lugar de consolas. Varios fabricantes produjeron estos dispositivos a partir de la de'cada de 1990, aunque el concepto se popularizó con el lanzamiento en 2002 del televisor Atari Classic 10 en 1 de Jakks Pacific. La mayoría de los fabricantes tienen sus propias marcas registradas para estos sistemas, como Play TV de Radica o TV Arcade de Majesco; sin embargo, la mayoría de los minoristas los denominan "juegos para televisión" o juegos "plug and play".<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




