<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>The PlayStation 4 (PS4) is a home video game console developed by Sony Interactive Entertainment. A console of the eighth generation, it competes with Microsoft's Xbox One and Nintendo's Wii U and Switch. Moving away from the more complex Cell microarchitecture of its predecessor, the console features an AMD Accelerated Processing Unit (APU) built upon the x86-64 architecture, which can theoretically peak at 1.84 teraflops; AMD stated that it was the "most powerful" APU it had developed to date. The PlayStation 4 places an increased emphasis on social interaction and integration with other devices and services, including the ability to play games off-console on PlayStation Vita and other supported devices ("Remote Play"), the ability to stream gameplay online or to friends, with them controlling gameplay remotely ("Share Play"). The console's controller was also redesigned and improved over the PlayStation 3, with improved buttons and analog sticks, and an integrated touchpad among other changes. The console also supports HDR10 High-dynamic-range video and playback of 4K resolution multimedia.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">La PlayStation 4 (PS4) e' una console per videogiochi domestica sviluppata da Sony Interactive Entertainment. e' una console di ottava generazione e compete con la Xbox One di Microsoft e le console Wii U e Switch di Nintendo. Abbandonando la piU' complessa microarchitettura Cell del suo predecessore, la console e' dotata di un'unita' di elaborazione accelerata (APU) AMD basata sull'architettura x86-64, che puo' teoricamente raggiungere un picco di 1,84 teraflops; AMD ha dichiarato che si tratta dell'APU "piU' potente" sviluppata finora. La PlayStation 4 pone una maggiore enfasi sull'interazione sociale e sull'integrazione con altri dispositivi e servizi, tra cui la possibilita' di giocare fuori dalla console su PlayStation Vita e altri dispositivi supportati ("Remote Play"), la possibilita' di trasmettere il gioco in streaming online o agli amici, con questi ultimi che possono controllare il gioco a distanza ("Share Play"). Anche il controller della console e' stato ridisegnato e migliorato rispetto a quello della PlayStation 3, con pulsanti e stick analogici migliorati e un touchpad integrato. La console supporta anche i video ad alta gamma dinamica HDR10 e la riproduzione di contenuti multimediali con risoluzione 4K.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">La PlayStation 4 (PS4) est une console de jeux vide'o de salon de'veloppe'e par Sony Interactive Entertainment. Console de huitie'me ge'ne'ration, elle est en concurrence avec la Xbox One de Microsoft et les Wii U et Switch de Nintendo. De'laissant la microarchitecture Cell plus complexe de son pre'de'cesseur, la console est e'quipe'e d'une unite' de traitement acce'le're' (APU) AMD base'e sur l'architecture x86-64, qui peut the'oriquement atteindre 1,84 te'raflops ; AMD a de'clare' qu'il s'agissait de l'APU "la plus puissante" qu'elle ait de'veloppe'e a' ce jour. La PlayStation 4 met davantage l'accent sur l'interaction sociale et l'inte'gration avec d'autres appareils et services, notamment la possibilite' de jouer a' des jeux hors console sur la PlayStation Vita et d'autres appareils pris en charge ("Remote Play"), la possibilite' de diffuser le gameplay en ligne ou a' des amis, ces derniers contrôlant le gameplay a' distance ("Share Play"). La manette de la console a e'galement e'te' redessine'e et ame'liore'e par rapport a' la PlayStation 3, avec des boutons et des sticks analogiques plus performants, ainsi qu'un pave' tactile inte'gre', entre autres changements. La console prend e'galement en charge la vide'o HDR10 a' gamme dynamique e'leve'e et la lecture de contenus multime'dias en re'solution 4K.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Die PlayStation 4 (PS4) ist eine von Sony Interactive Entertainment entwickelte Videospielkonsole für den Heimgebrauch. Als Konsole der achten Generation konkurriert sie mit der Xbox One von Microsoft sowie der Wii U und der Switch von Nintendo. Die Konsole löst sich von der komplexeren Cell-Mikroarchitektur ihres Vorgängers und verfügt über eine AMD Accelerated Processing Unit (APU), die auf der x86-64-Architektur basiert und theoretisch eine Spitzenleistung von 1,84 Teraflops erreichen kann; AMD gab an, dass es sich dabei um die leistungsstärkste" APU handelt, die es bisher entwickelt hat. Die PlayStation 4 setzt verstärkt auf soziale Interaktion und die Integration mit anderen Geräten und Diensten, einschließlich der Möglichkeit, Spiele außerhalb der Konsole auf PlayStation Vita und anderen unterstützten Geräten zu spielen ("Remote Play"), sowie der Möglichkeit, Spiele online oder an Freunde zu streamen, wobei diese das Spiel aus der Ferne steuern können ("Share Play"). Der Controller der Konsole wurde im Vergleich zur PlayStation 3 ebenfalls überarbeitet und verbessert, unter anderem mit verbesserten Tasten und Analogsticks sowie einem integrierten Touchpad. Die Konsole unterstützt außerdem HDR10 High-Dynamic-Range-Video und die Wiedergabe von Multimedia in 4K-Auflösung.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">La PlayStation 4 (PS4) es una videoconsola dome'stica desarrollada por Sony Interactive Entertainment. Consola de la octava generación, compite con la Xbox One de Microsoft y las Wii U y Switch de Nintendo. Alejándose de la microarquitectura Cell más compleja de su predecesora, la consola incorpora una unidad de procesamiento acelerado (APU) de AMD basada en la arquitectura x86-64, que teóricamente puede alcanzar un pico de 1,84 teraflops; AMD declaró que era la APU "más potente" que había desarrollado hasta la fecha. PlayStation 4 pone un mayor e'nfasis en la interacción social y la integración con otros dispositivos y servicios, incluyendo la posibilidad de jugar fuera de la consola en PlayStation Vita y otros dispositivos compatibles ("Remote Play"), la capacidad de transmitir el juego en línea o a amigos, con ellos controlando el juego de forma remota ("Share Play"). El mando de la consola tambie'n se ha rediseñado y mejorado con respecto al de PlayStation 3, con botones y sticks analógicos mejorados y un touchpad integrado, entre otros cambios. La consola tambie'n es compatible con vídeo de alto rango dinámico HDR10 y reproducción multimedia en resolución 4K.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




