<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>The Sega Hikaru is a successor of the Sega NAOMI and Sega Model 3 arcade systems that was developed in 1998 and debuted in 1999. The Hikaru was used for a handful of deluxe dedicated-cabinet games, beginning with 1999's Brave Fire Fighters, in which the flame and water effects were largely a showpiece for the hardware. It was significantly more powerful and expensive than the NAOMI. The Hikaru featured a custom Sega GPU with advanced graphical capabilities, additional CPU and sound processors, various custom processors, increased memory, and faster bandwidth. It was the first game platform capable of effective hardware Phong shading, the most intensive form of shading at the time, and was capable of the most complex lighting and particle effects of its time. It was the most powerful game system of its time (Planet Harriers, for example, was regarded as having the best video game graphics at the time), but it was very expensive and difficult to program. Since it was comparatively expensive to produce, Sega soon abandoned the Hikaru in favor of continued NAOMI development. It was succeeded by the more affordable NAOMI 2.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">El Sega Hikaru es un sucesor de los sistemas arcade Sega NAOMI y Sega Model 3 que se desarrolló en 1998 y debutó en 1999. El Hikaru se utilizó para un puñado de juegos de lujo dedicados, comenzando con Brave Fire Fighters de 1999, en el que los efectos de llamas y agua eran en gran medida una pieza de exhibición para el hardware. Era mucho más potente y caro que el NAOMI. El Hikaru contaba con una GPU Sega personalizada con funciones gráficas avanzadas, CPU y procesadores de sonido adicionales, varios procesadores personalizados, más memoria y un ancho de banda más rápido. Fue la primera plataforma de juegos capaz de aplicar el sombreado Phong por hardware, la forma más intensiva de sombreado de la e'poca, y de crear los efectos de iluminación y partículas más complejos de su tiempo. Era el sistema de juego más potente de su e'poca (Planet Harriers, por ejemplo, estaba considerado como el que tenía los mejores gráficos de videojuego de la e'poca), pero era muy caro y difícil de programar. Dado que su producción era comparativamente cara, Sega abandonó pronto el Hikaru en favor de continuar con el desarrollo del NAOMI. Le sucedió el más asequible NAOMI 2.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Der Sega Hikaru ist ein Nachfolger des Sega NAOMI und des Sega Model 3 Arcade-Systems, der 1998 entwickelt wurde und 1999 auf den Markt kam. Der Hikaru wurde für eine Handvoll Deluxe-Spiele mit eigenem Gehäuse verwendet, beginnend mit Brave Fire Fighters von 1999, bei dem die Flammen- und Wassereffekte vor allem ein Vorzeigeobjekt für die Hardware waren. Er war wesentlich leistungsfähiger und teurer als der NAOMI. Der Hikaru verfügte über einen maßgeschneiderten Sega-Grafikprozessor mit erweiterten grafischen Fähigkeiten, zusätzliche CPU- und Soundprozessoren, verschiedene maßgeschneiderte Prozessoren, mehr Speicher und eine schnellere Bandbreite. Es war die erste Spieleplattform, die effektives Hardware-Phong-Shading, die damals intensivste Form des Shadings, beherrschte und zu den komplexesten Beleuchtungs- und Partikeleffekten der damaligen Zeit fähig war. Es war das leistungsstärkste Spielesystem seiner Zeit (Planet Harriers beispielsweise galt als das Spiel mit der besten Videospielgrafik seiner Zeit), aber es war sehr teuer und schwierig zu programmieren. Da es vergleichsweise teuer in der Herstellung war, gab Sega den Hikaru bald zugunsten der weiteren NAOMI-Entwicklung auf. Sein Nachfolger war das preiswertere NAOMI 2.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Sega Hikaru est un successeur des syste'mes d'arcade Sega NAOMI et Sega Model 3, de'veloppe' en 1998 et lance' en 1999. Le Hikaru a e'te' utilise' pour une poigne'e de jeux de luxe de'die's a' une armoire, a' commencer par Brave Fire Fighters en 1999, dans lequel les effets de flammes et d'eau e'taient en grande partie une mise en valeur du mate'riel. Il e'tait nettement plus puissant et plus cher que le NAOMI. Le Hikaru e'tait e'quipe' d'un GPU Sega personnalise' dote' de capacite's graphiques avance'es, d'une unite' centrale et de processeurs audio supple'mentaires, de divers processeurs personnalise's, d'une me'moire accrue et d'une bande passante plus rapide. Il s'agissait de la premie're plateforme de jeu capable de re'aliser un ombrage mate'riel Phong efficace, la forme d'ombrage la plus intensive a' l'e'poque, et capable des effets d'e'clairage et de particules les plus complexes de l'e'poque. C'e'tait le syste'me de jeu le plus puissant de l'e'poque (Planet Harriers, par exemple, e'tait conside're' comme le meilleur jeu vide'o de l'e'poque), mais il e'tait tre's cher et difficile a' programmer. Comme il e'tait relativement cher a' produire, Sega a rapidement abandonne' le Hikaru en faveur de la poursuite du de'veloppement du NAOMI. Il a e'te' remplace' par le NAOMI 2, plus abordable.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Il Sega Hikaru e' un successore dei sistemi arcade Sega NAOMI e Sega Model 3, sviluppato nel 1998 e presentato nel 1999. La Hikaru e' stata utilizzata per una manciata di giochi deluxe per cabinati, a partire da Brave Fire Fighters del 1999, in cui gli effetti delle fiamme e dell'acqua erano in gran parte uno spettacolo per l'hardware. Era molto piU' potente e costoso del NAOMI. La Hikaru era dotata di una GPU Sega personalizzata con capacita' grafiche avanzate, CPU e processori audio aggiuntivi, vari processori personalizzati, una memoria maggiore e una larghezza di banda piU' veloce. Fu la prima piattaforma di gioco in grado di utilizzare efficacemente l'hardware Phong shading, la forma piU' intensiva di shading dell'epoca, e fu in grado di realizzare i piU' complessi effetti di illuminazione e particellari dell'epoca. Era il sistema di gioco piU' potente dell'epoca (Planet Harriers, ad esempio, era considerato il miglior videogioco grafico dell'epoca), ma era molto costoso e difficile da programmare. Poiche' la produzione era relativamente costosa, Sega abbandono' presto la Hikaru a favore di un continuo sviluppo del NAOMI. A questo modello successe il piU' economico NAOMI 2.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




