<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>The Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES), also known as the Super NES or Super Nintendo, is a 16-bit home video game console developed by Nintendo that was released in 1990 in Japan and South Korea, 1991 in North America, 1992 in Europe and Australasia (Oceania), and 1993 in South America. In Japan, the system is called the Super Famicom (SFC). In South Korea, it is known as the Super Comboy and was distributed by Hyundai Electronics. The system was released in Brazil on August 30, 1993, by Playtronic. Although each version is essentially the same, several forms of regional lockout prevent the different cartridges from being compatible with one another. The SNES is Nintendo's second programmable home console, following the Nintendo Entertainment System (NES). The console introduced advanced graphics and sound capabilities compared with other systems at the time. The system was designed to accommodate the ongoing development of a variety of enhancement chips integrated into game cartridges to be competitive into the next generation.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">La Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES), tambie'n conocida como Super NES o Super Nintendo, es una videoconsola dome'stica de 16 bits desarrollada por Nintendo que salió a la venta en 1990 en Japón y Corea del Sur, en 1991 en Norteame'rica, en 1992 en Europa y Australasia (Oceanía) y en 1993 en Sudame'rica. En Japón, la consola se denomina Super Famicom (SFC). En Corea del Sur, se conoce como Super Comboy y fue distribuido por Hyundai Electronics. En Brasil, Playtronic lanzó la consola el 30 de agosto de 1993. Aunque cada versión es esencialmente la misma, varias formas de bloqueo regional impiden que los diferentes cartuchos sean compatibles entre sí. La SNES es la segunda consola dome'stica programable de Nintendo, tras la Nintendo Entertainment System (NES). La consola introdujo funciones avanzadas de gráficos y sonido en comparación con otras consolas de la e'poca. El sistema se diseñó para dar cabida al desarrollo continuo de una variedad de chips de mejora integrados en los cartuchos de juego para ser competitivos en la siguiente generación.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Das Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES), auch bekannt als Super NES oder Super Nintendo, ist eine von Nintendo entwickelte 16-Bit-Videospielkonsole für den Heimgebrauch, die 1990 in Japan und Südkorea, 1991 in Nordamerika, 1992 in Europa und Australasien (Ozeanien) und 1993 in Südamerika veröffentlicht wurde. In Japan wird das System Super Famicom (SFC) genannt. In Südkorea ist es unter dem Namen Super Comboy bekannt und wurde von Hyundai Electronics vertrieben. In Brasilien wurde das System am 30. August 1993 von Playtronic veröffentlicht. Obwohl alle Versionen im Wesentlichen gleich sind, verhindern verschiedene Formen von regionalen Sperren, dass die verschiedenen Cartridges miteinander kompatibel sind. Das SNES ist die zweite programmierbare Heimkonsole von Nintendo nach dem Nintendo Entertainment System (NES). Die Konsole bot im Vergleich zu anderen Systemen der damaligen Zeit fortschrittliche Grafik- und Soundfunktionen. Das System war so konzipiert, dass es die Weiterentwicklung einer Vielzahl von in Spielkassetten integrierten Erweiterungs-Chips ermöglichte, um in der nächsten Generation wettbewerbsfähig zu sein.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">La Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES), e'galement connue sous le nom de Super NES ou Super Nintendo, est une console de jeux vide'o de salon 16 bits de'veloppe'e par Nintendo et commercialise'e en 1990 au Japon et en Core'e du Sud, en 1991 en Ame'rique du Nord, en 1992 en Europe et en Australasie (Oce'anie), et en 1993 en Ame'rique du Sud. Au Japon, la console est appele'e Super Famicom (SFC). En Core'e du Sud, il est connu sous le nom de Super Comboy et a e'te' distribue' par Hyundai Electronics. Le syste'me a e'te' commercialise' au Bre'sil le 30 août 1993 par Playtronic. Bien que chaque version soit essentiellement la même, plusieurs formes de verrouillage re'gional empêchent les diffe'rentes cartouches d'être compatibles les unes avec les autres. La SNES est la deuxie'me console de salon programmable de Nintendo, apre's la Nintendo Entertainment System (NES). La console a introduit des capacite's graphiques et sonores avance'es par rapport aux autres consoles de l'e'poque. La console a e'te' conçue pour s'adapter au de'veloppement continu d'une varie'te' de puces d'ame'lioration inte'gre'es dans les cartouches de jeu afin d'être compe'titive dans la ge'ne'ration suivante.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Il Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES), noto anche come Super NES o Super Nintendo, e' una console per videogiochi domestici a 16 bit sviluppata da Nintendo e uscita nel 1990 in Giappone e Corea del Sud, nel 1991 in Nord America, nel 1992 in Europa e Australasia (Oceania) e nel 1993 in Sud America. In Giappone la console e' chiamata Super Famicom (SFC). In Corea del Sud e' conosciuto come Super Comboy ed e' stato distribuito da Hyundai Electronics. Il sistema e' stato rilasciato in Brasile il 30 agosto 1993 da Playtronic. Sebbene ogni versione sia essenzialmente identica, diverse forme di blocco regionale impediscono alle diverse cartucce di essere compatibili tra loro. Lo SNES e' la seconda console domestica programmabile di Nintendo, dopo il Nintendo Entertainment System (NES). La console introdusse capacita' grafiche e sonore avanzate rispetto alle altre console dell'epoca. La console e' stata progettata per accogliere il continuo sviluppo di una serie di chip di miglioramento integrati nelle cartucce di gioco per essere competitivi nella generazione successiva.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




