<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>An arcade game or coin-op game is a coin-operated entertainment machine typically installed in public businesses such as restaurants, bars and amusement arcades. Most arcade games are video games, pinball machines, electro-mechanical games, redemption games or merchandisers. While exact dates are debated, the golden age of arcade video games is usually defined as a period beginning sometime in the late 1970s and ending sometime in the mid-1980s. Excluding a brief resurgence in the early 1990s, the arcade industry subsequently declined in the Western hemisphere as competing home video game consoles such as the Sony PlayStation and Microsoft Xbox increased in their graphics and game-play capability and decreased in cost. The Eastern Hemisphere retains a strong arcade industry.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">Un juego arcade o juego de monedas es una máquina de entretenimiento que funciona con monedas y que suele instalarse en negocios públicos como restaurantes, bares y salones recreativos. La mayoría de los juegos arcade son videojuegos, máquinas de pinball, juegos electromecánicos, juegos de canje o merchandisers. Aunque las fechas exactas son objeto de debate, la edad de oro de los videojuegos arcade suele definirse como un periodo que comienza a finales de la de'cada de 1970 y termina a mediados de la de'cada de 1980. Exceptuando un breve resurgimiento a principios de los años 90, la industria de los salones recreativos decayó posteriormente en el hemisferio occidental a medida que las consolas de videojuegos dome'sticas de la competencia, como la PlayStation de Sony y la Xbox de Microsoft, aumentaban su capacidad gráfica y de juego y disminuían su coste. El hemisferio oriental conserva una fuerte industria de los salones recreativos.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Ein Arcade-Spiel oder Münzspiel ist ein münzbetriebenes Unterhaltungsgerät, das typischerweise in öffentlichen Einrichtungen wie Restaurants, Bars und Spielhallen aufgestellt wird. Bei den meisten Spielhallen handelt es sich um Videospiele, Flipperautomaten, elektromechanische Spiele, Rücknahmespiele oder Merchandiser. Obwohl die genauen Daten umstritten sind, wird das goldene Zeitalter der Spielhallen-Videospiele gewöhnlich als ein Zeitraum definiert, der irgendwann in den späten 1970er Jahren begann und irgendwann Mitte der 1980er Jahre endete. Abgesehen von einem kurzen Aufschwung in den frühen 1990er Jahren ging die Arcade-Industrie in der westlichen Hemisphäre zurück, als konkurrierende Videospielkonsolen wie die Sony PlayStation und die Microsoft Xbox ihre Grafik- und Spielfunktionen verbesserten und ihre Kosten senkten. In der östlichen Hemisphäre gibt es nach wie vor eine starke Spielhallenindustrie.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Un jeu d'arcade ou jeu a' pie'ces est une machine de divertissement fonctionnant avec des pie'ces de monnaie, ge'ne'ralement installe'e dans des e'tablissements publics tels que des restaurants, des bars et des salles de jeux. La plupart des jeux d'arcade sont des jeux vide'o, des flippers, des jeux e'lectrome'caniques, des jeux de rachat ou des pre'sentoirs. Bien que les dates exactes soient controverse'es, l'âge d'or des jeux vide'o d'arcade est ge'ne'ralement de'fini comme une pe'riode commençant a' la fin des anne'es 1970 et se terminant au milieu des anne'es 1980. a' l'exception d'une bre've re'surgence au de'but des anne'es 1990, l'industrie des salles d'arcade a ensuite de'cline' dans l'he'misphe're occidental a' mesure que les consoles de jeux vide'o de salon concurrentes, telles que la PlayStation de Sony et la Xbox de Microsoft, ame'lioraient leurs graphismes et leurs capacite's de jeu et diminuaient leurs coûts. L'he'misphe're oriental conserve une forte industrie des salles d'arcade.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Un gioco arcade o coin-op e' una macchina per l'intrattenimento a moneta tipicamente installata in esercizi pubblici come ristoranti, bar e sale giochi. La maggior parte dei giochi arcade sono videogiochi, flipper, giochi elettromeccanici, giochi a premio o merchandiser. Sebbene le date esatte siano discusse, l'eta' d'oro dei videogiochi arcade e' solitamente definita come un periodo che inizia alla fine degli anni Settanta e termina alla meta' degli anni Ottanta. Se si esclude una breve ripresa all'inizio degli anni Novanta, l'industria delle sale giochi ha subito un declino nell'emisfero occidentale a causa dell'aumento della grafica e delle capacita' di gioco delle console domestiche concorrenti, come la PlayStation di Sony e la Xbox di Microsoft, e della riduzione dei costi. L'emisfero orientale conserva una forte industria delle sale giochi.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




