<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>The Poke'mon Mini (officially stylized as Poke'mon mini) is a handheld game console that was designed and manufactured by Nintendo and themed around the Poke'mon media franchise. It is the smallest game system with interchangeable cartridges ever produced by Nintendo, weighing just under two and a half ounces (71 grams). It was first released in North America on November 16, 2001, (two days before the GameCube was released) then in Japan on December 14, 2001, and in Europe on March 15, 2002. The systems were released in three colors: Wooper Blue, Chikorita Green, and Smoochum Purple. Features of the Poke'mon mini include an internal real-time clock, an infrared port used to facilitate multiplayer gaming, a reed switch for detecting shakes, and a motor used to implement force feedback. Poke'mon Channel features playable emulated demo versions of Poke'mon Mini games, including the console exclusive "Snorlax's Lunch Time". Games such as "Togepi's Adventure" were only released in Japan.</text>
			<text lang="es">La Poke'mon Mini (oficialmente estilizada como Poke'mon mini) es una videoconsola portátil diseñada y fabricada por Nintendo en torno a la franquicia mediática Poke'mon. Es la consola con cartuchos intercambiables más pequeña jamás fabricada por Nintendo, con un peso de 71 gramos. Salió a la venta en Norteame'rica el 16 de noviembre de 2001 (dos días antes que la GameCube), en Japón el 14 de diciembre de 2001 y en Europa el 15 de marzo de 2002. Los sistemas salieron a la venta en tres colores: Azul Wooper, Verde Chikorita y Morado Smoochum. Entre las características del Poke'mon mini se incluyen un reloj interno en tiempo real, un puerto de infrarrojos utilizado para facilitar el juego multijugador, un interruptor de láminas para detectar las sacudidas y un motor utilizado para implementar la retroalimentación de fuerza. Canal Poke'mon ofrece versiones demo emuladas de los juegos de Poke'mon Mini, incluido el exclusivo para consola "Snorlax's Lunch Time". Juegos como "Togepi's Adventure" sólo se lanzaron en Japón.</text>
			<text lang="de">Poke'mon Mini (offiziell: Poke'mon mini) ist eine Handheld-Spielkonsole, die von Nintendo entwickelt und hergestellt wurde und sich an der Poke'mon-Medienreihe orientiert. Mit einem Gewicht von knapp 71 Gramm ist es das kleinste jemals von Nintendo hergestellte Spielsystem mit austauschbaren Kassetten. Es wurde erstmals am 16. November 2001 in Nordamerika veröffentlicht (zwei Tage vor der Veröffentlichung des GameCube), dann am 14. Dezember 2001 in Japan und am 15. März 2002 in Europa. Die Systeme wurden in drei Farben veröffentlicht: Wooper Blue, Chikorita Green und Smoochum Purple. Zu den Merkmalen des Poke'mon mini gehören eine interne Echtzeituhr, eine Infrarotschnittstelle zur Erleichterung von Multiplayer-Spielen, ein Reed-Schalter zur Erkennung von Erschütterungen und ein Motor zur Umsetzung von Force Feedback. Poke'mon Channel bietet spielbare emulierte Demoversionen von Poke'mon Mini-Spielen, darunter das konsolenexklusive "Snorlax's Lunch Time". Spiele wie "Togepi's Adventure" wurden nur in Japan veröffentlicht.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Poke'mon Mini (officiellement stylise'e en Poke'mon mini) est une console de jeu portable conçue et fabrique'e par Nintendo sur le the'me de la franchise me'diatique Poke'mon. Il s'agit de la plus petite console de jeu a' cartouches interchangeables jamais produite par Nintendo, pesant un peu moins de 71 grammes. Elle est sortie pour la premie're fois en Ame'rique du Nord le 16 novembre 2001 (deux jours avant la sortie de la GameCube), puis au Japon le 14 de'cembre 2001 et en Europe le 15 mars 2002. Les consoles ont e'te' commercialise'es en trois couleurs : Wooper Blue, Chikorita Green et Smoochum Purple. Les caracte'ristiques du Poke'mon mini comprennent une horloge interne en temps re'el, un port infrarouge utilise' pour faciliter les jeux multijoueurs, un interrupteur a' lames pour de'tecter les secousses, et un moteur utilise' pour mettre en œuvre le retour de force. Le Poke'mon Channel propose des versions de de'monstration e'mule'es des jeux Poke'mon Mini, y compris l'exclusivite' de la console "Snorlax's Lunch Time". Des jeux tels que "Togepi's Adventure" n'ont e'te' commercialise's qu'au Japon.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il Poke'mon Mini (ufficialmente stilizzato come Poke'mon mini) e' una console portatile progettata e prodotta da Nintendo e incentrata sul franchise mediatico dei Poke'mon. e' la piU' piccola console di gioco con cartucce intercambiabili mai prodotta da Nintendo, con un peso di poco inferiore alle due once e mezzo (71 grammi). e' stata rilasciata per la prima volta in Nord America il 16 novembre 2001 (due giorni prima dell'uscita del GameCube), poi in Giappone il 14 dicembre 2001 e in Europa il 15 marzo 2002. I sistemi sono stati distribuiti in tre colori: Wooper Blue, Chikorita Green e Smoochum Purple. Le caratteristiche del Poke'mon mini includono un orologio interno in tempo reale, una porta a infrarossi utilizzata per facilitare il gioco multigiocatore, un interruttore reed per rilevare le scosse e un motore utilizzato per implementare il force feedback. Poke'mon Channel offre versioni demo emulate giocabili dei giochi Poke'mon Mini, tra cui l'esclusiva della console "Snorlax's Lunch Time". Giochi come "Togepi's Adventure" sono stati rilasciati solo in Giappone.</text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>
				<multiLine>false</multiLine>
				<autoScrollDelay>3000</autoScrollDelay>
				<singleLineScroll>true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>

