<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>TV game (TV game for short) or plug and play game (plug-'n'-play game for short) is an interactive entertainment device designed for use on a television set that integrates the video game console with the game controller. The term "TV game" can be used to refer to any number of self-contained, portable game systems operating on either batteries or an electronic power supply which plugs directly into a TV or VCR. The game software is built directly into the unit, which is typically designed to look like a toy or classic game console/controller with the addition of two AV ports. These systems usually contain either highly specialized games or activities, or a collection of classic games. Thus, it could be viewed as a video game console without interchangeable game software. As the game software is integrated into the game unit and almost never designed to be changed by the user, these game systems are typically sold by retailers as electronic toys or collectibles rather than game consoles.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">El juego de televisión (juego de televisión para abreviar) o juego plug and play (juego plug-'n'-play para abreviar) es un dispositivo de entretenimiento interactivo diseñado para su uso en un televisor que integra la consola de videojuegos con el mando de juego. El te'rmino "juego de televisión" puede utilizarse para referirse a cualquier número de sistemas de juego autónomos y portátiles que funcionan con pilas o con una fuente de alimentación electrónica que se conecta directamente a un televisor o vídeo. El software del juego está integrado directamente en la unidad, que suele estar diseñada para parecerse a un juguete o a una consola/controlador de juegos clásicos con la adición de dos puertos AV. Estos sistemas suelen contener juegos o actividades muy especializados, o una colección de juegos clásicos. Por tanto, podría considerarse una videoconsola sin software de juego intercambiable. Como el software del juego está integrado en la unidad de juego y casi nunca está diseñado para ser cambiado por el usuario, estos sistemas de juego suelen ser vendidos por los minoristas como juguetes electrónicos o artículos de colección en lugar de consolas de juegos.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">TV-Spiel (kurz TV-Spiel) oder Plug-and-Play-Spiel (kurz Plug-'n'-Play-Spiel) ist ein interaktives Unterhaltungsgerät, das für die Verwendung auf einem Fernsehgerät konzipiert ist und die Videospielkonsole mit dem Spielcontroller integriert. Der Begriff "TV-Spiel" kann sich auf eine beliebige Anzahl von eigenständigen, tragbaren Spielsystemen beziehen, die entweder mit Batterien oder einem elektronischen Netzteil betrieben werden, das direkt an einen Fernseher oder Videorecorder angeschlossen wird. Die Spielesoftware ist direkt in das Gerät integriert, das in der Regel wie ein Spielzeug oder eine klassische Spielkonsole/ein klassischer Spielcontroller aussieht und zusätzlich über zwei AV-Anschlüsse verfügt. Diese Systeme enthalten in der Regel entweder hochspezialisierte Spiele oder Aktivitäten oder eine Sammlung von klassischen Spielen. Man könnte sie also als Videospielkonsole ohne austauschbare Spielesoftware betrachten. Da die Spielesoftware in die Spieleinheit integriert ist und fast nie vom Benutzer geändert werden kann, werden diese Spielesysteme von den Einzelhändlern in der Regel als elektronisches Spielzeug oder Sammlerstücke und nicht als Spielkonsolen verkauft.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Le jeu TV (TV game en abre'ge') ou jeu plug and play (plug-'n'-play game en abre'ge') est un appareil de divertissement interactif conçu pour être utilise' sur un te'le'viseur et qui inte'gre la console de jeu vide'o et la manette de jeu. Le terme "jeu te'le'vise'" peut être utilise' pour de'signer un certain nombre de syste'mes de jeu autonomes et portables fonctionnant soit avec des piles, soit avec une alimentation e'lectronique qui se branche directement sur un te'le'viseur ou un magne'toscope. Le logiciel de jeu est inte'gre' directement dans l'unite', qui est ge'ne'ralement conçue pour ressembler a' un jouet ou a' une console/contrôleur de jeu classique, avec l'ajout de deux ports AV. Ces syste'mes contiennent ge'ne'ralement des jeux ou des activite's tre's spe'cialise's, ou une collection de jeux classiques. Ils peuvent donc être conside're's comme des consoles de jeux vide'o sans logiciel de jeu interchangeable. Comme le logiciel de jeu est inte'gre' dans l'unite' de jeu et n'est presque jamais conçu pour être modifie' par l'utilisateur, ces syste'mes de jeu sont ge'ne'ralement vendus par les de'taillants comme des jouets e'lectroniques ou des objets de collection plutôt que comme des consoles de jeu.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Il gioco televisivo (in breve TV game) o gioco plug and play (in breve plug-'n'-play game) e' un dispositivo di intrattenimento interattivo progettato per essere utilizzato su un televisore che integra la console per videogiochi con il controller di gioco. Il termine "gioco televisivo" puo' essere utilizzato per indicare un numero qualsiasi di sistemi di gioco portatili e autonomi che funzionano a batterie o con un alimentatore elettronico che si collega direttamente a un televisore o a un videoregistratore. Il software di gioco e' incorporato direttamente nell'unita', che in genere e' progettata per assomigliare a una console/controller giocattolo o a un gioco classico, con l'aggiunta di due porte AV. Questi sistemi di solito contengono giochi o attivita' altamente specializzate, oppure una collezione di giochi classici. Pertanto, possono essere considerati come una console per videogiochi senza software di gioco intercambiabile. Poiche' il software di gioco e' integrato nell'unita' di gioco e non e' quasi mai progettato per essere modificato dall'utente, questi sistemi di gioco sono in genere venduti dai rivenditori come giocattoli elettronici o oggetti da collezione piuttosto che come console di gioco.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




