<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>
	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <text>The Commodore Plus/4 is a home computer released by Commodore International in 1984. The "Plus/4" name refers to the four-application ROM resident office suite (word processor, spreadsheet, database, and graphing); it was billed as "the productivity computer with software built-in." Internally, the Plus/4 shared the same basic architecture as the lower-end Commodore 16 and 116 models, and was able to use software and peripherals designed for them. The Plus/4 was incompatible with the Commodore 64's software and some of its hardware. Although the Commodore 64 was more established, the Plus/4 was aimed at the more business oriented part of the personal computer market. While the Plus/4 had some success in Europe, it was a failure in the United States, where it was derided as the "Minus/60".<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="es">El Commodore Plus/4 es un ordenador dome'stico lanzado por Commodore International en 1984. El nombre "Plus/4" hace referencia a la suite ofimática residente en ROM con cuatro aplicaciones (procesador de textos, hoja de cálculo, base de datos y gráficos); se anunciaba como "el ordenador de productividad con software incorporado". Internamente, el Plus/4 compartía la misma arquitectura básica que los modelos Commodore 16 y 116 de gama baja, y podía utilizar software y perife'ricos diseñados para ellos. El Plus/4 era incompatible con el software del Commodore 64 y con parte de su hardware. Aunque el Commodore 64 estaba más consolidado, el Plus/4 se dirigía a la parte más empresarial del mercado de los ordenadores personales. Aunque el Plus/4 tuvo cierto e'xito en Europa, fue un fracaso en Estados Unidos, donde fue ridiculizado como el "Minus/60".<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="de">Der Commodore Plus/4 ist ein Heimcomputer, der 1984 von Commodore International auf den Markt gebracht wurde. Der Name "Plus/4" bezieht sich auf das im ROM enthaltene Office-Paket mit vier Anwendungen (Textverarbeitung, Tabellenkalkulation, Datenbank und Grafik); er wurde als "der Produktivitätscomputer mit eingebauter Software" angepriesen. Intern verfügte der Plus/4 über dieselbe Grundarchitektur wie die günstigeren Commodore 16- und 116-Modelle und war in der Lage, Software und Peripheriegeräte zu verwenden, die für diese Modelle entwickelt worden waren. Der Plus/4 war mit der Software und einem Teil der Hardware des Commodore 64 nicht kompatibel. Obwohl der Commodore 64 etablierter war, richtete sich der Plus/4 an den eher geschäftlich orientierten Teil des Personal Computer Marktes. Während der Plus/4 in Europa einen gewissen Erfolg hatte, war er in den Vereinigten Staaten ein Misserfolg, wo er als "Minus/60" verspottet wurde.<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Commodore Plus/4 est un ordinateur domestique commercialise' par Commodore International en 1984. Le nom "Plus/4" fait re'fe'rence a' la suite bureautique re'sidente en ROM a' quatre applications (traitement de texte, tableur, base de donne'es et graphique) ; il a e'te' pre'sente' comme "l'ordinateur de productivite' avec logiciel inte'gre'". En interne, le Plus/4 partageait la même architecture de base que les mode'les bas de gamme Commodore 16 et 116, et pouvait utiliser les logiciels et pe'riphe'riques conçus pour eux. Le Plus/4 e'tait incompatible avec les logiciels et certains mate'riels du Commodore 64. Bien que le Commodore 64 ait e'te' mieux e'tabli, le Plus/4 e'tait destine' a' la partie du marche' des ordinateurs personnels plus oriente'e vers les entreprises. Si le Plus/4 a connu un certain succe's en Europe, il a e'te' un e'chec aux e'tats-Unis, oU' il a e'te' tourne' en de'rision sous le nom de "Minus/60".<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
			<text lang="it">Il Commodore Plus/4 e' un home computer rilasciato da Commodore International nel 1984. Il nome "Plus/4" si riferisce alla suite da ufficio residente in una ROM con quattro applicazioni (elaboratore di testi, foglio di calcolo, database e grafici); fu pubblicizzato come "il computer per la produttivita' con software integrato". Internamente, il Plus/4 condivideva la stessa architettura di base dei modelli Commodore 16 e 116 di fascia bassa ed era in grado di utilizzare software e periferiche progettati per questi ultimi. Il Plus/4 era incompatibile con il software del Commodore 64 e con parte del suo hardware. Sebbene il Commodore 64 fosse piU' affermato, il Plus/4 si rivolgeva alla parte del mercato dei personal computer piU' orientata al business. Mentre il Plus/4 ebbe un certo successo in Europa, fu un fallimento negli Stati Uniti, dove fu deriso come "Minus/60".<multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>      <multiLine ifSubset="view:Carousel">false</multiLine>
<autoScrollDelay ifSubset="view:Carousel">3000</autoScrollDelay>
<singleLineScroll ifSubset="view:Carousel">true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>
</theme>




