<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>
	<include>./../theme.xml</include>

	<view name="system">
                <image name="systemsnap" extra="true">
                   <origin>0.5 0.5</origin>
                   <pos>0.5 0.5</pos>
                   <maxSize>0.8 0.7</maxSize>
                   <path>./_inc/systemsnap.png</path>
                </image>
 		<text name="systemDesc" extra="true">
         <pos>0.95 0.8</pos>
         <origin>1 0</origin>
         <size>0.90 0.1</size>
         <backgroundColor>00000000</backgroundColor>
         <color>F5F5F5</color>
         <fontPath>${themePath}/_inc/fonts/SF Slapstick Comic Bold.ttf</fontPath>
         <fontSize>0.055</fontSize>
         <text>EDuke32 is an awesome, free homebrew game engine and source port of the classic PC first person shooter Duke Nukem 3D— Duke3D for short—to Windows, Linux, Mac OS X, FreeBSD, several handhelds, your family toaster, and to your girlfriend's vibrator. Thousands of cool and useful features and upgrades for regular players and additional editing capabilities and scripting extensions for homebrew developers and mod creators have beem added. EDuke32 is open source software that is completely free to use for all non-commercial purposes. Created by Duke4.net community leader Richard "TerminX" Gobeille and a team of elite ninja programmers including Pierre-Loup "Plagman" Griffais, Philipp "Helixhorned" Kutin, and Evan "Hendricks266" Ramos (based on work by Todd Replogle/Ken Silverman/Jonathon Fowler/Matt Saettler), EDuke32 is the undeniable king of Duke Nukem 3D ports.</text>
			<text lang="es">EDuke32 es un impresionante motor de juego casero gratuito y un port del clásico shooter en primera persona para PC Duke Nukem 3D -Duke3D para abreviar- a Windows, Linux, Mac OS X, FreeBSD, varios dispositivos portátiles, la tostadora de tu familia y el vibrador de tu novia. Se han añadido miles de funciones y mejoras interesantes y útiles para los jugadores habituales, así como capacidades de edición adicionales y extensiones de secuencias de comandos para desarrolladores caseros y creadores de mods. EDuke32 es un software de código abierto totalmente gratuito para todos los fines no comerciales. Creado por Richard "TerminX" Gobeille, líder de la comunidad Duke4.net, y un equipo de programadores ninja de élite entre los que se encuentran Pierre-Loup "Plagman" Griffais, Philipp "Helixhorned" Kutin y Evan "Hendricks266" Ramos (basado en el trabajo de Todd Replogle/Ken Silverman/Jonathon Fowler/Matt Saettler), EDuke32 es el rey indiscutible de los ports de Duke Nukem 3D.</text>
			<text lang="de">EDuke32 ist eine fantastische, kostenlose Homebrew-Spielengine und Source-Portierung des klassischen PC-Ego-Shooters Duke Nukem 3D - kurz Duke3D - für Windows, Linux, Mac OS X, FreeBSD, verschiedene Handhelds, den Toaster der Familie und den Vibrator der Freundin. Tausende von coolen und nützlichen Features und Upgrades für normale Spieler und zusätzliche Bearbeitungsmöglichkeiten und Skripterweiterungen für Homebrew-Entwickler und Mod-Ersteller wurden hinzugefügt. EDuke32 ist eine Open-Source-Software, die für alle nicht-kommerziellen Zwecke völlig kostenlos genutzt werden kann. EDuke32 wurde von Richard "TerminX" Gobeille, dem Leiter der Duke4.net-Community, und einem Team von Elite-Ninja-Programmierern wie Pierre-Loup "Plagman" Griffais, Philipp "Helixhorned" Kutin und Evan "Hendricks266" Ramos (basierend auf der Arbeit von Todd Replogle/Ken Silverman/Jonathon Fowler/Matt Saettler) entwickelt und ist der unbestrittene König der Duke Nukem 3D-Portierungen.</text>
			<text lang="fr">EDuke32 est un moteur de jeu homebrew gratuit et un portage source du jeu de tir à la première personne Duke Nukem 3D (Duke3D) sur Windows, Linux, Mac OS X, FreeBSD, plusieurs ordinateurs de poche, le grille-pain familial et le vibromasseur de votre petite amie. Des milliers de fonctionnalités et d'améliorations intéressantes et utiles pour les joueurs réguliers, ainsi que des capacités d'édition supplémentaires et des extensions de script pour les développeurs de homebrew et les créateurs de mods ont été ajoutées. EDuke32 est un logiciel open source dont l'utilisation est entièrement gratuite à des fins non commerciales. Créé par Richard "TerminX" Gobeille, leader de la communauté Duke4.net, et une équipe de programmeurs ninja d'élite comprenant Pierre-Loup "Plagman" Griffais, Philipp "Helixhorned" Kutin et Evan "Hendricks266" Ramos (sur la base du travail de Todd Replogle/Ken Silverman/Jonathon Fowler/Matt Saettler), EDuke32 est le roi incontestable des portages de Duke Nukem 3D.</text>
			<text lang="it">EDuke32 è un fantastico motore di gioco homebrew gratuito e un port sorgente del classico sparatutto in prima persona per PC Duke Nukem 3D - Duke3D per brevità - su Windows, Linux, Mac OS X, FreeBSD, diversi palmari, il tostapane di famiglia e il vibratore della vostra ragazza. Sono stati aggiunti migliaia di funzioni e aggiornamenti utili e interessanti per i giocatori abituali e ulteriori capacità di editing ed estensioni di scripting per gli sviluppatori di homebrew e i creatori di mod. EDuke32 è un software open source completamente libero di essere utilizzato per tutti gli scopi non commerciali. Creato dal leader della comunità Duke4.net Richard "TerminX" Gobeille e da un team di programmatori ninja d'élite, tra cui Pierre-Loup "Plagman" Griffais, Philipp "Helixhorned" Kutin e Evan "Hendricks266" Ramos (sulla base del lavoro di Todd Replogle/Ken Silverman/Jonathon Fowler/Matt Saettler), EDuke32 è l'indiscutibile re dei port di Duke Nukem 3D.</text>       
      <zIndex>100</zIndex>
		 <alignment>left</alignment>
				<multiLine>false</multiLine>
				<autoScrollDelay>3000</autoScrollDelay>
				<singleLineScroll>true</singleLineScroll>
      </text>
	</view>

</theme>